pwnbase: o shit FIRST
Bloodswordz88: Hail brothers and sisters
lawli3t__: hi
homestarr: yooooo
birkett0011: weeeeeeeeeeeeeew
lawli3t__: first
5_betbluff: What Up son
benchai18: Two
zartharus: Seco d
youngsachi: TriHard
pwnbase: Lmao you call yourself a geohot fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
zartharus: Third
Leon_Trolltsky: Woo
benchai18: Whatup nucka
DlShLe: what up
wizardwatch1: Yo
desg92: hack the planet
jbnunn: fifth-ish
5_betbluff: NJ represent
benchai18: Great. Another night of not doing shit
JaeGeeTee: George!!! We are LinkedIn connections. I can die content.
lawli3t__: xdd I WAS FIRST BROOO
lawli3t__: sdfmlsd
Mieer: No way
Teo0308: yoo
Bloodswordz88: HahaThisisfine
twinprimes71: bro
birkett0011: LUL
benchai18: Stop streaming George. I do nothing but watch u when ur on
shanumbra: LUL
Mieer: Suuup folks
T3chHS: good evening
sebastianh_777: hya
sebastianh_777: eya*
Mieer: Mirceua is here
lawli3t__: But I was playong Minecraft so
sebastianh_777: dammit
twinprimes71: bro geo
lawli3t__: good bye
Bloodswordz88: who is going to survive the presidential election is more like it
Ayyyy420Lmao: !uptime
benchai18: @lawli3t__ I know stfu 😉
Mieer: It is 3 PM here in Amsterdam
homestarr: thats hella morbid
twinprimes71: bro geohot
benchai18: George do u eat ass?
Mieer: George,
goldensoap_: where is your one milion followers on instagram
benchai18: George they gave u a blue check yesterday btw
Ayyyy420Lmao: how does augur get its data since the oracle problem is unsolvable? aka chainlink is a scam Kappa
danbokhari98: Does anyone here know image processing
nic0latesla: i love you
xXICEW0LFXx: currently doing homework with assembly..... and i want to die
benchai18: I don’t even know what Augur is
Ayyyy420Lmao: @danbokhari98 im skilled on mspaint
55start: can someone explain what is happening lol
joker2k999: LUL
benchai18: Can’t u make one?
Mieer: Today I bought a shit-ton on Toilet Paper
padahou: So annoying that I live in Greece and it’s like 4 am right now ...... at least quarantine
danbokhari98: @Ayyyy420Lmao help me find the raster image of color slicing
Mieer: Isn't everyone looking at Italy?
Mieer: optimise your graph with Italy's data as of now
hanycodes: what did you conclude after 5 days of this ?
zartharus: At last. I’ve being following this series 1 day behind on YouTube this whole time. Finally when I scream at the screen George will be able to react. It won’t just be a video
kraplife: @padahou i know right?
lordkyrus: im italian, the situation is ridicolous
bsx1123: Please port Renault
twinprimes71: mentality beast
birkett0011: Congrats
Mieer: Nice congrats on the advancements on your company !
bsx1123: Renault Zoe
Ayyyy420Lmao: SKODA not sold in america?
jbnunn: let's get to Land rover
C0deCane: fuck yea been waiting on some bio today
flippe31: decent prediction site: https://neherlab.org/covid19/
almonte550: Is this a comma ai stream?
jbnunn: it's a ford basically
Mieer: The French will be pissed
5_betbluff: what's a safe amount of beef jerky to eat in a day?
Mieer: lol
goldensoap_: geothoot how are u so smart
o______________________k: ty for streaming today :)
guacDev: george!!!!!
Mieer: Land Rover / Jaguar
guacDev: youre streaming a lot lately
yaus_baus: tata owns vw
Bloodswordz88: shout out to Scotty Kilmer lol
yaus_baus: dont they
homestarr: bio stats is done in r not python :(
DirectorHomeless: using the data from other countries is potentially flawed for a number of reasons, not least the issues with testing
OrlinTheMage: make love to me Geo!
benchai18: Last night the unofficial Geohotz discord was made. It’s not gonna be dope til y’all join. For crazy people who like similar shit https://discord.gg/FuWwMFD
Mieer: I was in India last July.. dude.. I was driven by a TATA vihicle in the middle of the night and this car.. XD I barely got to point B.
JaeGeeTee: Bro!!!!!! You can’t comma ai stream!!!!! That’s fucking sacrilige
Cazaa_: hi george!!
Mieer: Wait what website is that?
lordkyrus: people are dying every day just because the hospitals are full. We have more deaths than china..
rafalive: hey george do you still live in montreal?
amo77777: It's bad here in Germany, but I think the UK is going to have massive problems
Stegosaurian: Can someone gift me a sub if you can. I wanted to watch the last steam but the video is only available for subs
kratosboii: sup george @georgehotz
Lizardan: This corona crisis might actually get Trump elected november.
matvey_ryabov: Do i need to watch the prior 4 coronastreams to understand this one?
logi6000: what's up. how's your day
frostism1: just came. Can someone link again?
bichid69: ml for video absolutely sucks man
archer723: even with the prior 4 maybe you still cannot understand...
bichid69: what a joke
luigifrcruz: If you need a global COVID-19 Forecasting dataset. Here is a pretty good one. https://www.kaggle.com/c/covid19-global-forecasting-week-1/data
C0deCane: I feel like there may be some big guessing going on there but I could be wrong
dog_runner09: hello from Nigeria
ad5k: Hello scholars
logi6000: what's up
almonte550: I think 3 millions is worth hurting the economy
Ayyyy420Lmao: just lower the population to the infectable population
FurikuriYugi: Yo yo yo what up fam
sebastianh_777: What are you trying to write here with these corona stream?
Mieer: Hmm.. do you think India will out-'perform' the US in spread and dynamics of this virus? I mean what will the carrying capacity be in India
hypertextlabs: you hear about helm.ai?
bichid69: what do you do when you're not streaming?
hypertextlabs: https://www.helm.ai/
imafungi53: whats the goal
benchai18: @georgehotz U watch Lex’s video??
amo77777: @imafungi53 creative exploration
C0deCane: @georgehotz I heard today that there is 40 different mutations that have been found
FurikuriYugi: Fear will cause stress and make your immune system weaker
OmegaThicccBoi: LUL
youngsachi: LUL
Ghost_001: LUL
liiiiiig0: LUL
hypertextlabs: have you heard of what they are doing?
FurikuriYugi: Kreygasm
Ayyyy420Lmao: probably an ICO scam
DirectorHomeless: the problem lies in the testing. arguably the only dataset where they had proper observations was the diamond princess, where everyone was tested, even if not displaying symptoms. it transpired 85% had contracted it iirc but most had no reaction. this would point to much higher existing infections and lower mortality rate...
Ghost_001: D:
deva73: yo!
benchai18: @georgehotz U watch Lex’s video??
lordkyrus: LUL
angel_j_a: they just raised $13M
Mieer: Hmm.. do you think India will out-'perform' the US in spread and dynamics of this virus? I mean what will the carrying capacity be in India
C0deCane: comma ai > helm ai
Ziv0: LUL
r0xtehem0x: Elisa Lam
Ayyyy420Lmao: lam
benchai18: @c0decane Nepotist
hypertextlabs: why the f did they just raise 13m
kratosboii: whos this chick @georgehotz
benchai18: Elisa lam
Ayyyy420Lmao: why does she have awikipedia entry?
benchai18: That was me too
benchai18: Elisa lam
v0sn: helm ai sucks
jbnunn: @benchai18 which episode from Lex?
hypertextlabs: yea that's why I brought garbage into the chat lol
benchai18: She does
sebastianh_777: What are you writing in this stream?
hypertextlabs: lol
benchai18: She did****
Rovelo: LUL
stalys_: LUL
hypertextlabs: your mad now yess
brownyyyylocks: yo
Rovelo: LICENSING LVL 2 LUL
v0sn: openai > helm ai
elliotc90: george how did you get into programming?
soeim: good job triggering him
Ghost_001: LUL
C0deCane: @benchai18 i like open source better bro
WatchMeFailPlay: New Jersey represent! Big fan since I was 14. You're the reason I got into the world jailbreaking. Big ups man
miiiiiiim: people with money dont like the words open source
Abnico: darwinsim
hypertextlabs: that's my question right
benchai18: @jbnunn His coronavirus video. YT: “Lex Friedman corona”
Mieer: @georgehotz - Will India out-perform US in virus spread and dynamics ??
birkett0011: @georgehotz you done much in simulation? https://hash.ai/
hypertextlabs: tru Tru srry
benchai18: @c0decane No bro. NO!
OmegaThicccBoi: LUL
hypertextlabs: back to CV//19
C0deCane: lol brooooooo
Rashad242: let's hack
jbnunn: ty @benchai18
brownyyyylocks: Anyone have link to the space casino book from yesterday stream?
bichid69: brum brum with the boom boom
benchai18: @c0decane Would u be my bro, brah?
logi6000: anyone have that link about hacking yesterday
lordkyrus: lordkyrus subscribed with Twitch Prime.
logi6000: that book
almonte550: 0.8 millions only?
r0xtehem0x: Can you explain the % of total? those look high
elliotc90: @georgehotz do something useful bro, you are not going to make any breakthrough in this field. You know literally 0
brittonx2: great news
Mieer: How bad can coronavirus get in the US? We’re about to find out. https://www.datawrapper.de/_/CUi1z/
logi6000: @elliotc90 you never know man
bichid69: @elliotc90 its not about results ITS THE JOURNEY BRO
Landowner555: fuck seriously, 6 weeks?
Ayyyy420Lmao: just flatten the curve over 10 years lmao
Rovelo: 8 people at our company went to austria for skiing and all 8 came back with coronavirus monkaS
Greaser_1: Hi, from Portugal!
elliotc90: @logi6000 of course we do. He has no background in this field. To think he can do something is very naive.
benchai18: Btw tried the fish tank cleaner last night. Didn’t work. Fucking killed me actually.
stalys_: monkaS
s0rrz: bro let people have fun @elliotc90
Mieer: If Corona is not killing us.. it will be the quarantine that will. We are SOCIAL beings.. I don't think I can remain at home until June
Mieer: 6 weeks is ALOT
nomad119: Comma Bio would've let them know for sure.
bichid69: 6 WEEKS OF SUCK YO
Srule: Would a 60% key board be ok for watching pornhub?
bigduddas: squadHYPERS no school
Ayyyy420Lmao: a life of suck
miiiiiiim: @elliotc90 how dare you mess around with something you dont understand
logi6000: @elliotc90 even if he doesn't get any results. it's about the journey. plus he never streams and now he does
almonte550: Are some people already immune from exposure to other coronavirus?
Rovelo: @almonte550 no
Ayyyy420Lmao: do they even have models
almonte550: @Rovelo link?
elliotc90: @logi6000 at least he could do something he is good at tbh. I guess its okay tho
bichid69: the UK are using a C based model from 13 years ago
Lizardan: Wait how did he snap windows to the side on a MAc?
Mieer: I am off to sleep. I have an exam in 2 days
logi6000: @srule no you need more room to catch the cum
Rovelo: @almonte550 wdym? its a different virus from other coronaviruses
Mieer: People out my dudes
yungdeli_: what do you do during the day>
liiiiiig0: LUL
brownyyyylocks: u guys the book link from yesterday!! anyone remember?
mritzing: part of the problem is a lot of it is being handled at a state by state level, so there's 50 different chances for incompetence there
brittonx2: they do what they do because the general population would lose their minds if they knew the truth
bichid69: MULTI SEQUENCE ALIGNMENT
bichid69: DYNAMIC PROGRAMMING YO
Ayyyy420Lmao: heuristics algo for alignement
Rovelo: @almonte550 you can't expect to develop immunity to coronavirus if you have something completely different
stalys_: only in NY?
aaaakshat: LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: who cares torrents > premium
yaus_baus: stay flattened bros
aaaakshat: pornhub stonks going up now
Rovelo: @almonte550 or novel coronavirus i mean
o______________________k: going there now !
Lizardan: premium is bad
logi6000: I now have plans after the stream
1monkjuice: i mean youre talking about it now
firmstool: SOME people. PEPE
Mieer: XD
bigduddas: 420lamo ok dud
slimpimp007: this is a simp trap
1monkjuice: i might even drop a visit now
Lizardan: It's even more fake
1monkjuice: they do a lot with ads
aaaakshat: just get adblock bro
Mint2bSpiced: Basic Local Alignment Search Tool (BLAST) finds regions of similarity between biological sequences. The program compares nucleotide or protein sequences to sequence databases and calculates the statistical significance.
Mieer: I am more interested in India (virus spread and dynamics)
Ozonemaster: how useless is it tho
Jehhred: homemade POV wil always be the best
DirectorHomeless: its fake af in 4k tho
leftyytwo: let's watch some pornhub premium together on stream
ad5k: Is pornhub actually a public company lol
Ayyyy420Lmao: there's a paper
logi6000: @leftyytwo I second that
Ayyyy420Lmao: look the original paper tha published blast
dsqst: Aight!
mritzing: i can see if i can find my old prof's pdb workshops :
wizardwatch1: OpenStax
happypuppppy: Molecular Biology of the Cell is pretty standard
Landowner555: i havea 4th ed of alberts essential biology Kappa
jimmyadaro: Sup boys
DatGuyToby: a man has as many masters as he has vices
eiscosogin1: i just did a lit review on machine learning
Ghost_001: practical knowledge is better, get that pornhub prem
Landowner555: essential cell biology*
1monkjuice: andrew Ng?
jbnunn: Sebastian's course
DatGuyToby: porn is control
deva73: what are views on fastai?
almonte550: @Rovelo I mean, what our antibodies look to find the virus is the spike and the nucleocapsid, are they so different that our body takes them as different things? for example the spike of sars and covid-19
mutrx: yo
birkett0011: Have you messed with RL in simulation ?
Srule: mindgeek
Mint2bSpiced: Molecular Biology of the Cell 6th Edition
Landowner555: "mom this isnt what it looks like"
Landowner555: yeah this one
logi6000: @landowner555 lmao
almonte550: @Rovelo when I said "they" I meant coronaviruses
aaaakshat: Most sin stocks aren't listed on public exchanges
happypuppppy: yea the 6th edition
Srule: pornhub goes by mind geek for corporate stuff.
DirectorHomeless: no porn companies are public, investors just buy infrastructure stocks since margins on porn are razor thin
Landowner555: i have the 4th edition of this book if u want, its not that good
aaaakshat: and investing in porn sounds weird
brownyyyylocks: Cellular and Molecular Immunology By Abbas, Lichtman, Pillai
elliotc90: comma ai doesnt have its own machine learning library. Most of you guys have no clue how it works in actuality. Not even george
Rovelo: @almonte550 yes
ak0ya_: Essential Cell Biology textbook
samosasauce8: https://github.com/kerasking/book-1/blob/master/ML Machine Learning-A Probabilistic Perspective.pdf
toldhow: why don't you take programming courses? from beginner to apocalyptic hacker??
Kodaly: mrmLaff
Rovelo: @almonte550 in very simple terms
brownyyyylocks: Modern Virology by Dimmock, Easton, Leppard
guinness84: LUL
guinness84: here we go
tupypaint: lol bout to get roasted
stalys_: PogChamp
FastCashCoding: lol
Incurs0: called out LUL
aaaakshat: eliotc90 is a troll he's been saying crap like this for a while nows
youngsachi: PogChamp
eiscosogin1: why write a library when other libraries are REALLY good
liiiiiig0: lol @elliotc90 gonna get rekt
Ziv0: elliotc90 is a troll
stalys_: roast incoming
ren1ght: coronavirus fetish
ak0ya_: https://www.amazon.com/Essential-Biology-Fifth-Bruce-Alberts-ebook/dp/B07TJJTGTV
Ayyyy420Lmao: why would u need ur own library just use that tool from google
Bloodswordz88: invest in porn. its future proof
hexicity1: @elliotc90 ...
Kodaly: what is the worst case runtime of randomized quick sort
logi6000: can't wait to see how this turns out
Program: good evening everyone
slimpimp007: LUL
brittonx2: LOL, did you get more groceries today or are the bags from yesterday? lol
mutrx: @elliotc90
Ghost_001: LUL
1monkjuice: 1monkjuice subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months!
1monkjuice: officially funding coronavirus research
s0rrz: @elliotc90 cmon
FastCashCoding: @elliotc90 explain DansGame
Ghost_001: FANN >
eiscosogin1: tensorflow isnt good enoguh for me reeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
logi6000: Elliot you gonna speak up
christianthefalco: UWU hacker daddy pls gib more book recos uwu
aaaakshat: LUL
Landowner555: this is THE standard in bio classes
shaquille_oatmeal5: paging elliot
Landowner555: 2nd/3rd
stalys_: don't deprive us of a good roast FeelsBadMan
tupypaint: dude is googling hard rn
FastCashCoding: lol
Landowner555: LUL "BEST BOOK EVER"
Incurs0: he left chat LUL
logi6000: maybe Elliot is just typing we will see
hexicity1: George Hotz is my favourite instagram influencer
pwnbase: @tupypaint he's googling how to unshit your pants
aaaakshat: hahahahjahaha
wizardwatch1: The openstax books are pretty good. They are free in the app or cheap for print
Usisuvach0: @georgehotz put sumamed in treatments also
s0rrz: maybe he some kind of genius
r0xtehem0x: r0xtehem0x subscribed at Tier 1.
tacorising3: @tupypaint lol
Landowner555: elliot90c is busy making season 6
aaaakshat: @eliotc90 where you gone buddy
OopsyPoosy: heya!
DirectorHomeless: imagine walking into the boardroom on a wednesday, meeting with the big boss, and he asks 'so, what have we bought recently?' 'well, we bought €500M AAPL, €150M NVDA and €800M PORN'
Usisuvach0: sumamed=pill
Ghost_001: machine learning streams when FeelsBadMan
Lizardan: h'es so gay
bcrscahh198987: !uptime
Kodaly: biology is pointless pretty soon humans wil lbe made from computers
logi6000: Elliot you gonna speak up
ad5k: Eliot doesn’t have time for you brainlets
ak0ya_: https://www.amazon.com/Essential-Biology-Fifth-Bruce-Alberts-ebook/dp/B07TJJTGTV this is a very good book for how cell works
birkett0011: MICOLOCONDRAIA IS POWER HOUSE OF THE CELL
yaus_baus: minecraft streams when
Rovelo: @almonte550 and not only that but vaccines can have unintended consequences aswell that have to be tested, and can have varying degrees of effectiveness
Usisuvach0: google sumamed
Program: can you get a textbook just on 'DNA'?
bcrscahh198987: You have an interesting life mr hotz
l1ght5p33d: We learned so much know protien Chem !!!!
C4TFive: the mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell, we know this!
Ayyyy420Lmao: Cellular and Molecular Immunology 9th Edition Authors: Abul Abbas Andrew H. Lichtman Shiv Pillai this was the reference book for our inmunology credits
happypuppppy: LUL
Landowner555: are u gonna pirate these? legit want to know if its possible
Landowner555: IM NOT FBI
hexicity1: George how do you remain focused? i swear i have ADHD and cant focus on something i want to do sometimes
33333333333333: mitochondria is the power house of the cell bro. c'mon man, basic knowledge
brownyyyylocks: @ayyyy420lmao I have this textbook!
Ghost_001: botted reviews LUL
leftyytwo: elliot deleted his twithc acc
WatchMeFailPlay: eliot dipped
ak0ya_: I learned cell biology from that book
logi6000: @leftyytwo no way
Ayyyy420Lmao: @brownyyyylocks i pirated it :^DDD
hexicity1: George how do you remain focused? i swear i have ADHD and cant focus on something i want to do sometimes :/
optimizely: how do you think of interesting projects to work on?
leftyytwo: elliotc90: Tell me about how modern AI is just statistics and it is in no way capable of creating AGI. Also tell me why
l1ght5p33d: Substrate Reagent = WINN
Ghost_001: @hexicity1 coke
atzehji: do we have some goal for the end of this series? @georgehotz
liiiiiig0: @Landowner555 just google Library Genesis
tupypaint: lol
youngsachi: LUL
blueglue321: How long does it take you to absorb a textbook?
christianthefalco: @hexicity1 pathetic
C0deCane: You order the lab equipment yet? @georgehotz
kp1877: Can I get a PlayStation rap? It would make my quarantine
hexicity1: @Ghost_001 tempting
logi6000: he spoken
lordkyrus: adderal
nomad119: We
hexicity1: @christianthefalco pathetic?
aaaakshat: do you speed read?
Landowner555: @liiiiiig0 oh ive heard about it
1monkjuice: this is like a course of how to learn
brownyyyylocks: LOL!! It's standard for 3rd yr immunology at my uni
Usisuvach0: https://www.drugs.com/international/sumamed.html they say this might be good
Landowner555: ty
nomad119: We all know that the layout matters
liiiiiig0: @Landowner555 np
logi6000: the hater spoke
ad5k: Speed reading is scam
optimizely: how do you think of projects to work on?
almonte550: @Rovelo and that's true because they are different viruses only? even tho they have almost the same spike which is the thing that antibodies are looking for?
stalys_: 4Head
happypuppppy: oh no plz just ignore the troll
youngsachi: 4Head
Jehhred: Next week he'll have a full blown lab with beakers and shit
yaus_baus: lmao
happypuppppy: he's cuttin into bio time
Lizardan: @optimizely by using his brain
WatchMeFailPlay: lmaoo
Ayyyy420Lmao: tulsi gabbard is hot
l1ght5p33d: RON PAULLL
Incurs0: comma.ai.bio
PiroFloydian: JEB
PiroFloydian: JEB JEB JEB
b1nk: i want tulsi to step on me
alwayxtoxic: supervised learning is just statistics
eiscosogin1: tulsi is hot and has half sane politics
FastCashCoding: rip ron paul
YoshikawaDotA: kek
mutrx: @georgehotz elliotc90: Tell me about what size of a total problem space is needed in order for a neural network to be able to "solve" it.
FastCashCoding: corona gonna take him out and all his btc
wizardwatch1: https://openstax.org/details/books/biology
Srule: man cracks iPhone in 2009, chat thinks he can hack a corona vaccine.
yaus_baus: supervised learning = excel regressions
optimizely: George how do you think of projects to work on?
theonlymonkas: bernie
C4TFive: How would the secret service protect Tulsi while she surfed? HahaThink
OopsyPoosy: 4am right now better see some progress
mritzing: Ron paul said coronavirus was a hoax, then rand paul got it
FurikuriYugi: Do you even science bro lol
Ayyyy420Lmao: Cellular and Molecular Immunology 9th Edition Authors: Abul Abbas Andrew H. Lichtman Shiv Pillai this was the reference book for our inmunology credits
brittonx2: Cheer100
eric_hansen: @georgehotz thanks for getting me and my entire family hooked on spindrift
almonte550: Hype trainnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnn
aaaakshat: @Srule you'd be surprised at the power of chat
FastCashCoding: PogChamp
Ghost_001: scam train PogChamp
youngsachi: PogChamp
Incurs0: scam train PogChamp
FastCashCoding: lol scam train for sure
ar2zee: why you spent 3 days on coronavirus and we still have this disease
IndoPridePinoy: this streamer hype training off of coronaivurs, shameless
happypuppppy: time to get HYPED PogChamp
mutrx: @georgehotz elliotc90: Tell me about what size of a total problem space is needed in order for a neural network to be able to "solve" it.
FurikuriYugi: They could all catch it and die for all I care
Ayyyy420Lmao: for cell biology we used this one https://www.amazon.com/Molecular-Biology-Cell-Bruce-Alberts/dp/0815341059
wheely_mcbones: Watch the ones written by young proffesors
Ghost_001: not false
FastCashCoding: took 1 semester of cell bio
thekalkulator: hello world
Emanuell45: we all computer science majors here lol
Coolio1232: use the IB biology text book
theonlymonkas: give some book recommendations
logi6000: @georgehotz elliotc90: Tell me about what size of a total problem space is needed in order for a neural network to be able to "solve" it.
YoshikawaDotA: ur trying too hard elliot
Ziv0: elliotc90 took you that long to google that LUL
FastCashCoding: oh god
Vepicfishal: why is it forbidden to talk about typewriter?
Ayyyy420Lmao: trees? i smoke those
ad5k: Eliot couldn’t code a simple LGMA model
mutrx: @Coolio1232 was your IB exams cancelled lmao
l1ght5p33d: is this... SU groups?
mutrx: @georgehotz elliotc90: Tell me about what size of a total problem space is needed in order for a neural network to be able to "solve" it.
Rovelo: @almonte550 the spike binds differently, not by alot but by enough to rule out effective use of sars-cov antibodies for sars-cov-2
Coolio1232: @mutrx nah i graduated last year
FastCashCoding: dang dont be mean
Ayyyy420Lmao: man i linked 2 books
Krlithus: what is your goal?? are u looking to do some contribution to the vaccine research??
mutrx: immunology
thekalkulator: math major here
Incurs0: LUL
happypuppppy: monkaS
birkett0011: rip
almonte550: @Rovelo I see
youngsachi: LUL
FastCashCoding: lol
tupypaint: F
liiiiiig0: LUL
FastCashCoding: rip
yaus_baus: big flex
Emanuell45: f
shaquille_oatmeal5: F
DeathCavalier: F
jermss: pog
RelativeTimes: f
Ghost_001: LUL
PiroFloydian: F
Coolio1232: f
Landowner555: @mutrx immuno is too far left field i think
C0deCane: LUL
wizardwatch1: https://openstax.org/details/books/biology It’s free
purplegreenpanda: LUL
Srule: sorry, i'm straight
brownyyyylocks: BLOCKED
optimizely: @georgehotz how do you think of projects to work on?
FastCashCoding: geohot
lordkyrus: LUL
treestompztv: LUL
DeathCavalier: monkaS
1monkjuice: lmao
brittonx2: lol
logi6000: let's switch from dictator to communism
Emanuell45: @georgehotz becareful he might hack you
theonlymonkas: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
FastCashCoding: nb4 new account
deva73: hail the president
aaaakshat: mmmmblockin out the haters
JMSWRNR: do we need visa to be in this chat Kappa
FurikuriYugi: Boom ban hammer
eric_hansen: @georgehotz look at Campbell Biology by Pearson
TheKoreanZombi: By elliott, you machine larning flat-earther.
s4j0k5: what's basic lab equipment?
toldhow: why don't you take programming courses? from beginner to apocalyptic hacker
Ghost_001: quora LUL
Rovelo: @almonte550 the sequence of the amino acids binds differently to a large enough degree that is
Landowner555: dude theres no best course for biology, they are all tedious and time consuming
mritzing: just bio is super broad
logi6000: @jmswrnr yes your Visa is to follow
theonlymonkas: no news
bsx1123: microbiology
aaaakshat: penis study
wheely_mcbones: information theory in biology, I think is that
FurikuriYugi: All the things
FastCashCoding: lol your alma mater probably discovered comp bio @georgehotz
s4j0k5: what's basic lab equipment?
eric_hansen: @georgehotz I think the field you want to look at is "Synthetic Biology"
ak0ya_: MIT course 7 intro bio with eric lander is veru good
christianthefalco: and
ar2zee: I have K-1 visa
Ghost_001: CoolStoryBob
Landowner555: IaMaBiOlOgY
mutrx: @georgehotz i got biology, immunology and biochemistry notes
deva73: computational neuroscience sounds cool
death_gadget: Let's study Game Theory
AresRai: I am a biology monkaS
Program: monkaGUN
jermss: watch MIT bio course on youtube
aaaakshat: "I am not a computer, I am a biology" -geohot 2k20
FurikuriYugi: Know they self
Ayyyy420Lmao: classes in bio are pretty pointless since they just follow the reference book 90% of the time
C0deCane: just found out im not a robot, thanks corona virus - @georgehotz
Natschz: gift me a sub please
nomad119: https://www.biostarhandbook.com/
brofessorbob: Do you know the Central Dogma of Biology
mritzing: PyMol is the software we'd use to do mol modeling
brofessorbob: ?
treestompztv: w e a r e b i o l o g y
ak0ya_: https://ocw.mit.edu/courses/biology/7-012-introduction-to-biology-fall-2004/index.htm
bttmndl: biology is just physics
Rovelo: @almonte550 if you look at flus, many of the antibodies are similar enough in function to work for future mutations, but mutations are also varied enough that some will be different enough to pass through
Emanuell45: biology sucks, its all about memorization
mutrx: @georgehotz i got biology, immunology and biochemistry notes
l1ght5p33d: you must follow the reference book
eric_hansen: @georgehotz Go look at the field of synthetic biology, I think it will fit what you're looking for
thekalkulator: @Emanuell45 i conquer
lordkyrus: just curious, why he's on a mac?
fxmatd: how long will we be confined?
l1ght5p33d: the reference book is all that is good and holy
brofessorbob: What about biology do you need to know?
lordkyrus: always tought about that
Ghost_001: just throw a NN at it 4Head
C0deCane: @fxmatd until its over
williamjennings1: Hype Train
AresRai: cellular biology train
mutrx: @georgehotz i got biology, immunology and biochemistry notes
brofessorbob: mix and match dna from different specieis
PiroFloydian: 69% nice
fxmatd: when over?
Srule: do you really read that fast or are you just flexing for chat?
ak0ya_: https://www.amazon.com/Physical-Biology-Cell-Rob-Phillips/dp/0815344503 this book is biology from physics perspective
Ghost_001: LUL
brofessorbob: charged atom
ak0ya_: yes! i did
ak0ya_: took it at MIT
Landowner555: no, i paid absurd amounts of money for my courses Kappa
C0deCane: @fxmatd when most of the world decides to give up
Digital_donger: I once read a wikipedia page Kappa
FastCashCoding: missing electron
thekalkulator: wth... is this chemistry?
Ghost_001: negatively charged no ?
almonte550: @Rovelo I was hoping to be immune to multiple coronaviruses just by being immune to covid-19 I guess that can't happen
christianthefalco: in my experience, bio doesn't have great layers of abstraction like software. You kinda need to know chemistry to say anything interesting about genetics
4zimut: (insert-comic-sans-joke)
Ayyyy420Lmao: molecule, you can have an ion of amphetamine
deva73: add or remove electron from atom
brofessorbob: incomplete valence electron
GoBerserk: @thekalkulator the first section is biochemistry
brofessorbob: partial dipole moments
FastCashCoding: the dipoles
C0deCane: Kappa
FastCashCoding: hehe
Emanuell45: @georgehotz wtf how do you remenber that?
fxmatd: @c0decane LUL
thekalkulator: thanks @GoBerserk
edeustua: dispersion force
deva73: charges
brofessorbob: partial dipoles br
brofessorbob: bro
Rovelo: @almonte550 on a positive note though, covid-19 seems to mutate less frequently which means a vaccine could cover for a significantly longer period
AresRai: its not easy to to completely understand
21_savior: yo chat, why use chromium over chrome?
deva73: dipoles right
berkieee: what are any of the forces
mritzing: vanderwales is a tent term
PiroFloydian: @21_savior open source
phyde79: need a course, from the atom to the vaccine
almonte550: @Rovelo ok, that's some good news
mritzing: gromacs pymol
Srule: my main is acing the qui without studying
deva73: nope
FastCashCoding: negative
GoBerserk: you did them backwards
FastCashCoding: POsitive is cation
almonte550: @Rovelo thanks for the clarifications btw!
FastCashCoding: NH
Landowner555: THEY ALL HAVE COOH AND NH2
Digital_donger: @21_savior sometimes less google
deva73: nh2 group
brofessorbob: Correct
edeustua: acid on one side, amino on the other
Ayyyy420Lmao: is this college level?
edeustua: NH3 and COOH
Cammmmy: Is that comic sans?
wizardwatch1: Everything but the r group
Mint2bSpiced: I would also recommend Essential Bioinformatics by Jin Xiong
Rovelo: @almonte550 nps :) love to help inform in these uncertain times
GoBerserk: @Ayyyy420Lmao yes
AresRai: @Ayyyy420Lmao no this i highschool level for now
edeustua: NH2*
ankitc: i fell dumber everysecnd
deva73: electronegativity
Ayyyy420Lmao: looks really basic
PiroFloydian: OH group
GoBerserk: OH
atzehji: why are you interested in biology again?
Landowner555: LUL
l1ght5p33d: Nucleus
Ayyyy420Lmao: nucleus...
edeustua: nucleus!
FastCashCoding: the hydroxl has some positive charge
Rovelo: LUL highschool biology
djcows: Do you have photographic memory?
logi6000: pro has no nuleus
slimpimp007: still glad I took SL chem
ak0ya_: nucleus
logi6000: this is middle school level
l1ght5p33d: Nucleus stuff
alextodoroki: tfw cheating with twitch chat
Landowner555: OLD xd
Ayyyy420Lmao: old kek
l1ght5p33d: Nucleus stuff ** general **
deva73: prokaryotics have primitive nucleus
Emanuell45: @logi6000 still dont understand 0 of it lol
logi6000: @emanuell45 lol
AresRai: prokaryote cells got that easy share system too
mutrx: @georgehotz MDS are pretty cool but if you're trying to use it to predict a specific outcome (mutagenicity, toxicity..etc.) then we've found in our lab that actually calculating various quantum mechanical descriptors from the molecules and deriving a model from this is more accurate than simulating; look into SAMPL6 competition for malaria.
almonte550: @Rovelo actually that give me curiosity of how specific antibodies for a virus are created... I'll research about it later
eric_hansen: georgehotz presents: "Twitch Learns BIology"
jermss: ribosomes make protein
l1ght5p33d: WE WANT MORE RNA SEQUENCE
logi6000: you don't know lysosomes or ribosomes
deva73: talking about nucleus lets shift the dioscussion towards nukes😂
eric_hansen: p r o t e i n
latenightbj: latenightbj subscribed with Twitch Prime.
logi6000: yes
Ayyyy420Lmao: ofc
Emanuell45: no lol
Landowner555: u learn it then u forget it...
GoBerserk: yeah
mutrx: @georgehotz MDS are pretty cool but if you're trying to use it to predict a specific outcome (mutagenicity, toxicity..etc.) then we've found in our lab that actually calculating various quantum mechanical descriptors from the molecules and deriving a model from this is more accurate than simulating; look into SAMPL6 competition for malaria.
Digital_donger: I forgot all of this NotLikeThis
Emanuell45: @Ayyyy420Lmao how do you konw it lol
PiroFloydian: ribosomes are the 3d printers @georgehotz
Rovelo: @almonte550 videos on youtube are a good way to learn the basics fast, use articles and research papers once you have fundamentals down :) happy researching!
Ghost_001: monkaS
FancyDawg_: Hey George can you refresh us on what you are doing?
axlebear: Yeah organic chem guys have all the amino acids grilled into them
eric_hansen: something something lipids something soap wash your hands
Ayyyy420Lmao: abstraction/classification you have the short chain/branched, the acidics the basics the and the aromatics
Ghost_001: bio people are hardcore monkaS
Rovelo: organic chem flashbacks ResidentSleeper
Plurmorant: bio tests monkaS
mutrx: disuphide
Landowner555: THEY ARE
Plurmorant: I beat molek-syntez, so I'm a bit of a legend
logi6000: George do you want a basic bio quizlet
Landowner555: hydrogen bonds
christianthefalco: h bonds baby
GoBerserk: they are h-bonds
RakeRoux: *Don't touch your face
jermss: DNA has hydrogen bonds
Landowner555: mendelian genetics is the hugest waste of time holy fk
Ayyyy420Lmao: mr I dont care about the basis of eugenics wew
logi6000: George do you want a basic bio quizlet
Plurmorant: GTACGTGATCGACG
Landowner555: LMAo
Landowner555: matching pattersn
Landowner555: SeemsGood
Emanuell45: Am i the only one lost with this stuff?
Plurmorant: @Emanuell45 no one here knows bio
mokmuu: @georgehotz this may be useful for later, but there is a terminal based cURL'able stats server - ' curl https://corona-stats.online '
eric_hansen: ResidentSleeper
christianthefalco: regulation baby. shit gets complicated
AresRai: half is artistic matching exam LUL
GoBerserk: @Emanuell45 probably not
joshiemoore: joshiemoore subscribed at Tier 1.
Ayyyy420Lmao: nothing to do
mutrx: @georgehotz MDS are pretty cool but if you're trying to use it to predict a specific outcome (mutagenicity, toxicity..etc.) then we've found in our lab that actually calculating various quantum mechanical descriptors from the molecules and deriving a model from this is more accurate than simulating; look into SAMPL6 competition for malaria.
logi6000: George do you want a basic bio quizlet
Emanuell45: @purplegreenpanda thank god, these people making feel dumb
Landowner555: promoters are just a region of DNA that transcirption factors bind to to initiate transcription
Ayyyy420Lmao: promoteres are dna sequences tha bind to proteins that promote dna transcription of nearby elements
Program: They promote priming ;)
Rovelo: @Emanuell45 its not too bad, just a bit fast if you don't know the basics
SpyKnife: when are you going to beat plague inc? :P
l1ght5p33d: unknown unknowns T_T
Kawhiet: This font makes the quiz seem like its for middle school
logi6000: @spyknife he is the cure bubbles that you forgot to pop
Landowner555: dont waste ur time with sequencing stuff
l1ght5p33d: the one that amplifies it
Musashhhi: these streams are awesome
Ayyyy420Lmao: nope
happypuppppy: @georgehotz you should do 7.103 instead, its also intro bio but with more focus on genetics / cancer / virology
l1ght5p33d: crispr is plasmid fuckings
happypuppppy: 7.013
logi6000: why can't we use CRISPR against rona
Landowner555: HAHA
doretts: @Musashhhi Indeed!
r0xtehem0x: PhD bio friend said this is the standard bio book: https://www.amazon.com/Campbell-Biology-11th-Lisa-Urry but also recommends the one you're leaning towards
happypuppppy: @geohotz 7.013
Landowner555: @r0xtehem0x its not working link
dzid26: instead?
Ayyyy420Lmao: not cell bio tho it's more general
Landowner555: WHO SAYS POOR REFERENCING
christianthefalco: NEW LEX FRIDMAN INTERVIEW
Landowner555: HAHAHAHA
edeustua: thats the basic one
Ghost_001: LUL
Rovelo: 1 STAR FOR CONDITION LUL
eric_hansen: @georgehotz I can attest to the campbell bio book being a good choice
localcanofdutchgold: 5Head
DefinitlyNotXanbot: u can download those books?
Landowner555: dude u had the good cell bio book
r0xtehem0x: Could be a big scam book
C0deCane: make your children glow at night with crisper, buy now for just 46 ez monthly payments of 2500 USD's
Rovelo: GLOBAL WARMING IS A MYTH nymnKRD
AresRai: a few corona viruses were found in the melted ice LUL
1monkjuice: diggin down the rabbit hole 4real
Rovelo: i am fucking terrified with russian permafrost viruses monkaS
Kemisdan: LUL
Landowner555: LMFAO
Incurs0: LUL
almonte550: HAHAHAHAH
birkett0011: LUL
alicyka: biology without ecology is just learning a single organism
Hawklite: increase global warming to kill coronavirus is the only answer
happypuppppy: @geohotz 7.013, i typed it wrong last time
Landowner555: @alicyka ecology sucks bro
logi6000: @hawklite ah yes the final solition
MrStereoX: Hey ! @georgehotz have you ever heard about the "black cube" company ?
ron1n541: ron1n541 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
PiroFloydian: @Hawklite and release long dead viruses frozen in ice
l1ght5p33d: With catalytic converter you can burn 1000 gallons doesn't matter for the environment
wholesome_pepe: systems biology is what ur looking for
1monkjuice: 7.013 7.013 7.013
1monkjuice: ye
alicyka: well I'm too drunk and dumb to know anything so you can't convince me landowner
0deinkymi0: check out library genesis for free pdfs (it's legal too)
alicyka: i win
Landowner555: Keepo
onemarko: did you hear about cell phone subscriptions drop in china? conspiracy?
guinness84: can you repeat that
latenightbj: @0deinkymi0 lol i was literally pullling thee books on there
Landowner555: DNA MAN
wholesome_pepe: systems bio is data sci moleecular bio
FastCashCoding: lipds
almonte550: Did we failed the other exam?
cleofn: 5head
cleofn: 5Head
l1ght5p33d: ENZYME
mritzing: fat
mikenachos: lipids are fats
Rovelo: fat
ViennaZoe: what are we doing?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @ViennaZoe revieew of highschool curriculum
almonte550: @ViennaZoe learning stuff
l1ght5p33d: enzyme == catalyst == true
MrStereoX: Hey ! @georgehotz have you ever heard about the "black cube" company ?
ar2zee: He doesn't believe in global warming or what, I don't get it? how he will explain all the things that happening right now in Antarctica ?
shaselton: well, hello there
tykabmo: He is going full dowrigHakc dowrigHakc dowrigHakc dowrigHakc mode!
mritzing: better off with a bioinformatics course?
GoBerserk: @ar2zee he said he understands its real, he just doesn't want it shoved in his face
C0deCane: @tykabmo LUL dowrigHakc yup
logi6000: @ar2zee no he just doesn't want it shoved down his throat every second
ViennaZoe: ok @ayyyy420lmao
genieyou1: Hi bro love you
ackxhpaez: I’m all for global warming. I hate cold weather
AresRai: @ar2zee learn to phrase it better than "things happenings in antartica" if you want people to take u seriously
amo77777: @ackxhpaez same
1monkjuice: intro to algos nostalgia in this web :)
tykabmo: @C0deCane oh hello again code, how are you doing?
Landowner555: speaking of MIT open courseware, Eric Lander has great lectures on youtube
logi6000: @aresrai whatever man we got the idea
l1ght5p33d: open book / notes / group test or no......
C0deCane: pretty good man, hbu? stayin healthy? @tykabmo
ar2zee: @AresRai ok
mik12f4: can you reverse engineer what makes COVID19 different concerning asymptomatic spreading?
alicyka: I'm having a fucking dance party in the arctic, explain that warming truthers w
guinness84: lol
Landowner555: @mik12f4 litreally no one knows that
tykabmo: @C0deCane yeah staying away from Covid-19 and doing more programming lol.
Shelledlizard4: hey
Ayyyy420Lmao: @Landowner555 God does Kappa Kappa Kappa
Landowner555: Keepo
mimiron010: did he pee in like 5 seconds
painpainmorepain: r u pooping
Digital_donger: wash hands DansGame
kthxbai32: TableHere
mikenachos: i think its like any virus, the body doesnt respond to the virulent DNA so it has to run through the cycle to eventually build antibodies using light/heavy antibody combinations
ar2zee: @mimiron010 nohe pooped
Ayyyy420Lmao: chicken tendies better
eric_hansen: You didn't wash your hands for 20 seconds @georgehotz
antonypereira88: TheIlluminati
painpainmorepain: u dick will catch corona
phrixus_bro: i like fish
alicyka: fish fillet is the best food in the world
happypuppppy: not rationing his food :z
C0deCane: Antarctica might be pretty nice in our future
shaselton: what do I think of fish...i think, "meh"
dr_set: that you apartment is going to stink
Digital_donger: dead fish PogChamp
antonypereira88: LUL
kthxbai32: 20second dinner
painpainmorepain: u need cap to go to the other part
eric_hansen: that single cube of ice on the ground bothers me so much
wholesome_pepe: i'm just happy python has so many toolkits for scientists. makes life so much easier
logi6000: @painpainmorepain yo that sound like a fucking death sentence
cankunwang: Same my dinner
alicyka: I don't even know what kind of fish it is, it's jsut delicious. Make like 8 of those bitches dude! Shit rocks my socks!!!
Landowner555: ur kitchen is fkn huge dude
mutrx: guys you realise the washing ur hands and not touching your face meme applies to when youre OUTSIDE
guinness84: thats his bedroom
Ayyyy420Lmao: it's hake 90% of the time
C0deCane: just sitting here down on the beaches of Antarctica drinkin some Corona - 2075
Landowner555: @mutrx hey this isnt a biology stream 4Head
Digital_donger: his kitchen has a bed PogChamp
kthxbai32: Living room
eric_hansen: @Landowner555 that's the size of his entire house
Rovelo: NotLikeThis living on frozen food
aj37z: !uptime
mikenachos: look into light/heavy chains
logi6000: George what's up with that bed in your kitchen
Landowner555: @eric_hansen cbrahBuddy cbrahThrust
alicyka: covid doesn't apply to people that watch anime and program for weeks between trips outside
un3okapi: @mutrx memes are memes inside or outside
Zipzipcekirge: is folding at home a scam
painpainmorepain: @logi6000 absolutely
mritzing: jin xiong is good fundamentals
cankunwang: Mol bio of cells https://send.firefox.com/download/a467a695c0c20f93/#yqKaOlQvHeZiUwmcdXhq7Q
axlebear: folding laundry at home
dendyliu: a
wizardwatch1: https://openstax.org/details/books/biology
MichaelA1337: hey
C0deCane: I just fly my drone into town to pick up groceries 2025 America after corona
painpainmorepain: find the cure man, i just tested positive
eric_hansen: @georgehotz go look at the field of synthetic biology
nomad119: @georgehotz https://www.biostarhandbook.com/
MichaelA1337: what are you working on rn?
murkythunder: @painpainmorepain really? and its too late for you its a vaccine not a cure
AresRai: @MichaelA1337 biology 101
wizardwatch1: https://openstax.org/details/books/biology It is free and great
C0deCane: better yet groceries just come to you via drone LUL
Sniky83: have you watched this ? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gG7uCskUOrA
eric_hansen: @georgehotz go look at the field of synthetic biology
logi6000: @painpainmorepain that's a whole tragidy
daopportunist: Focus George.
roystang: we're advanced biology now
logi6000: @georgehotz painpainmorepain just got corona we need a cure now
guinness84: i live there pog
adibaby04: YOOO GEORGE WUZ POPPIN REMEMBER ME?
AresRai: yay intern streams
C0deCane: LUL try and hire a couple of them
painpainmorepain: @logi6000 thank u
Landowner555: LMAO
0xbeeff00d: george create new corona latest v1.1
slimpimp007: let me drive the boat
Ayyyy420Lmao: google tailored sugestions
mritzing: nice targetted ad there
l1ght5p33d: is this.. docker for cells?
montrealchrislee: what are you studying?
aj37z: did you release the alpha version of vaccine yet
Ayyyy420Lmao: what are you trying with that paper?
el_pirulote: even gods have limits
davedavidsonfromdavis: e coli would look good on my wall
localcanofdutchgold: lul
AresRai: @georgehotz put it in the stream title LUL
citsejam12: people just don't understand EXPLORING ;-)
Ghost_001: Kappa
mikenachos: are you interested in drug manufacturing/antibody production?
painpainmorepain: @murkythunder cure vaccine like i care, just give me something that will end it, let it be George pee
Natschz: have to get clean before the teest right?
ron1n541: is open courseware legit? only cruised them, never finished one.
axlebear: For kratom too?
Plurmorant: @ron1n541 the best
firmstool: MOAR LAYERS
cankunwang: basically most about sequence alignment stuff
firmstool: herp derp
Ghost_001: mootif LUL
mikenachos: alpha and beta sheets
cankunwang: set of conserved regulatory elements
logi6000: one of your viewers has corona. it's painpainmorepain
Ghost_001: monkaS
l1ght5p33d: a legit scam maybe xDDDD
entangledbeing: Nice prof pic
AbsydeAuberon: Jebaited
ticklepusss: are you a polymath?
Landowner555: lmao
guinness84: im a pussymouth
localcanofdutchgold: ^
KillerBee20: are Andrew Ng's ML courses the best way to start out?
roystang: woah future
ron1n541: INVEST IN VIROLOGY FUTURES
entangledbeing: Anyone have comma ones in the chat?
Landowner555: future virology, ironic
Zipzipcekirge: aka world war 3
ron1n541: You heard it here
boozer_man: javascript
nitrixen: George seems like the kind of guy that'd be into Lisp.
wholesome_pepe: please dont make a bio-weapon Kappa
l1ght5p33d: wtf does covalent mean here
AresRai: actually future virology is still 10 years behind LUL
pz3300: What’s happenin George?
l1ght5p33d: ohhh covalent bonds... not math then ok
mritzing: within the sim
cankunwang: lol those bags still there
pavankumarp: time and dimension i believe
mikenachos: histones and the likes
logi6000: "those little shits" George hotz Jr 2020
atzehji: i don't have a textbook. but in bioiinformatics next semester i will study: basic molecular biology NGS technology TGS technology
l1ght5p33d: covalent ionic brings back poorly defined memories
GoBerserk: bats consume bugs
cankunwang: joker: kill the bats
Landowner555: bats r actually really important
davedavidsonfromdavis: how about people stop eating bats
localcanofdutchgold: they inspired the creation of batman
Appz_x: FBI OPEN UP
Ayyyy420Lmao: bats r cute
pz3300: No bat soup
el_pirulote: We kill the Batman
Usisuvach0: bats r cute lol
ron1n541: Their poop is real important to cave ecosystems
thugis123: I wish you the best of luck with that, batman wont be a easy fight
davedavidsonfromdavis: bats fried in delicious gutter oil
Usisuvach0: ugly as fuck creatures
axlebear: How about we just don’t eat bats
localcanofdutchgold: megabats are not cute
Jehhred: While we're at it, kill anything that shows any possibility of spreading disease
davedavidsonfromdavis: if you have never googled gutter oil.... have fun
Ayyyy420Lmao: we dont have megabats here just regular
dr_set: bats eat a shit ton of insects, but because we are already killing all the insects, we are on the way of starving all the bats
mutrx: 15 sources say... @georgehotz
pz3300: Fox bats aren’t cute
l1ght5p33d: covariant and contravariant much better defined... poor organic chemists
bttmndl: biology is just physics
AbsydeAuberon: bats are cute
happypuppppy: but those other articles they link to are news to whats the problem Kappa
WooWhey: Kill all the CNN's!
Usisuvach0: lol
Gustavevi: lmao
cankunwang: fake news~!
PiroFloydian: all science is just math if you abstract it enough @georgehotz
pz3300: CNN cites CNN
Ayyyy420Lmao: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Common_noctule#/media/File:Nyctalus_noctula.jpg dont say its not cute
WooWhey: Anderson Cooper is the Anti-Christ.
Usisuvach0: fucking rat @Ayyyy420Lmao
nitrixen: Essentially, their immune system prevents them from dying from these deadly diseases, so they become great hosts.
mr_stochastic: He's back! Awesome :D
Usisuvach0: you call that cute
mutrx: birds > bats
daopportunist: focus George
vruthlessv: how is that cute
Jehhred: For every one bat, kill a bird
Usisuvach0: he is trolling
Natschz: but if you kill the mother bat then all other bats die or get cured or does this only apply to vampires?
l1ght5p33d: they are pretty cute if u hear them chirp n stuff
gorgoleon89: wow, hots streaming 2 days in a row?
C0deCane: Theres a lot of scammers/trolls that take the formats of our media companies and post fake news online and people actually think its those media companies lol
AresRai: kill every host that has too strong of immune system compared to us :)
Usisuvach0: fucking bats carry around 300 viruses similar to this
happypuppppy: whats going to happen to batman if we do this BibleThump
l1ght5p33d: happy little bats
logi6000: @gorgoleon89 5 actually
goldensoap_: George Focus we need a cure and u are our last hope
mr_stochastic: @georgehotz You do most of this fun programming in the cloud or just on your laptop?
omniilista: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TfG_L49Hv-s come on man, leave the bats alone
Jehhred: @gorgoleon89 This is day 5
foti_kasparov: Would you rather eat a cooked bat or get into politics?
Ayyyy420Lmao: and cats give u toxoplasmosis and make u retarded
gorgoleon89: fug, missed the other 3 :D
cankunwang: lol
Landowner555: LMFAO
Landowner555: THAT WAS GORGE LIKE 2 MINS AGO
Landowner555: george*
logi6000: got it so we just need to nuke china
davedavidsonfromdavis: fry your bat in https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zrv78nG9R04
localcanofdutchgold: imagine strolling and then you see this fool https://i.pinimg.com/originals/ff/3f/71/ff3f71492d7b360b06a5ebe1280aa100.jpg
boriskurikhin: finally i caught a geohot livestream
C0deCane: bats kill all the mosquitoes, how about make china regulate what the hell their citizens are selling and eating
Jehhred: What if we deep fry all the bats?!
davedavidsonfromdavis: deep fry in https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zrv78nG9R04
benchai18: No need to panic guys. I’m back
vruthlessv: what
Krakken_TM: yo george
Usisuvach0: china are disgusting
Usisuvach0: they eat dogs cats
gorgoleon89: my nose is runny, how fuged am i? @georgehotz
Usisuvach0: everything that should not be eaten
logi6000: got it just need to nuke china. I'll go get the codes now. ( FBI agent I'm joking don't worry. I couldn't get the codes if I wanted to anyways)
SpaceGhost8: i missed the ending last night, are we building a lab?
benchai18: @usisuvach0 Mongolian delicacy is rats, btw
Krakken_TM: i found an epic conspiracy theory thats not so crazy and backed up by very logical stuff. u want me to send u the link from youtube so u can watch later if u into these things? :D
Usisuvach0: bullshit
benchai18: Fucking gross
Usisuvach0: eating rats
benchai18: Swear
C0deCane: @Usisuvach0 thats a little far for me but seriously they just need to regulate some things. im fine with cultural beliefs but for fuck sake
mik12f4: can twitch alert people when channels are streaming?
Usisuvach0: disgusting as fuck
thecoder15: yo turn your volume up @georgehotz
thrashtazs: @georgehotz did you end up buying a bunch of lab gear last night
dzid26: is our body temperature related to tempreture at which viruses die?
brownyyyylocks: im a vegetarian
atzehji: i don't have a textbook. but in bioiinformatics next semester i will study: basic molecular biology; NGS technology TGS technology; idk if it helps
AresRai: :o
Landowner555: LOl i found that out like a few days ago too
l1ght5p33d: v-diff corona.alpha corona.beta
Natschz: don't get attached to it!
Jehhred: deep fry the bats
AbsydeAuberon: cute coronavirus absydeUWU
Appz_x: you mean it doesnt come from beer?
Time4Boom: corona = crown (spanish)
cellophane11578: the cutest viruses get all the attention
dog_runner09: uma delicia
benchai18: @usisuvach0 For real. A close business associate of mine is like a filthy wealthy Mongolian, and this bitch starts showing me what we’ll do in Mongolia if I come visit. Fucking rat snacks
5_betbluff: you see Fauchi said covid might be seasonal?
Ayyyy420Lmao: sopa do pangolin
dingus74: Dont eat bats
Gamer_nohope: @dog_runner09 lol
cellophane11578: can bats eat us?
Gamer_nohope: esses BRs
mr_stochastic: @cellophane11578 Yes, they're called vampires
C0deCane: I guess thats what you have to do when you have a population that large ?????
ron1n541: @cellophane11578 not if we eat them first
cellophane11578: lol
l1ght5p33d: ACE 2 !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
OlympusDev: Hey
Appz_x: i was reading that certain blood types make you more susceptible to corona
knilecrack: hey man
Zipzipcekirge: if we bite bats do they get a virus?
logi6000: I only know about the cannibinoid receptor
C0deCane: we would actually be in shape in america if they ate cows like we do LUL
vruthlessv: so bats are immune to all corona viruses?
benchai18: According to some scholar Chinese guy (critical of his own government) claims that it’s the super rich elite that eat the disgusting shit
t00big2fl4il: Yo what up? Mac n cheese and a sick Stream!
dingus74: Is eating bats Keto
ron1n541: not pangolins?
architectzs: yo
knilecrack: so feel free to eat bats
mritzing: https://www.rcsb.org/news?year=2020&article=5e74d55d2d410731e9944f52 here's good images of corona
benchai18: @dingus74 Nah. Paleo tho
C0deCane: flying rats dude
ron1n541: i thought the interm carrier was the pangolin
bufferovrflw: @vruthlessv If they were immune, bat coronavirus would die, sicne it can
l1ght5p33d: called what
bufferovrflw: *can't propagate
knilecrack: on steroids
eric_hansen: @georgehotz take a look at this paper titled "Coronavirus Genomics and Bioinformatics Analysis": https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3185738/
roystang: from camels
vruthlessv: but they are carriers
architectzs: what’s a good windows manager for windows?
echobrother: can you do hacking tutorials
aj37z: 100x lev
Jehhred: Bats are carrier pigeons for corona virus
architectzs: ^^
knilecrack: South Korea had incident
vruthlessv: its like mosquitoes
logi6000: @echobrother this is hacking
l1ght5p33d: get your vaccinations kidssss
SpaceGhost8: great, another pandemic to look forward to
wholesome_pepe: can we hack the corona to a therapeutic RNA sequence instead of a pathogenic one via crispr?
HexaField: @echobrother hacking tutorial is an oxymoron. teach yourself.
foti_kasparov: But is it possible to try the vaccine on bats rather than people?
Gamer_nohope: "Approximately 35% of patients with MERS have died"
mr_stochastic: @architectzs Default, you're not gonna get much more on windows
benchai18: I wonder if there’s a MERS vac
architectzs: idk how to use default lmao
benchai18: Vax
scarbromangler: @benchai18 i don't think there is
benchai18: Fuck
scarbromangler: funding dried up a few months after sars lol
DrakenZA: it seems viruses have a limited set of resources and they can be super deadly, but not spread well, or spread well and just be super deadly
SolarBerry: this is the equivalent of plague before antibiotics
informalgarlic: George is great at everything except econ
mr_stochastic: @architectzs Ha, start with alt-tab :D
tsAllySparkles: fung & liu? more like lung and flu
architectzs: ik that lmao
benchai18: @solarberry What is? Covid?!
echobrother: @hexafield: no its not
amedhussaini: amedhussaini subscribed with Twitch Prime.
guinness84: heres this big fucking word that no one knows but ima use it so. i get published
ron1n541: or intel circa 2019 ayyyyyy
HexaField: @informalgarlic the first law of economics is that everyone is terrible at economics
benchai18: @solarberry Corona for sure isn’t like plague. Black Death took out I think 25% of Europe
echobrother: @HexaField: how is this hacking
knilecrack: all bad things happen in europe :)
logi6000: yeah it's where the lysosomes get their driving license. the dmv
benchai18: I don’t mean fatality rate, I mean 25% of ALL Europe does
benchai18: Died*
logi6000: rough and smooth er
knilecrack: yeah
guinness84: just put in an order for $1200 worth of weed
ron1n541: ER is bio101 dude
Mint2bSpiced: Here is another book recommendation if you want more stats stuff: Statistics and Data Analysis for Microarrays Using R and Bioconductor, Second Edition (Chapman & Hall/CRC Mathematical and Computational Biology)
bufferovrflw: I really like the vibe to this stream
guinness84: :bless:
wholesome_pepe: ACE2 could be a good target to deliver drugs to lungs or GI tract if we can exploit it with engineering
HexaField: @echobrother you are incoherent
AntiVax_SoccerMom: plague is still around
logi6000: rough er has ribosomes over it
Usisuvach0: black death=bacteria
SpaceGhost8: says bacteria right there
Usisuvach0: yersinia pestis
benchai18: Bacteria
alicyka: we should know because it showed up at Comicon 3 years ago
360Plato: ? its in the first line
Ayyyy420Lmao: it say amoeba right there
AresRai: Bacteria were so tough
aMANT3: damni thought the beep was for me
spockshocks: black death is basically SARS
logi6000: George do you want a basic bio quizlet
Landowner555: @aMANT3 it sounds very realistic
echobrother: @HexaField You don't know the definition of incoherent
brownyyyylocks: awful diet
benchai18: Bacteria not virus. Bubonic plague was the most known form. Yersinia pestis is right
Landowner555: arent all bacteria prokaryotes?
foti_kasparov: prognosis of deaths is much better cbrahDavid cbrahDavid
pz3300: Pro
Ayyyy420Lmao: @Landowner555 not in this stream
benchai18: BLACK DEATH was the name of the outbreak
Zipzipcekirge: china again
SpaceGhost8: also in China LUL
wholesome_pepe: @Landowner555 some bacterium dont have a nucleus
echobrother: @HexaField how can you teach your self hacking?
benchai18: Consumption was NUTS. Tuberculosis. White plague
Landowner555: @wholesome_pepe exactly, tjats a prokaryote
logi6000: George do you want a basic bio quizlet
AresRai: no anti biotics, bacteria had rent free
pz3300: Poor nutrition
chucknorrisbeard12: black plague 200 million?
Ozonemaster: they eat with hands in the floor in india
Bloodswordz88: HahaThisisfine
SpaceGhost8: medicine wasn't even a thing back then
alicyka: What do you call 20 million dead Chinese people? a Leap year
Ozonemaster: its amazing that it is not happening atm
knilecrack: how much Spanish flue killed people?
Appz_x: spanish flu 50 mill
brownyyyylocks: @ozonemaster No, they don't.
knilecrack: damn
1monkjuice: poverty 500m
knilecrack: that's like most deadliest isn't it?
shissle: spanish flu -120M died
cellophane11578: rip
vruthlessv: It's hilarious coz if you remember there were loads of memes at the start of 2020 about there being "plagues" every 100 years on 1820, 1920 and 2020
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz How did they "beat" the black plague? Or did just enough people die for it to not spread anymore?
OlympusDev: I have way too many channel points
benchai18: Here’s a fucking thought. What happens if bubonic plague mutates. It’s gonna rape all of us to death
echobrother: How can you teach yourself Hacking
benchai18: @bufferovrflw Quarantine. That was the start.
mrhdr: Write something special below and give it some glitz in chat!
see_you198: H y
SpaceGhost8: -380 :)
Ayyyy420Lmao: shiny mesage
OlympusDev: Something Special
mr_stochastic: @echobrother Just start programming on some project you're interested in. Learn as you go
knilecrack: @benchai18 no. It does not have where to mutate
wholesome_pepe: a lot of therapies are focused on delivering drugs to the cytoplasm cuz getting into the nucleus is hard
bufferovrflw: @benchai18 How long did it lasT?
benchai18: @bufferovrflw Then, anti biotics.
JesseSkinner: hows the research going?
goldensoap_: geohot how can to learn myself hacking
alicyka: Highlightest messages are blackface for twitch
l1ght5p33d: This is the 1337est stream on earth
knilecrack: @benchai18 if it didn't foind something else to live in
OlympusDev: Something Special!
eric_hansen: looks like a buffer overflow attack LOL
benchai18: @knilecrack But what about in rats??
logi6000: @goldensoap_ first learn English
echobrother: @mr_stochastic But programming is different then hacking
masee14: So what are we doing here?
knilecrack: @benchai18 let's hope they die fast, and we don't eat them
goldensoap_: @logi6000 (
benchai18: @knilecrack Amen, but it came to us from rat fleas. Not eating rats
benchai18: New York could be fucked
mr_stochastic: @echobrother Depends what you mean by "hack", but either way programming is involved :d
ron1n541: oh shit nature is using ASLR
prostidude221: @echobrother ???
alicyka: new york fucked = fine by me
echobrother: @masee14 We are hacking the coronavirus
knilecrack: @benchai18 well that can be tricky
brittonx2: Cheer100
Usisuvach0: https://www.ovulation-calculators.com/coronavirus/
pwnbutt: @georgehotz what is this that your coding? :)
Usisuvach0: are china hiding
Usisuvach0: no new cases there at all
knilecrack: @benchai18 but if organisms die fast that are infected by the virus, then it' hard that is going to mutate. That is why corona is serious
d3estruction: !commands
0xatul: China numba WAN
NullJupiter: hey there
m113v: corona is not apple, u cant hack it Kappa
Ayyyy420Lmao: compress your genome with frameshifting
NullJupiter: wtf are you doing?
Usisuvach0: usa=10k new cases
gill_bates_macrosoft: wassup boys
knilecrack: ola
knilecrack: gill bates :D
davedavidsonfromdavis: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zrv78nG9R04
masee14: What does "hacking" the coronavirus mean?
logi6000: @knilecrack yeah the CEO of macrosoft. you don't know him. the only CEO with down syndrome
pz3300: Make a vaccine before bill gates does george. Or were all fucked!
starone5: can someone explain me what he's working on, or is there a link or something I can read about it?
C0deCane: apparently there are seven known coronaviruses that can affect people
SpaceGhost8: I thought Elon was going to save us
Ne0Zer0: it means pretending to reverse it Kappa
Ayyyy420Lmao: the underscore means the end of a codon
Ayyyy420Lmao: the underscore means the end of a codon.
benchai18: @bufferovrflw It wasn’t one event. It recurred until last century. But the HORRENDOUS outbreaks were in the 1300’s I think. And BTW, the death toll was 30-60% of Europe
C0deCane: Elon's down in his private tunnel just chillin with all the toilet paper
l1ght5p33d: gaining all knowledge of the system allows better hacks
bigduddas: HACKERMANS he cracking this
benchai18: @bufferovrflw outbreaks kept occurring. Europe, and also the Middle East via traders I think
SpaceGhost8: Tesla shifting all production to toilet paper PogChamp
Digital_donger: PogChamp
Bloodswordz88: :O
NullJupiter: what are you doing @georgehotz ?
Bloodswordz88: HahaSnowhal
pwnbutt: can someone tell me what he is doing?
foti_kasparov: the vaccine
NullJupiter: lol
AntiVax_SoccerMom: pwnbutt 99% of use dont know either
Ne0Zer0: hes doing his homework
pz3300: If you touch your face again george you will surely get corona
Appz_x: reverse engineering covid 19
Digital_donger: @pwnbutt studying the virus
ankitc: fitness twitch is a thing
logi6000: @pz3300 he's in quarantine
spockshocks: hes getting investors right now, it all looks really smart :)
C0deCane: new drinking game while under lockdown, everytime you hear the word corona take a shot LUL hahahaha
nitrixen: I followed along, but I've never touched python :(
foti_kasparov: But George said to tell that he's doing the vaccine if anybody asks
NullJupiter: he is learning from wikipedia lol
parviz_gc: hi
t00big2fl4il: frameshift = offset?
AntiVax_SoccerMom: nothing wrong with wikipedia
pz3300: But it will get in through under the doors
echobrother: what language is he coding in?
Digital_donger: @nitrixen just learn it 4Head
mashafique: @echobrother python
logi6000: @nitrixen it's fairly simple. you can prob get fairly good in a week with sentdex tutorials
Appz_x: python
cellophane11578: python is very readable and easy to get into
echobrother: @Appz_x It does not look like python to me
C0deCane: @AntiVax_SoccerMom except over 3 million articles are written by one person LUL
foti_kasparov: it is python
mr_stochastic: @echobrother It's certainly python
NullJupiter: it is just in the jupyter gui
Digital_donger: he's using a jupyter notebook
mr_stochastic: @NullJupiter That's the IDE
MurdocLIVE: Could you give a quick summary of your progress so far? I haven't had a chance to watch all the previous vods yet @georgehotz
logi6000: I can't stand jupiter
echobrother: @mr_stochastic What IDE is he using
shekshas369: @MurdocLIVE same same
logi6000: what's the point of jupiter
mr_stochastic: @logi6000 Cuz doesn't support vim? :(
C0deCane: @MurdocLIVE he said he will have this thing cracked in 12 weeks, well now 11
mashafique: @echobrother jupyter notebooks
mr_stochastic: @echobrother Jupyter Notebook
logi6000: @mr_stochastic I mean that too
C0deCane: Kappa
GFWL: there is good emacs implementation for jupyter :)
mr_stochastic: @GFWL How's that pinky doing lol
pz3300: @logi6000 I was gunna take cs50 on Edx to get started. Is that course worth taking?
MurdocLIVE: @C0deCane Ah thank you! Is there something he learned/discovered that led him to say that?
pwnbutt: Is java handier than python? Aiming to study 2 year program of java
Penguino138: Come on George move them groceries
GFWL: @mr_stochastic evil mode man
NullJupiter: jupyter is nice if you want to test something out
logi6000: @pz3300 huh
yungdeli_: what you eating?
mr_stochastic: @GFWL True dat. Spacemacs user?
nitrixen: Is it me or is the entire DNA field some programming in disguise? The code of life.
logi6000: edx?
jmv_chin: welcome back; how are you enjoying stream life
Mirw_: He's porting covid19 to osx
pz3300: Online computer courses.
Jehhred: Those groceries will stay there for the entire lockdown period
shekshas369: @nitrixen simulation theory i see what you did there
whycopper: lmfao
syns0r: !claim
dingus74: jackoo1Weird_SG
yungdeli_: isn't there things in there that need refrigeration?
GFWL: @mr_stochastic I never tried spacemacs, only have tried emacs gui. I thought doom emacs look interesting
Battlestein: Battlestein subscribed with Twitch Prime.
knilecrack: i didn't understand a word you said
foti_kasparov: SCAAAAMM TRAAAINNNN
logi6000: how about level 5 and we smoke weed
bufferovrflw: I like the groceries where they are rn tho
pz3300: Computer science. I’m a noob
guy_ross: guy_ross is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 13 in the channel!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to Emanuell45!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to publishcoffee!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to ICAntF331MyFAce!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to cactusvacuum!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to DecayingSkullz!
entangledbeing: What’s level 3 lol
AntiVax_SoccerMom: SCAM TRAIN? PogChamp
Digital_donger: PogChamp grocery relocation goal
dingus74: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp TriHard
peter35_: PogChamp
yungdeli_: SCAM TRAINNNNNN
Ayyyy420Lmao: stolen credit cards gang PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
cactusvacuum: damn thanks @guy_ross :D
logi6000: ooooo gifters
shekshas369: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood Kreygasm Kreygasm
knilecrack: @AntiVax_SoccerMom rofl @ your name ahahahaha
dingus74: scammed LOL
AresRai: PogChamp scam train choo chooo gift me
mutrx: dodged
foti_kasparov: Need 3 100 bits cheers
syns0r: LET'S GET HYYyPPPPEEEDDDD
mrhdr: guy_ross dodged :(
whycopper: choo choo
gordinhodaora: lol
guy_ross: hype!
theonlymonkas: we want gaming
whycopper: let em rot xD
foti_kasparov: GO SCAAAAM TRAAAIN
logi6000: level 5 and we smoke weed
AbsydeAuberon: PogChamp100
entangledbeing: Can someone explain level 3 pls
MurdocLIVE: Could you give a quick summary of your progress so far? I haven't had a chance to watch all the previous vods yet @georgehotz
mr_stochastic: @georgehotz What is level 3?
pwnbutt: @georgehotz whats handier to learn, java or python? or is there no big difference in the big picture
cellophane11578: Make another goal to set a washing hands record of 20sec
AresRai: @MurdocLIVE so hes earning biology 101 so far
dingus74: MercyWing1 TriHard MercyWing2
brownyyyylocks: twitchies revolt!!!
mashafique: whatcha eating there Geo
devm0d: Fish in its natural form
knilecrack: did you wash your hands bro? before eathing that
knilecrack: eating*
xmalware60: enjoy your meal
theonlymonkas: are you trying to scamm us?
devm0d: Scamsticks
logi6000: level 5 and we smoke weed
entangledbeing: Hearing Geo eat ASMR
ankitc: how big is your monitor
Jehhred: You live in La and aren't eating kale chips, what gives?!?!
Usisuvach0: onion rings?
Ayyyy420Lmao: tamoxifen
mr_stochastic: @Usisuvach0 Calamari
sidthescikid: monkaS
Ayyyy420Lmao: and theres aromatase inhibitors
Ayyyy420Lmao: why?
Slippery3: what are you up to @georgehotz ?
ymelnyk: ymelnyk subscribed with Twitch Prime.
logi6000: level 5 and we smoke weed
Usisuvach0: oh ok @mr_stochastic
nitrixen: @georgehotz Is it just me or the entire DNA field resembles a whole lot what we do in programming? But chemically.
entangledbeing: Start an ASMR channel eating your satsumas 😂
11plus4thinking: what are you eating :)
Ayyyy420Lmao: fishdicks
mortalal: @georgehotz what we programming today?
11plus4thinking: describe taste :)
hootdaflute: have you heard of Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease, 100% fatal
yungdeli_: @mortalal no programming
whycopper: do you own a pornub account
whycopper: lmfaoo
hordead: LoL
Andremm2: still scary
4zimut: it's fine
guinness84: knowledge calms the soul Kappa
theonlymonkas: where is the tea?
knilecrack: rofl
eric_hansen: go take a look at virusite.org it's a website extracted from NCBI sequence databases and has features such as sequence searching
nitrixen: @whycopper I've worked at Pornhub, lol.
Ayyyy420Lmao: can jet fuel melt steel beams?
NullJupiter: It's scary for economy @georgehotz
yungdeli_: going through history hm.............
hordead: You skim through the papers... you don't even read them
whycopper: @nitrixen how was it? yall get discounts?
mutrx: @nitrixen is nothing NSFW then?
informalgarlic: Do you want coronavirus? I can get you coronavirus? @georgehotz
entangledbeing: Can u make a truths list and share it
eric_hansen: @georgehotz go take a look at virusite.org it's a website extracted from NCBI sequence databases and has features such as sequence searching
foti_kasparov: What's going on that new shit virus that started in China?
Jehhred: If anything I'm now more scared of SARS
xxblueshift: @georgehotz love from the UK
nitrixen: @whycopper We had access to the database, so yeah, of course we do :P
informalgarlic: More
11plus4thinking: if only 5% gets corona virus and the deathrate is 4% 16 mil will die
mutrx: look at SAMPL6 competition @georgehotz
Gamer_nohope: "doing corona virus marathon any %"
sidthescikid: 150k !
whycopper: @nitrixen dam son did you get to fuk
whycopper: lmfaooo jk
HellxNebula: what you would say to a beginner who wants get into coding , what language should be his first and how to get better @georgehotz
jermss: https://pubpeer.com/publications/B4044A446F35DF81789F6F20F8E0EE# Hydroxychloroquine and Azithromycin as a treatment of COVID-19: preliminary results of an open-label non-randomized clinical trial
Ayyyy420Lmao: good times
pagepuga: these deaths could overlap too because sick people die mostly
hordead: @georgehotz When is everything going back to normal?
Ayyyy420Lmao: i remember that time we had a bull market after the death plague
Digital_donger: but the second wave NotLikeThis
thecoder15: lol
zennydmt: have u been to india
Ayyyy420Lmao: black plague
Appz_x: what if it mutates MonkaS
meta_man: Yeah, going to be some overlap with some people who would have died this year anyway
hordead: @Digital_donger second wave ..??
theonlymonkas: how many new corona cases?
guinness84: 1m people is almost two times the population of wyoming
Bloodswordz88: should I start eating ass again Geo?
Usisuvach0: @theonlymonkas here
Landowner555: ok thats it im leavin the house
Usisuvach0: https://www.ovulation-calculators.com/coronavirus/
t00big2fl4il: Teamwork makes the stream work
Landowner555: BREAK THE QUARANTINE
HexaField: it's not the deaths that i'm scared of, it's the fact that we are so much more globalised and our global economy is so much more fragile than 100 years ago
yungdeli_: do you talk like this around your house when no one is watching?
11plus4thinking: more than a million will die from coronavirus
AresRai: the expert that went on joe rogan said the same thing, 500k deaths
supersaltpack: I thought they are worrying about the exponential growth of the infection
hordead: @georgehotz Am I going to day a virgin????
thecoder15: @georgehotz they asymptomatic study was proven false their tests were just false positive
cemck: still too much for the 21st century
Zipzipcekirge: not acceptable if i die
11plus4thinking: this is just the beginning
theonlymonkas: @Usisuvach0 thanks
Digital_donger: @hordead historically pandemics sometimes have a second wave
murkythunder: @11plus4thinking no way, wont pass 50k
foti_kasparov: @bloodswordz88 Not George here, but for sure
AzzoDio: other forms of death will also increase if hospital can't treat other causes
Ayyyy420Lmao: @Digital_donger like feminism? that one got to the fourth or fifth
11plus4thinking: @murkythunder think of all the poor countries them come back to me
xiic: is this taking into account deaths due to overwhelmed hospitals from otherwise preventable illnesses?
cachedtv: economy will still be rekt
wholesome_pepe: there are genetic and environmental factors that contribute to how many ACE2 proteins your body expresses
AntiVax_SoccerMom: CurseLit
shekshas369: 4Head
mikey9988: LUL
yungdeli_: LUL
Digital_donger: @Ayyyy420Lmao I guess LUL
Ne0Zer0: LUL
cookienz: LUL
whycopper: rookie
murkythunder: @11plus4thinking poor countries are doing better, the worst countries are countries like UK and US, where people give no fucks and are spoilt
Ayyyy420Lmao: @AntiVax_SoccerMom sick name
Appz_x: SHOULD HAVE FLIPPED IT
NullJupiter: f
AresRai: LUL
brownyyyylocks: wow
cookienz: just hire a chief
AzzoDio: my sister needs emergency surgery this week, luckily her hospital is not a hot zone yet. 2 weeks from nkwt?
1re1: this also doesn't account for hospitals filling up right?
aflow404: Classic LUL
alicyka: People don't think that there's a point where people go from dying of the virus over to dying of poverty because nobody's working
AntiVax_SoccerMom: Ayyyy420Lmao SeemsGood
PotlePS: of just permanent lung damage, estimated 20-30% will have permanently decreased lung capacity (or something of the like)
hordead: @georgehotz is that a studio?
fuzzywuzza: they just approved the $2 trillion stimulus bill
murkythunder: LUL
dog_runner09: mother of ducklings
knilecrack: how is US lockdown functioning ? are you not allowed to go outside ?
theonlymonkas: but what does recovery actually mean? they can get the virus again?
PiroFloydian: TARTER SOUCE
shekshas369: classic George the iq of a god but the cooking skills of a potato
cookienz: LUL
Landowner555: this is the man whos gnna save us from corona folks
echobrother: @HexaField The global economy is not more stable It just was growing so much more
Vackin: i am more worried about the people that will die from causes because hospital are overwhelmed with covid19
wholesome_pepe: LUL
Mint2bSpiced: However, isn't this assuming, when we open our borders back open, we don't see a second wave?
pz3300: I’ll eat them
Jehhred: can make a car drive itself but fail at cooking... priorities
m00chan: is the curse worse than the disease in this case
m00chan: cure rather
NullJupiter: Its scary for economy @georgehotz
Usisuvach0: @georgehotz check this thing they say it might help search on google sumamed
shekshas369: clearly
knilecrack: yeah
AresRai: WutFace
420lokki69: yes
mescal33t: sure
AzzoDio: a very high percentage of doctors will also die. it takes an incredible amount of resources to train a surgical specialist
hordead: fuck no
shekshas369: same
knilecrack: looks like it's human life > $
DecayingSkullz: @guy_ross Thank you.
localcanofdutchgold: not if it's my teeth
shekshas369: we talking about a teeth
Ayyyy420Lmao: nonissue, that's the presprective of a central planner
echobrother: no
granti7: if its a hot chick, yeah
AntiVax_SoccerMom: philosophy stream
sregister: that a lot of teeth
420lokki69: yep
shekshas369: to safe a life
AresRai: nop
Nussinov: i will kill to prevent my tooth from getting pulled without anaesthesia Kappa
Paw_4: I think it's not about the quantity, it's about the suffering and the pain
1monkjuice: depends on who
C0deCane: Honestly all we can do is hope that no serious natural disaster happens in the next few months or something worse like another war starting
jmv_chin: what mouse ya use
happypuppppy: LUL
foti_kasparov: That first rule of alchemy.
alicyka: My philosophy has been that a person's life is worth the net profit of a person's life, so any suffering can be extrapolated to that value. I haven't thought about it much though
FancyDawg_: utilitarianism
shekshas369: @Paw_4 agreed
orami: what if the person dying was about to die anyway
420lokki69: its one tooth per person, not million
aflow404: whiskey will do for me LUL
PiroFloydian: We can stop the trolley and save all these people but if we do the trolley company will lose profits what do we do?
420lokki69: hell yes its worth it
mikey9988: true LUL
mashafique: well people can give a number they think is worth it but which people are actually willing to have their tooth pulled to help save that life?
m00chan: Nobody wants to be blamed
DecayingSkullz: Hello everyone
LocoLuka: true
AresRai: Hopefully it does clean the political field x)
m00chan: SO theyre going overboard
Appz_x: this is a virus created to target old people and get rid of social security
happypuppppy: what's gonna happen to Bernie BibleThump
opus_000: Navy pelosi looked like she had a fever
shekshas369: well if talking about a teeth any teeth is worth a life
anotherkidnamedaustin: whats the bell curve? the media? the std dev?
foti_kasparov: Sacrifice people to save people
Ayyyy420Lmao: no
t00big2fl4il: the politicians are freaking out because it is poking holes in their legitimacy
shekshas369: clearly
420lokki69: yes
mashafique: no
echobrother: yes
shekshas369: yes
AntiVax_SoccerMom: sure
kidjulien: yep
AresRai: no
hordead: YESSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS
Paw_4: yes
eric_hansen: no
plazmacsgo: yep
Ne0Zer0: LUL
shekshas369: YES
mescal33t: yes
Ayyyy420Lmao: nonono
m00chan: yes
localcanofdutchgold: bye @georgehotz
LocoLuka: fuck no
aflow404: foooookkkk noooooo
knilecrack: yes
Foxxy_xx: ofc
Major_Spicy: NO KEKW
hordead: NOOOOOOOOOOO
Appz_x: your dead bud
FancyDawg_: George is a utilitarian CONFIRMED?
stillgeting: NOway
eNoq: no
cachedtv: yea
bufferovrflw: been there done that
shekshas369: 10000%
guinness84: which tooth
purplegreenpanda: no :)
matvey_ryabov: noooo
guy_ross: any day of the week
4zimut: sure, get me an iphone tho
orami: HELL NO yeoswaKEK
Vackin: nope
dr_set: yours, ok
MrStereoX: Do you know the company "Black cube" @georgehotz
brownyyyylocks: nope
Bloodswordz88: the bat is the innocent one here
dzid26: do we really suffer though?
sidthescikid: N OMEGALUL
Goooshlrific: no
dog_runner09: yes
StopitDonk: if you teach me python yes
foti_kasparov: NOOOO
wootawee: the real question - would you rather get a tooth pulled or bet 1 in 500 you die now
hordead: noo
aflow404: VoteNay VoteNay VoteNay VoteNay
nitrixen: Everyone who says no gets banned.
GoodOlSmokey: @georgehotz simple. tie the tooth to the door
firmstool: fuck no LUL
C0deCane: what would you do for me dude?
Digital_donger: I think so :)
pz3300: Ooooh
SoulRedding: I need that tooth man
opus_000: give me 7k
Vackin: with or without
thecoder15: lol
caligula443: NICE KNOWN YA
Bloodswordz88: it hurts tho
pz3300: Tough spot
shekshas369: i mean imagine form a relgious point of view its a freeticked to paradise for pulling a teeth
purplegreenpanda: i only have one left
alicyka: I'm drunk as FUCK so I'll get my toe pulled off for laughs my dude
Jehhred: Nah, you're dead bro
theonlymonkas: LUL yes
knilecrack: ezbut noone gets the point of corona. If transmission rate of corona get over 10 it has a much more chance to mutate to something much worse then a lot more ppl gonna die.
alicyka: OnceI sober up I'll kill you for pocket money
shekshas369: like saving a lift for a teeth
shekshas369: ez done
AresRai: some people would die from the pain LUL
devm0d: I’ve done that a couple times, dentist is very good and saves me time
cellophane11578: which tooth?
pz3300: Will I still get updates on my comma?
AzzoDio: @georgehotz I don't think there's a scenario where you do no mitigation and the economy is just like before. all the chaos and all the deaths and all the hospitals overwhelmed will also hurt the economy
l1ght5p33d: exploits
foti_kasparov: DO IT FOR THE BROOS!
hordead: @pz3300 as long as you run aot update
sidthescikid: I hate those questions because we will never be able to answer them. I guess that why its important to talk about them.
Landowner555: do you believe that herd immunity will actually help prevent the spread? if there is selective pressure for the corona to mutate, dont you think that its more likely that will happen?
GoodOlSmokey: @georgehotz your house could easily be Welcome to the Game 3's environment
kev061895: Hello
peter35_: do you know the philosopher david pearce?
benchai18: @chat Any of you guys use Discord? If there was a fully built out Unofficial george Discord server for these and other related topics... anyone even interested or not really???
t00big2fl4il: is it logrithmic
atzehji: hospital stay 4 days?
mashafique: how does on stop being a lazy piece of shit? asking for a friend Kappa
AzzoDio: @georgehotz also advances in therapeutics and serology. monoclonal antibodies by September.
alicyka: IRC 4 lyfe
kev061895: It's so bad
homestarr: are you doing anymore sequencing analysis?
Landowner555: @mashafique lmfao
Ayyyy420Lmao: just take drugs
Abnico: just do it?
nitrixen: @alicyka o/
Abnico: listen to nike
mineyful: are onion rings literally deep fried onions
l1ght5p33d: whole med / insurance such a scame
MrStereoX: @benchai18 Sure Achi!
localcanofdutchgold: 4Head obviously
l1ght5p33d: scammmm
SlaterUSA: did our man buy the little gene-gadget last night?
shekshas369: agreed
Landowner555: wtf, no way
benchai18: I didn’t ask u Georgie lo. UNOFFICIAL
Ayyyy420Lmao: dna vaccine?
l1ght5p33d: MARKET RATE TREATMENT
AresRai: 10 years in bio field is not really 10 years
SoulRedding: what is "economy"
HexaField: @benchai18 join the portal discord, it's an unofficial discord and the most active IDW discord, over 4000 members
Lizardan: People die sometimes 4Head
pikomane2: is corona virus North Koreas Christmas present they were promising?
11plus4thinking: just make an agi that is way smarter than us 4Head
devm0d: You have to remain curious bro
guinness84: this went from biology to morbid real quick
wholesome_pepe: yes. if we had the infrastructure to do PCRs on everything we would have the insight
hordead: what??? comma ai have seels?
xiic: meh, the world isnt going to forgive China this time.
benchai18: @hexafield Portal? Explain. Not the game, I presume?
NullJupiter: EU economy is breaking down lol @georgehotz
Landowner555: @wholesome_pepe 4Head
Ayyyy420Lmao: mind = blown
AntiVax_SoccerMom: i can feel my brain physically growing
homestarr: !discord
SlaterUSA: trickle-down economy, nbd right
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Here is a timeline for treatment options: https://synbiobeta.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/COVID19_Timeline_SynBioBeta_LeapsByBayer.pdf
1monkjuice: automate production and delivery
wootawee: xiic if by china you mean US then yes
Paw_4: @AntiVax_SoccerMom HAHAHAH
Vackin: economy is a trust in a system
benchai18: @antivax_soccermom Not if you’re an anti vaxxer it’s not
dorkmo: open your dishwasher
sidthescikid: China LUL
Natschz: how many donate blood to safe lifes? it's probably not as painful as getting a tooth pulled?
burzum_: what experiment? i wasnt here
m00chan: progress of humanity is more important?
NullJupiter: Which experiment? @georgehotz
Lizardan: @Vackin wrong
alicyka: I'm young and dumb: Isn't it weird that we've had like 5 "pandemics" in the last 18 years since SARS? I feel like there's been nothing between Spanish Flu and SARS
dingus74: "the experiment" ?
hordead: you need the protein mannn
Landowner555: AWWWW
roystang: i can read lips
pikomane2: F can't hear
knilecrack: bro you didn't mute
Goooshlrific: read lips
localcanofdutchgold: read his lips ez
aj37z: bog
shekshas369: aw men
dorkmo: CORONA TASK FORCE PHONE CALL
granti7: elon musk is calling
shekshas369: come on
purplegreenpanda: no streamer TriHard
eric_hansen: any deaf people good at reading lips?
shekshas369: so close
Ayyyy420Lmao: bruh its not muted
knilecrack: ahahahahahha
1re1: turn around so we cant read lips
METH_HEAD_MIKE: not muted LUL
Lizardan: KappaPride
pikomane2: audio ???
opus_000: lol
cachedtv: lmao
knilecrack: ahahahahaha
knilecrack: NICE ONE
GoodOlSmokey: i can read lips guys here we go
aj37z: bog dump it
bufferovrflw: haha
foti_kasparov: READ HIS LIPS
thecoder15: lol
Joftus112: Rip
burzum_: who knows what the experiment is about?
alicyka: Spend bits on unmuting stream
shekshas369: @1re1 damn you
SlaterUSA: "hello yes? what... google wants to hire me again?"
mescal33t: RPGGhosto
NullJupiter: he is smiling its a girl lmao
shekshas369: exposed
peter35_: we need to hack our appliances and stop them from beeping at us
l1ght5p33d: What does Elon want?
Abnico: bog called
shekshas369: lipreaders
METH_HEAD_MIKE: cocaine dealer monkaS
kev061895: @goodolsmokey 👍🏼
4zimut: he got us
nitrixen: The oven glass door. ENHANCE. ENHANCE.
iIyaRPV: monkaS
Ayyyy420Lmao: @NullJupiter it's a male girl
0R4NG3: monkaS
dorkmo: you left and i dont know how to work the oven
Natschz: can someone see the vibrations on the bag ?
xiic: Parts of the US are very fucked but China could have prevented this if they hadnt lied and suppressed information and destroyed evidence
foti_kasparov: cbrahFor cbrahThe cbrahBoys cbrahFor cbrahThe cbrahBoys
hordead: @METH_HEAD_MIKE yupp loll
lordBzzl: lool, fear of the unmuted muted button
mrhdr: coke dealer has arrived squadR
aMANT3: using the planet leaf vibration to recreate the audio
benchai18: “Hey bitch, send me dem pix hooker”
0R4NG3: 3 letter agency agent joined the chatroom monkaS
ankitc: he did not leave us at OBS
pikomane2: welcome back
hordead: cokeeee dealer?????
l1ght5p33d: Elon wants the comma ai model
burzum_: what's the experiment @georgehotz ?
t00big2fl4il: Yo!
benchai18: “Hey hooker, lemme get sum dem fish sticks”
knilecrack: rofl
pikomane2: lol
AresRai: LUL
mescal33t: beastyLULWW beastyLULWW beastyLULWW
rtcspxstn: alicyka it's largely because it's much easier to transmit things across large distances now
PiroFloydian: LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: funny thing is that it's true
shekshas369: LUL LUL DansGame DansGame
t00big2fl4il: what experiment
wholesome_pepe: LUL
eric_hansen: KEKW
sidthescikid: LUL
foti_kasparov: gmbenjTruthHurts gmbenjTruthHurts gmbenjTruthHurts gmbenjTruthHurts gmbenjTruthHurts gmbenjTruthHurts gmbenjTruthHurts gmbenjTruthHurts
dawaeSHW: LUL LUL LUL
SlaterUSA: ask him if he takes payment in twitch bits
happypuppppy: have you looked up any realistic genetic/molecular animations on youtube?
AresRai: probably true
cellophane11578: pistolCop hey buddy let me see your hands
lordBzzl: synthesize some in jupyter
wholesome_pepe: price gouging dealer monkaS
sidthescikid: "Yeah the markets aren't cooperating bruh"
SoulRedding: price gouging during an emergency is ILLEGAL
aflow404: LUL
eric_hansen: it was a girl wasn't it @georgehotz
echobrother: is he joking
sidthescikid: "No supply"
t00big2fl4il: What level are we at?
peter35_: think of the cokehards FeelsBadMan
benchai18: Got that 8 ball in ur pocket
Landowner555: @foti_kasparov ben finegold fan !
l1ght5p33d: I love it buy BTC
Major_Spicy: @georgehotz its funny, my dealer said the same thing
shekshas369: haha
t00big2fl4il: What level
Lizardan: Bro, I was going to start a $130K job and now they're telling me I have to wait BibleThump
dorkmo: cutting your coke with virus powder
bufferovrflw: This IDIOT won the drug war with this ONE SIMPLE TRICK
SlaterUSA: cocainavirus
solitarynative: Kreygasm
shekshas369: when your coke dealer cares about his farmers
devm0d: @echobrother Of course
wholesome_pepe: i got u on a pico gram for 1k
shekshas369: money well spend
burzum_: the experimeeeeeeent
ankitc: why are you smiling
linkrager: never play f6!
granti7: receving calls from AI girls
aflow404: LUL
echobrother: @devm0d How do you know
NullJupiter: What experiment did you mean? @georgehotz
Landowner555: coronavirus HALTS the war on drugs
microx0ft: you are the best
benchai18: George u joke, but a bunch of junkies are in crazy withdrawals on the street rn
burzum_: we will never know
foti_kasparov: @landowner555 :)
devm0d: Can someone update me on what we’re hacking on today?
Ayyyy420Lmao: 1 paper per hour Kappa not even that really, this pace LUL
snapcs1: we are hacking coronavirus
eric_hansen: coronavirus drops drug overdose rates to 0%
SlaterUSA: @devm0d the planet
shekshas369: @devm0d technically the Virus itself lol
microx0ft: geohot what monitor are you using?
nitrixen: Assert dominance. Make the virus fear you.
homestarr: 2010 kinda old lol
Paw_4: @devm0d he is hacking the fucking pandemic
0R4NG3: DansGame
devm0d: @slaterusa Ahh hack the planet!!
SlaterUSA: precisely
SolarBerry: DansGame
opus_000: hack cicada
benchai18: “Hey bitch, ill give u my strand”
alicyka: I read the lips: "hey georgie whatcha doin <3?" "Trying to figure out how many people I'd kill to get my tooth pulled"
eric_hansen: didn't wash hands DansGame
Major_Spicy: Yellow hands DansGame
WaeHaKe: Cheer100 Cheer100 when we talking politics?
mik12f4: your going to spoil us with all these back to back streams.
mikey9988: DansGame
MrStereoX: @benchai18 are you opening the discord?
eric_hansen: HE TOUCHED HIS LIPS
hordead: Lol that's after you had your hands in your mouth
zennydmt: how many hours of sleep do u get per night
0xatul: why does my meme comments gets auto mod'ed
microx0ft: what monitor areu using
sidthescikid: Util is an optimist's coping tool
Abnico: economy as a social construct
shekshas369: i always wonder about that tho tbh
C0deCane: I heard some boomer today say "back in my day we didn't get this kinda shit, but thats cause we worked out in the fields and had real immune systems" LUL
dzid26: no. it's great purge of the scam companies
devm0d: I sold everything, I’m out. It’s all a scam.
snapcs1: what an idiot lollll @C0deCane
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz https://twitter.com/JustinWolfers/status/1242641219517366278
AzzoDio: @georgehotz If the hospital system collapses, if doctors quit or get infected and the medical system collapses, that's ALSO a terrible economy. Try to model the effect of the economy of a having no hospitals for X months
HexaField: George are you opposed to an unofficial discord server? I have experience running them and if you aren't opposed I'll start one. Done well they can be a great resource and organisational tool, and anecdotally so. Up to you.
alicyka: I feel you, I'm making jokes. 10000 people not making food for a month eventually = 100 people dying because of high food cost
C0deCane: Nobody probably even knew honestly
foti_kasparov: How to prevent it?
shekshas369: well if it hit us back than without the internet you hell as bet can be sure quarantine at home wouldn'T be this effective
devm0d: Twitter
shekshas369: Pornhub saving the world 1 fap at the time
devm0d: Twitter caused this madness
shekshas369: LUL
benchai18: It really does feel like all these outbreaks are recent. SARS, mers, h1n1, Ebola, corona.... all this shit wasn’t happening when I was a fucking kid.
SlaterUSA: @georgehotz did u buy one of those gene gadgets last night?
firmstool: physical symptoms?
benchai18: Oh interesting
C0deCane: dude if you look into psychology just the minimal part of it this whole thing becomes really scary
AzzoDio: We know about it because of a surge of atypical pneumonia in Wuhan, even before it was sequences or tested
MrStereoX: Do you know the company "Black cube" @georgehotz
xiic: you think the affected people wouldnt have recorded such an event in their history?
firmstool: small pox etc. physical symptoms
robinbrinkler: "Antiviral Agents From Fungi: Diversity, Mechanisms and Potential Applications"
Abnico: social distancing will stay after the virus, look into it
hordead: @C0deCane what do you mean?
HexaField: @georgehotz are you opposed to an unofficial discord server? I have experience running them and if you aren't opposed I'll start one. Done well they can be a great resource and organisational tool, and anecdotally so. Up to you.
Ayyyy420Lmao: @Abnico twitch user not affected
l1ght5p33d: Sample bias * Infinity
jasondesante: 90s was pretty dope
shekshas369: the 90s were pretty dope tho
devm0d: I had a pool in the 90s
SlaterUSA: confirmation bias
foti_kasparov: except people
shekshas369: that was my point earlier like by how much do you quantify suffering ?
bufferovrflw: This is taking 90s nostalgia too far
NullJupiter: but population expanded too
faraday_lenz: we need blockbuster again
jasondesante: all games go back to point and click, and yea you're right George I'm just bustin yo balls
Abnico: new york was trash in 90s lmao
1monkjuice: log scale that
knilecrack: 90s were crap
shekshas369: cause people in the 90s lived pretty good
entangledbeing: Nice in some places shitty in others...
alicyka: 90's was dope socially, but today is to the point where the bottom shelf shit is the same as top shelf shit in the 90s
knilecrack: only good music nothign besides that was crap
Ayyyy420Lmao: im autistic i dont do restaurants
C0deCane: @hordead your own thoughts can cripple you and studies show that when you consistently hear one thing you believe it and your mind can actually trick you and your body into becoming sick. That will definitely overrun our health resources with cases of this virus that don't actually test positive
C4TFive: Pager stonks gunna booooom!
AzzoDio: @georgehotz As a thought experiment, pretend there's no mitigation or quarantines possible. How much damage does the economy take from the surge of deaths, medical system. Who is going out to eat in that scenario? Dow still crashes IMO
weedlord666: we used zagat guidebook bro
t00big2fl4il: Bitcoin
memphisFPS: my house was trash humid and cold during 90s
cellophane11578: the 90s were nice because we were young and dumb? xd
optimizely: @georgehotz how do you choose what project to do next?
SlaterUSA: we had these things called maps :D
entangledbeing: Hard to see the reality of the economy sitting from an ivory tower...
weedlord666: paperback yelp
soisoisoi: you'd use maps
aflow404: ASK SOMEONE
m00chan: we dont know how good we have it
Abnico: ussr was the goood old days
benchai18: But why would that stuff disappear?
cankunwang: it only means the stock market is a huge bubble?
axlebear: In the 90s everyone was carefree
Lizardan: @georgehotz do you believe this crisis is going to help Trump get re-elected? I think so
benchai18: Why would phones disappear?
SHAVEYY_: @georgehotz install arch linux for a stream
xiic: payphones are not a function of the economy, they're a function of technological progress. We're not going back to payphones
C0deCane: stress can weaken your immunity as well
HexaField: George are you opposed to an unofficial discord server? I have experience running them and if you aren't opposed I'll start one. Done well they can be a great resource and organisational tool, and anecdotally so. Up to you.
sidthescikid: Wouldn't later generations view the 2020's in that same light tho?
hordead: @C0deCane can you link me to one of these studies?
benchai18: Bro he lives in the ghetto
xiic: The rate of it is
happypuppppy: elon ?
xiic: not the state of it
wholesome_pepe: i wish i were born in the future where everyone else has done all the leg work
opus_000: physics
Ayyyy420Lmao: aliens
masters8: ?? Lots of people living in current day USSR miss those times
benchai18: Лол
cellophane11578: in soviet union we infect the virus Kappa
Reelix: Eh - Look at the ZAR VS the USD over the past 30 years - Some places go up, some go down :p
shekshas369: i mean you guys are talking about an era of Internet vs no internet pretty unfair comparison
zombiedigital: some countries will become out of this as a winner
Abnico: @HexaField all discord servers fail
optimizely: @georgehotz how do you choose what project to do next?
SolarBerry: monkaS
iIyaRPV: monkaS
shekshas369: wouldn'T it make more sense comparing the economy of 2k10 to 2k20 rather than the 90s ?
slim_bhris: dam that honda is loud
HexaField: @Abnico only because they aren't run well
WaeHaKe: dickhead in a maserati?
aj37z: theyre puring putside
Ayyyy420Lmao: ending the apartheid was a mistake
t00big2fl4il: yes but. Jobs and Woz were blueboxing payphones prior to the 90s
snapcs1: damn that guy revving his engine must be so cool
HexaField: wild generalisations there
aj37z: purging
devm0d: Bring back Phone phreaking pay phones!
treestompztv: vrrrrrr
SpaceGhost8: stockTank
granti7: are we reverse engineering the economy? pog
foti_kasparov: @optimizely He just waits for a virus to blow up I guess
HexaField: i know many that work just fine and have for years and years
sidthescikid: Yes because Africa's econ is stable Kappa
nitrixen: @georgehotz Technology can develop because a minority supports the essential needs of the majority.
amedhussaini: you ever try to hack the market? like algorithmic trading, etc?
Abnico: @HexaField i dont know of any good public ones
entangledbeing: The economy may go up but the standard of living you experience is not the case for most people in America...
devm0d: Who’s got a captain crunch whistle?
iIyaRPV: RUB vs USD is so monkaS rn
aj37z: kappa
C0deCane: @hordead its actually a psychological test that was done with advertisements you dealing with symbols and songs and other things like that i don't have a link right with me but im sure i gave you enough info you can google it, or you can just disagree with me idc
eldred57: There are people here who are talking about communism as good old times. All of them were in a privilege position with the party :D
Lizardan: true
l1ght5p33d: Same expense probably as 2010 all R and D
cankunwang: true
aj37z: cost 20 bucks to make i nchina
aflow404: dude after 2008, so much gentrification @georgehotz
Ozonemaster: what is rnd? ...
dvdutch: You figure this shit out yet
sidthescikid: research and development @Ozonemaster
stillgeting: ???
ayushsharma: Rnd is bullshit
knilecrack: yes on credit
cankunwang: I remember iPhone was such a luxury thing in 2010s
peter35_: getting a gf was better in the 90s for average guys FeelsBadMan
Lizardan: Debatable
shekshas369: is that true tho
Abnico: europe has higher standard than us
stillgeting: thats not right
weedlord666: how do you square that with the "decline of the middle class"
Ozonemaster: @sidthescikid aaa ok. its ID in my language
Ozonemaster: thx
sidthescikid: rnd is necessary tho
pz3300: People in us are no better off than in the 70s
benchai18: For sure we do
Lizardan: The first iPhone I could afford was the 4.
HexaField: @Abnico keep looking. they are out there. Eric Weinstein's the portal is highly active and growing. Rebel wisdom is fairly active, there is the science network of around 10 servers that are huge.
Ayyyy420Lmao: europe higher standards than usa LUL
ICAntF331MyFAce: @peter35_ FeelsBadMan
knilecrack: USA lives on credit.
entangledbeing: Yeah your probably right
benchai18: Broke ass kids own iPhones and MacBooks
wholesome_pepe: if we measure by life expectancy then yes. cuz time = money = value
HexaField: Bridges of Meaning is JBP's and it is very active too
sidthescikid: Me too :)
cachedtv: what do you think will happen to tesla since no one will be buying luxury goods?
Abnico: @HexaField i will check them out! thanks
ummyeah1929: i know people in tiny little pueblos in mexico who own the newest iphone LUL
C0deCane: American poverty is fuckin nice compared to Chinese poverty
xiic: Look at the wealth gap over the last 20 years in the US, that's where the decline of the middle class can be seen
mattdougherty22: @Abnico Check out The portal
un3okapi: https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2018/10/01/bottom-percent-are-still-poorer-than-they-were/
axlebear: The happiness index has continued to plummet though
knilecrack: I grew up in the 90's 2 wars in 5 years :) it was very nice
queencitydisco: middle class has shrunk but has lost people in both directions
Abnico: okie
lostindetails: Is wearing face masks underrated?
benchai18: I broke up a broke ass bitch in LA
knilecrack: corona means nothign to me
Ayyyy420Lmao: @axlebear that just proves the unabomber right
echotaco: Happiness is a function of perception, people will get used to whatever happens
m00chan: in musk we trust
heyitsrama: tsla is doing good because holland is getting rid of subsidies soon
entangledbeing: What about increasing wealth inequality? Does trickle down
heyitsrama: they gotta get the cars into the countries
HexaField: @georgehotz are you opposed to an unofficial discord server? I have experience running them and if you aren't opposed I'll start one. Done well they can be a great resource and organisational tool, and anecdotally so. Up to you.
HexaField: tell me to shut up if im spamming
ayushsharma: Is the economy inflating ?
foti_kasparov: @knilecrack Are you from Kosovo?
snoozejunkie: this channel is fire
weedlord666: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Income_inequality_in_the_United_States#2007–2016_reduction
knilecrack: No. I'm from serbia
shekshas369: they are pretty much the same
knilecrack: but I was born in croatia
shekshas369: jokes on you
pz3300: How much a loaf of bread cost
mashafique: I had some pretty good ramen bowls in 2019 LUL
treestompztv: https://clips.twitch.tv/TrustworthyBrightKathyKappaPride this past clip of you LUL
m00chan: not mcdonalds fries
sidthescikid: Mc Donalds turned into a budget salada ngl
m00chan: used to be made with beef tallow
eldred57: Tesla is selling more and more in China and its factory there is up and running. GM will be significantly more fucked
t00big2fl4il: the tech is good that economies allow, but the skills to create and innovate are better and are born from necessity
snapcs1: ?????????????
cankunwang: I saw my own eyes these days, ppl used like 5 credit cards but not able to pay for food at Walmart
m00chan: until saturated fat scare
SpaceGhost8: interior sure, but look at those OG burgers
l1ght5p33d: meh ...
roystang: @georgehotz inside of a mcdonalds != qualty of living
Ayyyy420Lmao: mcdonalds has turned low quality with celulose fillers so they can keep price the same...
hordead: @georgehotz it's just aesthetics
atzehji: what we pay is hours of work at the end. efficientcy of production processes won't go back. i feel like economic problems will be very temporarely
entangledbeing: Do you believe in trickle down economics?
Reelix: 1990 -> US$1 = ZAR2.50 --- 2020 - US$1 = ZAR17.37 - I'd prefer 1990 thanks :p
aj37z: now you got pink chicken nuggets
devm0d: My income went up over time so yeah my meals got better
picklesareok: dont you think thats more of a representation of the company's health more than individual people?
snapcs1: evaluating the economy by mcdonalds restaurant design galaxy brain
weedlord666: what a strange anecdote
picklesareok: health or wealth
zwisch: dark meat > white meat
dzid26: buildings with fake decorations
Ayyyy420Lmao: inflation adjusted pls
HexaField: @georgehotz are you opposed to an unofficial discord server? I have experience running them and if you aren't opposed I'll start one. Done well they can be a great resource and organisational tool, and anecdotally so. Up to you.
Major_Spicy: @snapcs1 i mean, it is super popular, so it is kind of okay LUL
AlwaysTilted_: What’s your order when you hit up McDonald’s?
heyitsrama: lmao its the same
plazmacsgo: the income increased because of inflation
pz3300: Mac Donald’s only make money from rent
memphisFPS: cars have became really good too compared to 10-20 years ago
heyitsrama: 61k -> 63k
Ayyyy420Lmao: real means inflation adjusted
devm0d: Didn’t your 20 year scam chart show ya that wages are stagnant for last 20 years??
knilecrack: talkin about economy: https://i.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/original/001/795/988/c92.jpg
lordBzzl: maybe by sheer repetition things get better
SpaceGhost8: slightly up, but not much overall
t00big2fl4il: fiat currency vs bitcoin
pz3300: Yeah inflation without electronics
l1ght5p33d: i am the recession
Natschz: so if the economy falls far enough we will live in castles again?
heyitsrama: georgehotz your disconnected from teh test of america my brotha
5_betbluff: this gotta be the most intelligent conversation in a twitch chat lol
HexaField: Geohot discord server. https://discord.gg/VYdj5dx George, if you don't want it to be a thing it's gone. I have had good experiences with them.
dzid26: cars are barely different nowadays compared to other technologies
pz3300: Yes
Ayyyy420Lmao: "inflation tracks economic growth" ???
SpaceGhost8: right
nitrixen: Second chart is adjusted.
Reelix: Yes
t00big2fl4il: 500 in 2009 bitcoin
Ozonemaster: cars are waaaaaaaay better
treestompztv: @georgehotz https://clips.twitch.tv/TrustworthyBrightKathyKappaPride
dingus74: Lol yeah cars are 10x better
raystriker98: they were junk
memphisFPS: dude cars are so well equipped nowadays
sidthescikid: LUL
Ozonemaster: turbos had gotten better
Appz_x: 2019 honda civic with comma ai is the best
pz3300: It should be food not electronics
Ozonemaster: more hp
benchai18: Why median and not average????
Natschz: if the economy gets to worse tv's will get black/white again?
lordBzzl: lool, used to have tape players
cemck: for technial goods but how was it for food ?
bromku: any data on food prices rn
360Plato: 2000s had shitty networking solutions
pz3300: For inflation
Reelix: @memphisFPS Assuming you can buy a car made in the past 15 years
elephantpandas: id say from 2010 up for most cars are good
informalgarlic: How does capitalism work in a fully automated society? @georgehotz
Ayyyy420Lmao: average is higher
devm0d: We’re off topic
t00big2fl4il: what about vintage tech?
nozpheratu: I've been driving a 1995 volvo for five years now, built to last if you're not a moron.
ummyeah1929: mean gonna be skewed
benchai18: Average is for sure higher. Median is like meh
pz3300: We still in recession from 2008, they just fudge the numbers
Lizardan: Trickle down ecomony 4Head
t00big2fl4il: I saw a boombox in best buy yo
weedlord666: electronics and tire compounds have advanced a lot in consumer cars
heyitsrama: @nozpheratu got my 73 240z :)
weedlord666: the rest not that much
SolarBerry: we need to solve coronavirus tonight
hordead: @georgehotz , ai wan'st around back then.. times are definitely better now
memphisFPS: all i am saying they are better products than they used to be, we have been building cars for over century now
l1ght5p33d: Every job should be automated to some degree
pz3300: Inflation adjustments should not includes electronics
nozpheratu: heyitsrama Got me beat
Ozonemaster: what u mean by that
plazmacsgo: true
ummyeah1929: because exponential inflation?
heyitsrama: nozpheratu ill wip the volvo
SpaceGhost8: much safer, more fuel efficient, probably has more horsepower
Mariosavitch: hello mr hotz
devm0d: I bought a 10gig hard drive at staples in 99’ for $330 and it failed in 3 months
Lizardan: Are cars cheaper now?
Ozonemaster: one can argue development is independent to economy
shekshas369: isn'T that innevitable since technology gets exponentially better
lordBzzl: definitely agree
memphisFPS: my car from 90s doesnt have seatbelts in read seats LUL
t00big2fl4il: 8trak
Natschz: So TV's will get back and white again?? @georgehotz
shekshas369: and thus exponentially faster obsolete?
xXICEW0LFXx: Finished my assembly lab homework
360Plato: midtier car beats a sports car of the 70s
Ayyyy420Lmao: my car has none of those feelspoor
axlebear: Things are more disposal today
xXICEW0LFXx: that took me 5 hours
lordBzzl: do cars have cd players still?
plazmacsgo: I think he mean that your perception of moneygrows less and less with the more money you get
memphisFPS: rear'
xXICEW0LFXx: I hate assembly
ShredderSherlock: not if you don't pay for the extra packages
Reelix: Will your car from today still be working 20 years from now, since your car from 20 years from now is still working today.
t00big2fl4il: I remember when seatbelts became a law in california
atzehji: i think you should compare the same thing for inflation though. and thake the average. it doesn't hold for tec
xXICEW0LFXx: that's also a lie, i don't hate assembly
sidthescikid: New cars have seat warmers PogChamp
11plus4thinking: why do people still buy apple products
pz3300: What’s your point though george?
informalgarlic: How does capitalism work in a fully automated society, Mr. communism is evil?@georgehotz
Ayyyy420Lmao: @sidthescikid a friend has a 20years old volvo with seat warmers
Jehhred: your car has power windows
plazmacsgo: ohh I see
theonlymonkas: my car doesn't even have seats LUL
AntiVax_SoccerMom: 10 MCCHICKENS?
devm0d: Back to VIRUSES
SpaceGhost8: buying a mcchicken for $1 LUL
Mariosavitch: buy 10 of them
cemck: how with real estate compared?
plazmacsgo: makes sense
HexaField: unofficial george hotz discord server. https://discord.gg/VYdj5dx George, if you don't want it to be a thing it's gone. I have had good experiences with them.
pz3300: Two hookers
sidthescikid: @Ayyyy420Lmao Ahead of their time
Mariosavitch: buy 100 mc chickens
l1ght5p33d: more cats
t00big2fl4il: 1000 iphone 11pro
360Plato: craftsmanshit is more expensive
localcanofdutchgold: 2?
shekshas369: @pz3300 priorities haha
memphisFPS: haha
hordead: @georgehotz Why are you not verified?
SpaceGhost8: let's start a cult :)
eric_hansen: however the purchasing power of the us dollar has declined significantly from the 1900's to now @georgehotz
Ghost_001: LUL
montecarlo: @HexaField he hates you!
erlsek: tanoviOK
l1ght5p33d: 200 kittens instead of 100 kittens = 2x as good
WaeHaKe: lmao
t00big2fl4il: gold standar?
Mariosavitch: ??
foti_kasparov: lul
pz3300: No you dont
HexaField: sure thing man. it's gone. :)
thekittyslayer7: @SpaceGhost8 i'm in
nozpheratu: I'm going to start a official a discord now
flickapotamus: the further u go up the more minscule the difference is say 50m and 100m
OlympusDev: Sounds good lets all start a Discord
informalgarlic: How does capitalism work in a fully automated society? @georgehotz
MrStereoX: @HexaField its ok you tried :)
Ayyyy420Lmao: im starting a discord channel too
t00big2fl4il: gold v bitcoin
ummyeah1929: we're toxic FeelsBadMan
4zimut: irc?
montecarlo: @HexaField he doesnt hate you!
foti_kasparov: Discord is waste of time
Ghost_001: D:
happypuppppy: @HexaField you still the real MVP my dude
plazmacsgo: @georgehotz how do you start contributing to a GitHub project. When I look at it , I can't understand it
l1ght5p33d: we like your streams a lot
t00big2fl4il: teamwork
Mariosavitch: @informalgarlic why should it not?
sidthescikid: monkaS No Discord
plazmacsgo: and its overwelming
MrStereoX: Discussing what ? @georgehotz
shekshas369: but i will hate you and your discord server if it causes him to stream less
brownyyyylocks: twitchies revolt
informalgarlic: How does our capitalism work in a fully automated society? georgehotz
mashafique: Discord servers = places where people go to post their anime waifus
plazmacsgo: gotchu
pz3300: Booooo
mikey9988: LUL
k3hvari: Vaping?
t00big2fl4il: get to work
hordead: is that soda?
360Plato: Make it a bioinformatics discord...
foogs_: are we choppin or what?
alicyka: Bitch I will post my anime waifu anywhere, anytime, I don't need discord
theonlymonkas: work work
Mariosavitch: the same way it works in any society @informalgarlic
nozpheratu: Let's make a "Not George Hotz" discord server
informalgarlic: @mariosavitch how do you buy goods with no money cause no jobs?
mashafique: @alicyka LUL
sidthescikid: @informalgarlic cap would collapse leading up to it i feel
benchai18: I already made it. With a pic of u from Lex’s podcast looking angry AF.
Landowner555: @alicyka lmfao
benchai18: I’ll delete
benchai18: Now
l1ght5p33d: run command ::: create attribute
burzum_: he never said the experiment, did he
foti_kasparov: @mashafique LUL
Ne0Zer0: turbotax is still a scam LUL
Mariosavitch: @informalgarlic the fact you think no jobs would exist is your false premise
knilecrack: did you hear about AMD hack?
Lizardan: @Ne0Zer0 its'not if you know how to use it
informalgarlic: @sidthescikid yeah agreed.
Landowner555: man that stove is loud
hordead: that's the coronavirus trying to brake in
sidthescikid: I bet he smelled the fish DansGame
l1ght5p33d: is AMD hack x01 instead of x00?
foti_kasparov: Cooking bats
theonlymonkas: LUL
Ne0Zer0: @Lizardan $80 to file cypto tax is a scam lol
Ayyyy420Lmao: inb4 corona19 has nothing to do with covid19 and is caused by a different virus
ICAntF331MyFAce: monkaS 👉 🦇 🥣
informalgarlic: What do you think fully automated means? Regardless any unemployment over 30%?would be horrible @mariosavitch
benchai18: I WOULD PAY $1000 TO SEE GEORGE CHAT WITH Duncan Trussel FOR A FEW HOURS
axlebear: Until the fire nation attacked
devm0d: George clearly has nuerolink installed with the speed he reads these
benchai18: virii
nitrixen: Imagine if covid-19 is bening and it's activated by something else.
Mariosavitch: @informalgarlic who builds and maintaines the automation?
sidthescikid: monkaS 👉 Discord
SpaceGhost8: didn't they record 17 days on one of the cruise ships?
Bloodswordz88: activated by 5G Kappa
PotlePS: 17 days on surface, what the fuck
nozpheratu: Depends on the surface, only a few hours on some metals.
pz3300: Hard surfsces
ummyeah1929: a week is under perfect lab conditions i think
Mariosavitch: who mines, ships, processes and packages the minerals? @informalgarlic
benchai18: I got a hard surface every morning
NullJupiter: Do you guys know the Kurzgesagt video on corona?
ummyeah1929: under sunlight/humidity itd be much less i think
benchai18: I got a hard surface rn actually
vruthlessv: what text editor is that
foti_kasparov: vim
gaffo: are you learning by wikipediaing?
granti7: @georgehotz did you take a look at chloroquine azithromycin to see why it would help fight corona?
luigifrcruz: A non peer-reviewed paper says it can stay on certain surfaces up to three days. http://the-scientist.com/news-opinion/sars-cov-2-can-live-on-plastic-and-steel-for-23-days-67260
vruthlessv: does vim custom themes or plugins
C0deCane: https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/types.html
Ayyyy420Lmao: classification by lineage i guess
Mariosavitch: @informalgarlic what is the final price of a good if its completely automated? If you say anything above free, explain to me where that price was derived.
Ayyyy420Lmao: genetic divergence
Mariosavitch: @informalgarlic i really think you have no idea what you are talking about
benchai18: The beta’s are little bitches
t00big2fl4il: alpha beta
aar0npham: aar0npham subscribed at Tier 1.
Ayyyy420Lmao: @Mariosavitch lmao at marx's price value theory
t00big2fl4il: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5744139/
Reelix: Bats - Not Rats
zwisch: sars also spread from civets
t00big2fl4il: alpha vs beta https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5744139/
hordead: Genius
hootdaflute: well it is a coronavirus..lol
wheely_mcbones: Cool, what is causing those changes?
pz3300: I always lose with Ace 2
Mariosavitch: Ace Venture 2 Receptor?
m00chan: what the hell is a civet
C0deCane: @Reelix bats = rats wings
Reelix: @C0deCane Fair enough
Waldoqq: Did you cuere the coronas yet?
wheely_mcbones: Civet is that animal who poo coffee
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz How come that nCOV is so much more "infectious" compared to HCOV?
entangledbeing: @wheely_mcbones Yes
C0deCane: @bufferovrflw simply because its less deadly
entangledbeing: Bucket list item
Landowner555: yeah
Landowner555: they have a discclaimer on pubmed
Rohitbokade94: What are we eating today?
guinness84: deez nuts
entangledbeing: So someone ate poop coffee and gave us all corona
snapcs1: bat soup
theonlymonkas: LUL
wheely_mcbones: China is making it free and China is producing most of the papers
Fosade: heyy brooo
benchai18: Well plug my baby and call me Norman Reedus .....WE’RE IN DEATH STRANDING NOW BOTS
wholesome_pepe: @bufferovrflw some scientists speculate that there is a mutation in nCov that makes it more airborne and therefore more infectious
jimmyadaro: I'm back, what's he doing?
gaffo: @georgehotz the laancet is making covid-19 papers free so I'm assuming many others followed suit.
hordead: why do they even sell the papers... they should be free
benchai18: @jimmyadaro Should I send u the GitHub link lol
gaffo: loos like elsevir did as well
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 LMAO
jimmyadaro: Sup @benchai18
dongmuya: I missed when Hotz used to call us "twitches" :(
wheely_mcbones: @hordead agree
Ayyyy420Lmao: @gaffo no way elsevier went free
l1ght5p33d: smol monies only
Ayyyy420Lmao: those dutch jews only care about money
Landowner555: @Ayyyy420Lmao they actualy did for covid
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao Who? LUL
Reelix: @hordead From a strictly financial standpoint - To fund the people who made them to make more
wholesome_pepe: if u cant beat sci-hub u gotta join them LUL
Mariosavitch: have you found the patch yet that would fix the beer virus
benchai18: @ayyyy420lmao I resent that biatch. I’m an American Jew and I too only care about money
l1ght5p33d: @benchai18 knew it
sidthescikid: okay, I think its time to devolve corona? Pop the red bubbles chat
hordead: @Reelix information should be free
Landowner555: so what makes this anti-viral????
FoxMcWeezer: FoxMcWeezer subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak! You got me into CS years ago. Worked at 2 Big Ns thanks to your mindset
wheely_mcbones: @Reelix most good scientists don't do it for money, the ones who get the money are businessmans
Reelix: @hordead What's your credit card number, CVV, and expiry date?
Mariosavitch: Meat
Landowner555: papers are publically funded, and yet not able to be accessed by the public
zwisch: taking zinc all the time is not good for you
Landowner555: iconic
hordead: @Reelix sure.. Give me a second let me get my card
C0deCane: hospitals are considering universal do not resuscitate orders for corona virus patients
jimmyadaro: cowabunga it is
Appz_x: make sure you take copper with zinc
Landowner555: @C0deCane thats bull
Landowner555: lies
miiiiiiim: @C0deCane ?
eric_hansen: @georgehotz do you take magnesium?
miiiiiiim: source
FreddiesDeadieButHasAces: what are we doing?
l1ght5p33d: treating a patient should be up to the doctor
pz3300: Fuck them supplements George. Just eat proper food man.
Reelix: @wheely_mcbones Could claim the same about the creator of any product
FreddiesDeadieButHasAces: research?
Pedroso: Hey George, How do you manage to be so disciplined?
hordead: @C0deCane nonsense
Landowner555: where are you storing this info????
l1ght5p33d: thats why hospitals pay them so much
Abnico: @benchai18 lol i laughed a lot
hordead: @Pedroso Just do it
wheely_mcbones: @Reelix yep, what this says about our society?
l1ght5p33d: if theres a loss in profit I'm sure doctor would be able to optimize that if his job required it
Reelix: @wheely_mcbones That people would prefer not to do manual labor if given the option
Ayyyy420Lmao: @wheely_mcbones what does it say about you? why arent you working for free? gimme ur money
hordead: @Reelix Not a reasonable comparison
C0deCane: @hordead just saw it on the news washington post but i don't believe much news anyways
extremelywide: LOL
hordead: So any discoveries about the Chinese virus?
wheely_mcbones: @Ayyyy420Lmao I'm actually working for free in college, making jobs in an area I'll probably not work just to spend my time with people I like
C0deCane: I like the kongflu a lot better LUL @hordead
Reelix: @hordead It is if you extrapolate several levels backwards. You need food which comes from farms which are currently not automated and require manual labour which requires payment.
peter35_: i learned about introns and exons from mgs2 LUL
el1s1us: good evening, say hi to brazil mr george
Ayyyy420Lmao: @wheely_mcbones ahahaah he does it for free
5_betbluff: gotta think a lot involved in farming is already automated or can be pretty easily
Landowner555: tbh papers should be available to the public but wheely is a tool
Landowner555: just use sci-hub tho
Reelix: Sure - It can - But then people complain that its not natural and so on
Landowner555: thank me later
sidthescikid: hey chat, is it possible for a machine learning algorithm with access to the internet just 'learn' or is there some external limitation?
Pedroso: @hordead Thanks, haha
nitrixen: Chat, is there an organism with not too many genes that we perfectly understand to use as learning material to get into this stuff?
duncansclarke: @sidthescikid What do you mean by learn?
Landowner555: @nitrixen ecoli
Reelix: @sidthescikid They work via positive and negative reinforcement, so it would need to know what it should be learning
Ayyyy420Lmao: @nitrixen bacteria or multicelular eukaria?
FreddiesDeadieButHasAces: that the thing their talking about up there lol
benchai18: @nitrixen Yes. @ayyyy420lmao‘s mom
FreddiesDeadieButHasAces: this is a great stream
FreddiesDeadieButHasAces: thanks @georgehotz
l1ght5p33d: @nitrixen what is "not too many genes"
pomprocks: biology is like some sort of alien technology 10000 years ahead of own
5_betbluff: Any one got advice on how to stop being lazy
Ayyyy420Lmao: @benchai18 woah cool it she died of cancer
hordead: @FreddiesDeadieButHasAces nice name
peter35_: in vivo
wheely_mcbones: yeah it can learn, but if you don't define it will probably "learn" things that are useless
FreddiesDeadieButHasAces: thanks @hordead
peter35_: "in glass"
pz3300: Yeah
benchai18: @ayyyy420lmao I’d say the same.... even if false
wholesome_pepe: in vitro = testube. in vivo = body
RNG_S0uL: NY is so fkd man it's getting scary here
pz3300: In vivo
Landowner555: in-vivo = in a living animal
theonlymonkas: yo vivo
happypuppppy: @5_betbluff just don't be lazy 4Head
sidthescikid: @Reelix Ahhhh, I see.
l1ght5p33d: with the Pure 100% AAA default Enzymezzz
5_betbluff: in vitro, isn't that a nirvana album
foti_kasparov: cbrah420Pepe cbrah420Pepe
benchai18: @ayyyy420lmao u know I love u don’t worry
Landowner555: in-silico = on the goddamn supercomputer
tkdboy555: @georgehotz is this relevant? https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/jgm.1111
tkdboy555: @georgehotz "An efficient RNA‐cleaving DNA enzyme can specifically target the 5′‐untranslated region of severe acute respiratory syndrome associated coronavirus (SARS‐CoV)"
Landowner555: ur computer is burning up dude
Landowner555: its so loud
C0deCane: well honestly to produce real data that we can rely on we need more time
l1ght5p33d: "An efficient RNA‐cleaving DNA enzyme can specifically target the 5′‐untranslated region of severe acute respiratory syndrome associated coronavirus (SARS‐CoV)"
l1ght5p33d: u mean a nuke
Abnico: what is with the autists asking how to code and not be lazy, is this stream cursed
Landowner555: LUL
Reelix: @sidthescikid For example, a ML thing for Mario would use an increase in the X axis (Moving right) as positive, so it would try a million different ways to do that, and follow the pathways that work
benchai18: @abnico Lol.
Landowner555: @tkdboy555 what is that called btw
foti_kasparov: @abnico Seen a lot of them
peter35_: Abnico have we had an adder*ll ref yey? Kappa
peter35_: yet*
tkdboy555: @Landowner555 I posted the title of the paper after the link
C0deCane: @Abnico teach me code pwease >(
l1ght5p33d: An efficient RNA‐cleaving DNA enzyme can specifically target the 5′‐untranslated region of severe acute respiratory syndrome associated coronavirus (SARS‐CoV) and nothing else ever for eternity and beyond
Ayyyy420Lmao: @tkdboy555 i dont think the dna can get inside cells in vivo, they used electroporation or some shit in the papaer i guess??
Waldoqq: IM BOUT MY PAPER LIKE A MUH F*CKIN SCRATCH AND WIN
foti_kasparov: Coming from r/depression and r/getdisciplined
Abnico: people over complicate things to give them excuses i assume
wheely_mcbones: are people coming here from ibs?
Tyoo_: hey george, opinions on renting vs owning? do you own your apt?
wheely_mcbones: I came from Lex Friedman
Landowner555: @tkdboy555 ty
benchai18: @abnico hOw I HaCk aNd bE sMaRt aNd GeTz goOdZ jOb aLsO wHaT aRmChAiR rEsT u UsE
Reelix: @sidthescikid Like "Moving 10 pixels right gives you 100 points, and getting a coin gives you 50 points - You have to get to 10000 points - Go"
C0deCane: yeah and only people in group 3 can go there LUL
AzzoDio: This one was better than the chloroquine study, where all the deaths were in the treatment group. You really want to compare outcomes but all these so far just do viral load.
Landowner555: @Ayyyy420Lmao yes, obviously
sidthescikid: @Reelix So if the goal for this hypothetical ML alg. is to interpret text, I would have sample data that compares the tested output to the correct answer and reinforce is respectivley
Abnico: @benchai18 hello what version of osx do u use?
dontbeameme: Did we find out how deadly it really is?
pz3300: Chinese people got skills. Dude in a back alley can make an iPhone from scratch
benchai18: @abnico I’ll tell u only if u tell me what resolution your monitor is set to. Please.
dontbeameme: Sacrifices need to be made for the good of the economy people
sidthescikid: Me :)
foti_kasparov: @benchai18 Should I go in college?
Ghost_001: not me :)
granti7: who wants to try fap? Kappa
gazny: Stick it in me doc
Risx: 0.2-0.6% if we go off SKorea & Germany
mashafique: Just blend all those meds into a strawberry smoothie and stick a straw in my mouth
benchai18: @foti_kasparov What time should I wake up in morning?
bufferovrflw: rip Prince Charles
Abnico: @benchai18 should i go to college?
wheely_mcbones: 1% is really high
pz3300: George mengalin there!
360Plato: How would you do the placebo lol
guinness84: ventilator death rate for <40 y/o?
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Theya are doing that. They used remdesivir on the first patent in the US
benchai18: @abnico Should I wipe forward or backward?
Reelix: @sidthescikid You would need to give it various levels of "correctness", and "wrongness" and input practices it can use (Eg: Click a link), and it would go
gazny: Do it to help prevent more deaths
cankunwang: only if ppl get treatment then 1%
dorkmo: https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2020/03/plague-inc-rolling-out-new-mode-where-you-fight-to-contain-the-outbreak/
Hawklite: what are the chances of death if you don't go on a ventilator?
masters8: Cause that's how placebo works...
happypuppppy: Bernie is 78 monkaS
anotherkidnamedaustin: comma.bio
Abnico: @benchai18 what underwear are u wearing?
pz3300: 50% of all medicine is placebo
Landowner555: WHAT
sidthescikid: @Reelix So tools and score
wheely_mcbones: if you know is a placebo is probably not gonna work
360Plato: @masters8 he doesnt get it
foti_kasparov: @benchai18 Should I start drinking green tea too?
Ozonemaster: i was afk i missed on that one
Ozonemaster: whats that treatment?
Lizardan: @pz3300 facts
t00big2fl4il: Favipravir?
sidthescikid: Trump is 73 thoo
dontbeameme: It’s the patients fault for not knowing what to tell the doctor
Ozonemaster: will do
Reelix: @sidthescikid Yup. It will try every tool in every possibile combination, and discard the pathways which give a low score / don't increase the score fast enough, and carry on going
nitrixen: Hydrocloroquine opens an ion gate that lets more Zinc in the cells. Zinc binds with I dont knwo what that stops the replication.
wholesome_pepe: the direct cause of death is actually the symptoms from the immune system going crazy and flooding your lungs
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz commit the changes?
zwisch: why do you /asdf every time you :w ?
iopanics: How can I find covid 19 genom sequence? Do you have a link?
nitrixen: @zwisch Presumably he doesnt know about :nohl
alicyka: "Sorry sir, we can't give you the medicine you want-- for your own safety, because some people don't want to take the risk"
benchai18: @abnico @foti_kasparov should I fill up unleaded 87 gas or 89?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @iopanics first google hit https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/genbank/sars-cov-2-seqs/
dorkmo: plot twist, george is Jude Law's character in the film Contagion CorgiDerp CorgiDerp
peter35_: does caffeine fuck with it?
PotlePS: FORSYTHIA
murgmasallam: @iopanics For the Wuhan genome , https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/nuccore/NC_045512/
Stegosaurian: dude how does he read so fast?
iopanics: @Ayyyy420Lmao thank you
ryanm0012: George come fix my computer
Ozonemaster: trainedf
wheely_mcbones: should I watch contagion?
pz3300: They even do placebo knee surgery’s now and they out perform the real surgery. No shit google it.
Reelix: @zwisch To make sure the window is currently focused
wheely_mcbones: @pz3300 I heard about that
J0hncr055: Can anyone explain what he means by 'reverse engineer coronavirus"? Like research for a potential cure or something?
Stegosaurian: I am trying to catch up but he scrolls before i finish the paragraph lmao
Hawklite: he doesn't actually read he just reads a few words and then guesses what the text says
sidthescikid: @Reelix Okay I understand. How would I start to do that? I kinda just want to know whether ML can get access to Wikipedia or Google and autonomously navigate and understand new topics
Stegosaurian: oh
J0hncr055: PotlePS Forsythia LUL
darkclemo: I have literally no idea what's going on but it's so interesting to me
t00big2fl4il: sequence https://www.gisaid.org/
mashafique: @J0hncr055 just working backwards from the virus and figuring out how it works and what its made of
wheely_mcbones: @J0hncr055 god or nature engineered he is trying to reverse engineer it to understand how it works
Reelix: @sidthescikid Finding an ML example in your programming language of choice would be the best way to start
J0hncr055: mashafique ahh gotcha thanks!
dorkmo: found the fure bros https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Forsythia
AzzoDio: @georgehotz here's one more treatment to consider, quercitin zinc, explanation here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vE4_LsftNKM&t=6m11s
entangledbeing: Final coronavirus stimulus bill is 880 pages long...
mashafique: @J0hncr055 no problem
sidthescikid: @Reelix Im sure there are python ML libraries
murgmasallam: Are spike proteins unique to a particular virus?
Reelix: @sidthescikid TensorFlow is common
nitrixen: @J0hncr055 Viruses are sequences of genes. The genes turns into different proteins that do various things. It's just like reverse engineering a codebase, to find out what are the functions and what they do, so you can patch where it's going wrong.
l1ght5p33d: @dorkmo "containing several winged seeds" agreeed
t00big2fl4il: excellent graphic https://www.gisaid.org/epiflu-applications/next-hcov-19-app/
Stegosaurian: @mashafique do you think the information found on wikipedia and the basic definitions on the websites is enough to really understand the virus? I fear the info there might be a bit too generalized and simplified.
wholesome_pepe: patent troll incoming?
nvda9: scam scam scam
dontbeameme: Wikipedia is not trusted source
sidthescikid: @Reelix I'll eat up that documentation then
eric_hansen: @georgehotz are you looking at homeopathic treatments too, such as isatis root
wheely_mcbones: little change in the molecule can cause huge changes in the effecst
granti7: did you check this? https://chemrxiv.org/articles/Repurposing_Therapeutics_for_the_Wuhan_Coronavirus_nCov-2019_Supercomputer-Based_Docking_to_the_Viral_S_Protein_and_Human_ACE2_Interface/11871402/4
wholesome_pepe: just change one of the double bonds. ez profits
dontbeameme: Plz someone edit the wiki George is using
nitrixen: @Stegosaurian He's opened over 100 papers since the beginning of this...
Reelix: @dontbeameme Until you try edit something only to have it reverted 5 minutes later by someone citing 10 different references
mashafique: @Stegosaurian I think Wikipedia can serve as a good starting point for understanding the basics of terms and whatnot. There are also references on Wikipedia that you can follow and read from there.
Nussinov: wikipedia's absolutely sufficient for his purposes here.
xhunter0001: But you promised you wouldn't be here today
sidthescikid: Wait thats actually a molecular-level scam LUL
AzzoDio: @georgehotz This is another zinc ionophore strategy https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vE4_LsftNKM&t=6m11s quercetin
nvda9: ca
ionelaipatioaei: !uptime
nvda9: can we trust Wikipedia
Juankinator: can you trust anything?
mashafique: @Stegosaurian I think to truly understand the virus you would need a thorugh understanding of virology and access to lab equipment to actually study it. George is just learning what he can and then trying to apply a programmatic approach to understanding the virus.
alicyka: Store-brand Adenosine
wholesome_pepe: u have to write a convoluted af patent that no one understands
Reelix: @nvda9 Scientific / Medical things are often edit-locked
sidthescikid: @nvda9 its better cited than any other website
hordead: @georgehotz Do you regret not becoming a doctor now?
RobMonstaFlex: isn't adenosine what caffeine blocks the reuptake of?
xxghom: what is he doing exactly?
TheFallDamage: whats ur kb?
Landowner555: isnt adenosine in caffeinee?
dontbeameme: @xxghom He finding the cure
TheFallDamage: LOL
kamtb28: Are your notes online anywhere?
darknesscrysis: is he developing an ai to find the cure for corona? and every other virus while at it :p
hordead: fap ratio?
mashafique: @Landowner555 Caffiene is its own molecule.
eric_hansen: @kamtb28 it's on his github: github.com/geohot
sidthescikid: monkaHmm
Landowner555: @masters8 i know that, i think they act on similar receptors though
Reelix: @darknesscrysis Currently attempting to reverse engineer it, and understand it as he goes along
nitrixen: @xxghom @darknesscrysis Viruses are sequences of genes. The genes turns into different proteins that do various things. It's just like reverse engineering a codebase, to find out what are the functions and what they do, so you can patch where it's going wrong.
sidthescikid: Imagine your body falling for the scam
horlabholu: @georgehotz what are you doing,what are trying to achieve?
wholesome_pepe: this is basic drug discovery?
mashafique: @Landowner555 yeah i believe it acts on teh adenosine receptors
RobMonstaFlex: same trick different patent maybe LUL
UniversalGeneve: these antivirals look like DNA base pairs since their action is to bind to the viral RNA
kamtb28: @eric_hansen thanks!
msuiche: Just got in, same question as @horlabholu
wheely_mcbones: small changes in the molecule can cause huge changes in the effects
tkdboy555: @xxghom he's currently identifying the molecules that can adhere to the enzyme gates through which Sars-Cov-2 enters the cell, thereby preventing the virus from penetrating the host cell
msuiche: I didn't realize you were streaming every day, that's awesome!
AzzoDio: @georgehotz FYI zinc is only one possible explanation of the mechanism the malaria drug might work : https://twitter.com/CurlyJungleJake/status/1238864747035942913
Reelix: Changing to -- in a program can also cause a majorly different outcome in a million LoC app :p
xxghom: thanks chat
wholesome_pepe: scammivir
Stegosaurian: @mashafique you would think there would be a thorough and detailed explanation about the virus or how it functions online but there aren't that many. I always assumed pharmaceutical companies publicly shared info like this
ryanm0012: george do you still fix computers?
mik12f4: Maybe we can vaccinate with Mosquirix or they can customize it?
l1ght5p33d: python is only one possible explanation
Landowner555: 50% of the effectivness of the drug boils down to how its delivered
Juankinator: cant we just nuke coronavirus?
Juankinator: Kappa
tkdboy555: if you can prevent the virus from entering through the gates that can fit into on the cell membrane, it can't survive.
Landowner555: other 50% from structure
Ozonemaster: inmunodepressant is a bit risky isnt it
Reelix: @Juankinator You could - Sure - But you'd eradicate almost the entirety of humanity in the process
mashafique: @Stegosaurian Viruses are pretty complicated. And there are different types of coronaviruses. If I'm not mistaken, coronavirus just refers to the virus shape.
Abnico: just execute the infected, simple
pz3300: It can’t survive a healthy person immune system
Reelix: @Abnico China literally locked infected people in their own house - It worked...
pz3300: Or we wouldn’t be here
Ozonemaster: adenine is of dna
mashafique: @Stegosaurian you can definitely find info on how viruses in general work I'm sur eonline
btpisroot: Bio study group
PiroFloydian: Adenosine is the sleepy chemical that caffeine mimics in the brain right @georgehotz
Landowner555: im so lost rn
l1ght5p33d: 3d diff
l1ght5p33d: with charge weight
matvey_ryabov: They do be a little diff
matvey_ryabov: )))
Abnico: hell yeah looks tasty
l1ght5p33d: plus folding probability
mashafique: It's pretty wild how much of a difference functional groups make.
wholesome_pepe: functional moieties and active binding sites Kreygasm
Ayyyy420Lmao: you can probably even find a NMR of a cristalized resecptor with cocaine bound
pz3300: Fuck synthetic drugs
UniversalGeneve: @georgehotz a molecule isn't "fully" engaged when in effect, i.e. only a portion of it is an active site that's recognized by whatever it binds to
wheely_mcbones: people who snort ritalin to play MTG all night know it
l1ght5p33d: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w0HLqrKjl4c
brewery85: LUL
TheFallDamage: thats just because of the bond with Oxygen they look similar
Abnico: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lisdexamfetamine
Reelix: They both have lots of Hydrogen, Nitrogen, and Oxygen - The same as the air we breath :p
zwisch: is George confusing adenine and adenosine again?
Reelix: Coincidence? ;D
williamjennings1: what is caffienes half liife?
Stegosaurian: @mashafique I know but I was surprised to see there was a culture of pharmaceutical companies keeping their research private while making it public would only do good. but C.R.E.A.M I guess lol
brewery85: timeout
hootdaflute: adenosine is also used to treat arrythmias of the heart
AzzoDio: Best case scenario for the world, drink 4 large ice coffees every day and you recover 100%
nitrixen: Imagine if people drinking coffee is what activates coronavirus lol
eric_hansen: i think the sleepy chemical is serotonin @georgehotz
Reelix: @williamjennings1 About 6 hours
mashafique: @Stegosaurian Oh yeah, money is def a factor
wheely_mcbones: @hootdaflute this explains a lot
PiroFloydian: yeah i cause thats why coffee naps work
williamjennings1: caffeine latest time to take caffiene and go to sleep on time
mikey9988: monkaW
pz3300: Herion is sleepy chemical
swill_: POG
AzzoDio: If I had to quit caffeine to avoid coronavirus, I am not sure I would survive quitting honestly. Dead either way.
Reelix: @williamjennings1 I can have a triple espresso and fall asleep 2-3 hours later - It affects everyone differently
swill_: first stream ive caught live hi goerge
mikey9988: would explain the uproars in the us and italy KEKW @nitrixen
zwisch: papaya has a lot of papain
alicyka: You could definitely use the last hour to convince a CNN reporter than coffee makes you susceptible to the virus
zwisch: papaya papain papaya papain
Abnico: @AzzoDio there is wayyyyyy better stim
alicyka: the iphone hacker said so
EduardoElGAMO: what this guy is doing ?
Reelix: @zwisch That's because papain is named after papaya...
l1ght5p33d: that paper looked legit af
zwisch: Reelix that was a simpsons reference
Reelix: Aaah
wheely_mcbones: did he described learning?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @Reelix then pikachurin was found in pikachu?
TheFallDamage: CoronaVirsu human made? hmmm
soawesome33: Maybe, george hack the coronavirus
l1ght5p33d: making a chart for the abbreviations only in your own paper = boss level
Reelix: @Ayyyy420Lmao Assuming we lived in Pallet Town - Sure - Could happen
FreddiesDeadieButHasAces: this is awesome, I alas must sleep, good night all
williamjennings1: Cool chair
Stegosaurian: George is gone. let's talk about how great of a company facebook is
soawesome33: George save the world
THX1342: hello
Stegosaurian: before he comes back quick
nvda9: it's morning here
wheely_mcbones: @TheFallDamage human interference leave a signature in the RNA, the Corona Virus don't have it.
UniversalGeneve: wanna see something crazy? the current ncov19 virus had been speculated since 2013: https://www.nature.com/news/deadly-coronavirus-found-in-bats-1.13597
williamjennings1: o:
TheFallDamage: @wheely_mcbones but they vaccine they are making is using the CHANGED RNA
mik12f4: Why wouldn't they consider using a vaccine for Malaria for Covid19? Mosquirix
MrTriharder: @georgehotz Facebook online hackathon is live right now. Topic is corona virus related work. Please participate
theonlymonkas: :0
hootdaflute: @UniversalGeneve uhh where have u been? MERS and SARS is a strain of corona
Ayyyy420Lmao: theres an even older on from 2007
wheely_mcbones: @TheFallDamage is close enough but not the same
Ayyyy420Lmao: https://cmr.asm.org/content/20/4/660 2007
t00big2fl4il: https://www.gisaid.org/epiflu-applications/next-hcov-19-app/
pz3300: Bill gates is like “ I took in told you”
THX1342: did geo buy the pcr kit?
TheFallDamage: @wheely_mcbones hmmm. yeah but that shouldn't be the case because a vaccine is a dead virus or weaker version of it
Ayyyy420Lmao: even a broken clock is right once in a while, like those goldbugs calling for market crashes
tkdboy555: @georgehotz check this out my dude https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3151162/
Reelix: @mik12f4 For the same reason that you have different vaccines for different things
btpisroot: Hey everyone, I am predicting that I will die.
pz3300: A broken digital clock is never right
MrTriharder: Idk how China managed to get one more virus in the span of 6 months
alicyka: If you want GIS data you can usually find a REST service using the developer console
mashafique: @btpisroot remember 100% of people who drink water die
RNG_S0uL: the movie contagion hits different today... spooky how similar even the talking points are
williamjennings1: congratz @btpisroot
Reelix: @btpisroot Within the next 75 years? Highly likely
wheely_mcbones: @TheFallDamage you are right, they are trying to engine a weaker version that is close enough, when they accomplish we'll have a good vaccine
Reelix: @mashafique Ban Dihydrogen monoxide? :p
Ayyyy420Lmao: molecualr docking = drug discovery how is that offtopic lul
mashafique: @Reelix that stuff is scary bro LUL
Stegosaurian: amazing how we don't know anything about how viruses evolved or what they evolved from since they can't fossilize
l1ght5p33d: corona 2020
MrTriharder: monkaS
TheFallDamage: @wheely_mcbones but they are not tho. they are just using the CHANGED RNA to make the vaccine not to engineer a weaker version
Landowner555: @Stegosaurian viruses are just an enigma
l1ght5p33d: we want dashboards
l1ght5p33d: WE WANT DASHBOARDS
Reelix: @georgehotz WAY slower
hootdaflute: @Stegosaurian did u read the wiki page on virus lol
pz3300: Virus has low iq
duncansclarke: drinking black coffee out of a glass?
wheely_mcbones: @TheFallDamage I think you are wrong, if you are right this is risking the life of the subjects.
duncansclarke: alpha move
Thotshotgg: Just tuning in... Any progress?
Reelix: @georgehotz Only the people who care to learn about it will research it, whilst it doesn't discriminate
peter35_: don't they talk about giant, ancient viruses frozen in Antarctica and permafrost and stuff?
l1ght5p33d: whole o chem graph
THX1342: can you link that paper @georgehotz please
l1ght5p33d: o chem data structs
wheely_mcbones: in Brazil at least we just reproduced to know about the behavior
l1ght5p33d: whole o chem data python
l1ght5p33d: whole one
nvda9: vi
UniversalGeneve: here's the one after mers: https://www.wired.com/2013/10/bats-next-sars-pandemic/
darkclemo: what could happen if george finds something extremely likely to solve covid? send it to scientists?
mikey9988: 5Head ahhh yes
williamjennings1: 5head?
prostidude221: !uptime
Abnico: ucla lab still open bro
TheFallDamage: @wheely_mcbones YES THAT'S WHAT I AM SAYING. They are doing it because they know the coronavirus was created and the CHANGED RNA will work. THAT'S WHY THEY ARE not worried about subjects its just the matter of time so no one would suspect anything
Landowner555: dood its bsl3
prostidude221: how the fck can you focus on something for so long NotLikeThis
mikey9988: it's a BTTV meme , basically means big brain sarcastically or unsarcastically @williamjennings1
wholesome_pepe: we solving protein folding now? if we can determine that from genetic data then that would be Pog
williamjennings1: i have a 5head
ackxhpaez: It was predicted in a 1981 Dean Koontz book!
mashafique: you should enable bttv on the stream @georgehotz for the dank emotes
wheely_mcbones: @TheFallDamage this CoronaVirus is not created, you have expert articles explaining that
nvda9: oh ye
Ayyyy420Lmao: he read that b4 stream to seem smarter
mikey9988: PopChamp @williamjennings1
nvda9: oh yea
mikey9988: PogChamp @williamjennings1
Landowner555: man fuk if anyones injecting me with that
ryanm0012: favorite paper ever?
TheFallDamage: @wheely_mcbones do u believe those expert articles? who posted them? SAME PEOPLE WHO CREATED IT
360Plato: Is there any way to even know if a virus was engineered
THX1342: does anyone have the link to this paper?
Thotshotgg: Kreygasm NotLikeThis Kreygasm NotLikeThis
UniversalGeneve: you're probably more than most other labs can, since science research is defunded
dprophecyguy: Hey @georgehotz some people are also saying that virus affect slow in tropical countries like India and Pakistan ...
l1ght5p33d: find microscope output
Reelix: @TheFallDamage Programmers make viruses - Programmers make anti-viruses - Coincidence?
ackxhpaez: The virus wasn’t lab-created, they were simply trying to weaponize it, but it got out
wholesome_pepe: making a mutation on a couple codons cant be detected as a hack
subconix: what have you learned about covid-19?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @360Plato if it has dna identity to diferent viruses
jmp0ut: yo geohotz
williamjennings1: @dprophecyguy those people are pretty immune because they live in not very good sanitary conditions already forr years
ackxhpaez: Like anthrax
jmp0ut: pharmacology is what you need
t00big2fl4il: alpha, beta, gamma, and delta coronavirus
jmp0ut: genome lyasing on side channels
jmp0ut: like serrapeptase
TheFallDamage: @Reelix thats what I am saying dude
jmp0ut: and MCT interstitial micronization
THX1342: williamjennings1 stfu...
Ayyyy420Lmao: heat button? gonna burn some gasoline
snapcs1: @williamjennings1 thats not how it works lmao
nvda9: is he taking notes on green text, can't read them
TheFallDamage: @georgehotz why china didnt close its border when they found the first case
Landowner555: @jmp0ut i swear ur making those words up
Reelix: @TheFallDamage Electricity in your PC - Lightning kills causes fire - Therefore... PC's cause light!
Stegosaurian: it already has two strains. luckily even if manages to evolve again. it won't evolve to be more deadly. because the deadlier the virus the less infectious it will be.
jmp0ut: not at all
williamjennings1: im just guessing lol
360Plato: @Ayyyy420Lmao thks
jmp0ut: you can look up every word
wheely_mcbones: @TheFallDamage the arguments convinced me, I'm open to new information, but the ones saying it was not engineered looks stronger to me now.
jmp0ut: and it makes sense
hordead: @georgehotz ny is going to start using the blood of recovered patients to help those critically infected.. isn't this all we need?
l1ght5p33d: Nueron protiens? Brain virus. name my band
Reelix: @TheFallDamage The same reason no-one else did
pz3300: He’s got a point though. We over sanitize our homes
jmp0ut: not my fault if you're not literate to use word searches
peter35_: TheFallDamage maybe they figured they could contain it in their country and western countries would fail
mikey9988: not a 5Head after all @williamjennings1
jmp0ut: proteases are very useful
mashafique: More like 3Head ela12
williamjennings1: have u seen india sanitary conditions
snapcs1: its not cool to spread misinformation
TheFallDamage: @peter35_ CHINA didnt announce the first case when they had it. they waited so long to announce the virus
Landowner555: "genome lyasing on side channels"
Landowner555: that sounds dumb man
jmp0ut: A protease is an enzyme that catalyzes proteolysis, the breakdown of proteins into smaller polypeptides or single amino acids.
snapcs1: if you dont know something dont talk like you do
jmp0ut: you sound dumb man
l1ght5p33d: bro india hasn't seen indian sanitary conditions
nvda9: a Chinese doctor imprisoned for 3years for making genetic modified baby
jmp0ut: why dont you want to resolve what i mean
jmp0ut: that's jank
nvda9: *genetically
jmp0ut: get dunked on
Landowner555: i already looked it up, nothing important comes up
TheFallDamage: @peter35_ simply but making an assumption by containing the virus in their country caused so many people's death
tkdboy555: @georgehotz the reason why I shared the molecular docking paper is because molecular docking and molecular dynamics and intertwined. You will need to implement statistical distributions of molecular docking methods into your program in order to highlight the behavioral probabilities of whatever drug/molecule you decide to simulate as a receptor blocker.
jmp0ut: because you're expecting a cookie cutter solution
jmp0ut: numpty
Stegosaurian: @nvda9 modification to what? can you link the source?
Landowner555: relax ...
Landowner555: yikes
jmp0ut: wake up
nvda9: it's on new York times
jmp0ut: tyke, squirt, champ
nvda9: wait
l1ght5p33d: wtf is numpty
l1ght5p33d: is this numpy
l1ght5p33d: only numpy here
dprophecyguy: Hey, @georgehotz Can you also tell how you read these papers so fast and without slowing down? I really wanna pick how you look for pointers and navigate through paper
t00big2fl4il: Rae1
UniversalGeneve: you can buy those btw
nvda9: here it is https://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/30/business/china-scientist-genetic-baby-prison.html
Landowner555: @dprophecyguy increase IQ 4Head
Reelix: @dprophecyguy I'm decent at software dev and such, but bio completely destroys me - No idea how he does it...
hootdaflute: primase is taught in basic bio
Landowner555: @nvda9 is that relevant to corona?
nvda9: no
Landowner555: thats old news man
xmalware60: Nidovirus?
dprophecyguy: @Landowner555 It's not about IQ, IQ might be related to the speed at which he is synthesizing information. But what i am talking about is, how he skim through the paper
dprophecyguy: I see that there is a pattern of how he is reading and skimming through by just looking at keywords
Landowner555: @dprophecyguy i mean iwas jk, but i think thats also related to IQ...
UniversalGeneve: @dprophecyguy every bio paper has an "abstract" section in the front page, read that and you get a summary of the entire paper. you dig deeper into it of you think it's relevant for your study/research
wheely_mcbones: @dprophecyguy pattern recognition, therefore IQ
Reelix: It's looking for specific familiar keywords to latch on to to get a jist of what its about
l1ght5p33d: 6 10
Kawhiet: Will viruses like this lead to more leeway on genetic testing?
DecayingSkullz: I have 4,040 channel points.
williamjennings1: @DecayingSkullz congratz
jmp0ut: now you're looking at phosphorylation
dprophecyguy: @UniversalGeneve Maybe that's case
DecayingSkullz: @williamjennings1 thx
jmp0ut: welcome to nerve gas VX production gang
mashafique: @UniversalGeneve I think every proper research paper has an abstract.
Ayyyy420Lmao: spend them
jmp0ut: organophosphate poisoning is some seirous business
THX1342: gdbio
happypuppppy: @georgehotz have you looked up any realistic molecular simulation videos on youtube
AresRai: its decades
Penguino138: Did you end up buying the DNA reader?
jmp0ut: last i heard of cheap chiral centers for nerve agents it involved borneol
l1ght5p33d: Nothings wrong if you generalize enough and add caveats
jmp0ut: bathtub VX gas
UniversalGeneve: @georgehotz here's a cool vid on dna replication: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Hk9jct2ozY
wheely_mcbones: a lot of it is certainly wrong because of how academic articles work, confirmation bias
Ayyyy420Lmao: @jmp0ut uncle fester is that you?
dprophecyguy: @UniversalGeneve Are you from bio field ?
tshields44: https://github.com/bigginlab/OxCompBio/tree/master/tutorials/MD
tkdboy555: @georgehotz Molecular docking is extremely relevant to ligand-protein interactions, which is basically what is happening when sars-cov2 binds to
jmp0ut: :)
tkdboy555: @georgehotz ACE2
Landowner555: @wheely_mcbones thats such a ridiculous statement lol
wholesome_pepe: cryo electron microscopy is the furthest we've come to observing it. before it was x ray crystallography
UniversalGeneve: @dprophecyguy yeah, trying to move into SWE tho
wheely_mcbones: the most renowned probably are not because you'll become famous by proving them wrong
tkdboy555: @georgehotz "Rapid Context-Dependent Ligand Desolvation in Molecular Docking" https://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/ci100214a
jmp0ut: 26 years of science in my belt
jmp0ut: including hacking polaritonic systems
wheely_mcbones: @Landowner555 most of them, the most important are not bs
AresRai: they need more computers in bio
TheZarkxs: and still do not develop a vaccine, thats how they spend our taxes
tkdboy555: @jmp0ut is my post relevant then?
Emanuell45: are we in qna
Landowner555: another WEEK>" LMAO
Emanuell45: ?
Lana_Lux: get them on stream
Landowner555: naw man
williamjennings1: few weeks
zelkh9: another week and had to google n terminus yeah ok bud
tkdboy555: @Lana_Lux you a beast
sliceserve: do you have one glass to the left, and another to the right?
ziggyzergling: true LUL
Lana_Lux: LUL
jmp0ut: @tkdboy555 sure is, good find
tkdboy555: @georgehotz "Rapid Context-Dependent Ligand Desolvation in Molecular Docking" https://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/ci100214a
nvda9: locust
Landowner555: the people who run these studies are mad smart
wholesome_pepe: we dont have the necessary tools to watch the components of a cell move around
theonlymonkas: but why bats don't die???
mehdi_tw: common geroge we know that if we give you few weeks you will create a new virus man
AresRai: get another virus expert LUL
Lana_Lux: @tkdboy555 haha
C0deCane: LUL thats how America does things
iamaaronbowley: i have better things to do yet im here :)
cookienz: start a gofundme and rent ur own lab ez
Ayyyy420Lmao: @Lana_Lux are u the girl that called him on the phone earlier???
bulksquat_thrust: Probably doesnt give the pharma companies enough money
murgmasallam: Do you have any idea about the vaccines in trials in the US? They are doing it already
gazny: We need Agile development in bio
aj37z: lmao
jmp0ut: like solving narcolepsy, not enough money
jmp0ut: they just want drug addicts
t00big2fl4il: throw the genome data at qira
Landowner555: fever drop to 0 4Head
hordead: a company will take all the credit
wheely_mcbones: yeah, and even after all that people still doubt vaccines
jmp0ut: noopept helped me retrained my brain
Lana_Lux: @Ayyyy420Lmao no
bulksquat_thrust: daily corona standups
Appz_x: lmao
tshields44: https://github.com/bigginlab/OxCompBio/tree/master/tutorials/MD
happypuppppy: isn't that what the github issue told you to do
TheZarkxs: coronavirus is a pretty cool name not gonna lie
UniversalGeneve: what's hard is that bio isn't really something you can just visualize. i'm a visual learner so i struggled with the subject for a while
tkdboy555: @georgehotz This will help "Rapid Context-Dependent Ligand Desolvation in Molecular Docking" https://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/ci100214a
theonlymonkas: imagine all the people
mashafique: My main issue with academia and the reason I didn't bother pursuing a PhD is there there's too much focus on fighting for grant money and pumping out papers instead of actually focusing on quality results. Add that to having to teach and other beaurocractic stuff that slows down progress.
l1ght5p33d: Thats what university students are for
t00big2fl4il: corona genome data input -> qira
jmp0ut: money is jank roaded
localcanofdutchgold: lul
jmp0ut: bank road is jank road now
bulksquat_thrust: @mashafique same
Ayyyy420Lmao: that happens so much with omeprazole, they give it out for no reason
THX1342: LUL
wheely_mcbones: the system is broken, maybe in the next years with crowdfunding
SolarBerry: martin shkreli
Thotshotgg: STAY INSIDE
Ozonemaster: qiravirus
Landowner555: @mashafique typically good papers require good quality results
Landowner555: @mashafique nature papers etc
l1ght5p33d: glory > money
xalariian: thoughts on toilet paper situation
bulksquat_thrust: omeprazole made my acid reflux worse
jmp0ut: at the end of world war 2 it took psychiatrists to rebuild japan, they were the drivers of the economic reparations post nuked japan not economists
williamjennings1: hotz university
Hawklite: why would you start your own university instead of trying to reform public schools?
ImpalerV: have we made any progress so far?
tkdboy555: @georgehotz "Rapid Context-Dependent Ligand Desolvation in Molecular Docking" https://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/ci100214a
jmp0ut: when psyops mutinies on five eyes
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz Why can't you apply the hacker culture but in open source kind of way
Landowner555: ur going to school!?
jmp0ut: it's always a party
UniversalGeneve: Isn't a PhD basically "work on a project, specialize you knowledge towards your project, and learn to teach"
Joeliftstuff: how many prog. languages do you know?
TheFallDamage: Trump University
wholesome_pepe: how universities gonna compete with open source knowledge tho?
l1ght5p33d: is this a scam
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
l1ght5p33d: are we being trolled
pz3300: Did you say your starting a university?
JdPaulBlart: trump university 2.0
Ayyyy420Lmao: @bulksquat_thrust yeah but the thing is that they give it out alongside any other med nowadays, at least in my country, they bought all the doctors or something, they say it's a ''stomach protector''
Landowner555: @UniversalGeneve Phds are meant to teach you how to think critically and scientifically about a problem, and solve it. everything else is secondary
informalgarlic: super happy fun time now university
Eternallightning: WYOMING ?
Kawhiet: Is this like Kanye's ranch?
gazny: What kind of weather we talking about
tornpaperyoyos: OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq
imafungi53: whats your net worth geo?
C0deCane: CULT 100%
mashafique: @Landowner555 exactly but often you find yourself trying to get something out there to keep getting funding
l1ght5p33d: WYOMING???
deep5: SAT KEKW
Stegosaurian: is it going to be free?
l1ght5p33d: double or triple bunk beds
TheFallDamage: Internship at Comma.ai guaranteed?
Jehhred: comma.edu sounds good
wheely_mcbones: like "prove you really want to learn and know how to learn new things"
pz3300: Fucking the teacher
yaus_baus: george hotz cult
Landowner555: @mashafique thats more on the end of the PI though
l1ght5p33d: not quad bunks ...
zwisch: just don't pull a Siraj
coloneljerkoff: Will polygamy be allowed?
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz Like Recurse Center https://www.recurse.com/ It's for programmers
Landowner555: @mashafique though yes grants are competitive..
dorkmo: https://wiki.opensourceecology.org/wiki/Factor_e_Farm
williamjennings1: hell yeah
Stegosaurian: how will you select teachers?
l1ght5p33d: this is troll af
jmp0ut: so what do i do with the automated robotic warehouses pumping hypersonic weaponry for the space race
jmp0ut: nvm coronavirus
happypuppppy: can you just pay me with github stars
THX1342: just keep the MBAs out of it and it will do fiine
iDoMathss: LOL “WHAT DO YOU NEED MONEY FOR”
TheFallDamage: everyone in ur universities gets an internship in comma ai
bulksquat_thrust: id take a 20k paycut to work at a research lab like that
RadricCSGO: D:
phrixus_bro: after 10 years you learn the real truth about Xenu
Ayyyy420Lmao: @georgehotz you think we will get to mars in our lifetimes?
Hawklite: $30k/year to watch youtube in the classroom
UniversalGeneve: LUL
Landowner555: HAHA
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz What's the point of being together at one location ?
l1ght5p33d: geohot dont compromise your morals
jmp0ut: hating on greedkeeping babyfuckers
iDoMathss: FYI check the price of a thermocycler
jmp0ut: we are in a CBRN simulation
optimizely: @georgehotz how do you choose what to work on?
SolarBerry: not in the corona future
DecayingSkullz: What's your D2F?
jmp0ut: who breeds in such environments
Emanuell45: sounds like fun ngl
mashafique: It would be cool to have a community for focused on learning and sharing information. I would love to participate from a math&physics perspective and learn from others and help others learn
mik12f4: i agree
pz3300: Headmaster George!
wheely_mcbones: @iDoMathss money is a pretty antiquate to measure someone contribution to society, it only works if people believe in it
Ozonemaster: odd view
360Plato: I never had that.... Just studied pdfs and wrote code
DevGabr: eae mano tira o corona da bahia pfv
Thotshotgg: WHAT DO WE HAVE TO DO?
Landowner555: *drops mic*
Ozonemaster: LUL
tornpaperyoyos: sphere itself
WEEEEEEEELL_ITS_KNOCC_OUT: SeemsGood
Kawhiet: Just drink pure zinc
Emanuell45: *walks away*
theonlymonkas: like prison
ICAntF331MyFAce: atpOld
Kawhiet: Got it
ziggyzergling: LUL
sliceserve: first time here, oddly interesting
360Plato: lol
TheFallDamage: which countries will do it first?
Landowner555: USA man
TeaLeafi: fascinating
pz3300: Getting high together
TeaLeafi: and true.
Parkpark1997: commaai cures covid-19
theonlymonkas: wash your hands
xmalware60: france
Parkpark1997: instant news headline
Eternallightning: "The only thing to fear is fear itself (unless ur >70 years old)"
Ozonemaster: this guy manages the desktop windows
Ozonemaster: like a master
hordead: LUL
jmp0ut: yes
Ozonemaster: my desktop is always shit
Natschz: What do we have to do?? xD
imafungi53: okay that was not 20 seconds
Eternallightning: Alt Tab
Joeliftstuff: what do you thinks gonna happen
jmp0ut: such bindoze
Landowner555: the only thing to fear is sphere itself - flat earthers
TheFallDamage: @georgehotz u washed ur hands for less that 20 seconds
Thotshotgg: Is Monolaurin a good supplement to take?
innerbean: this is really fascinating
Emanuell45: your hands a dry
bulksquat_thrust: bulksquat_thrust subscribed at Tier 1.
sliceserve: is that the sleeping bed to the side?
tornpaperyoyos: imwaspS imwaspS imwaspS imwaspS imwaspS imwaspS imwaspS
Emanuell45: are*
xmalware60: Please wash your hands for at least 20 seconds
jmp0ut: pl0x signature so janked
Parkpark1997: washing hands dont cure coronavirus
Stegosaurian: @georgehotz What's the sickest you've been? why aren't you afraid of catching it?
Eternallightning: just dont get it 4Head
imafungi53: i missed it why shouldnt i be scared again?
Landowner555: h4ckerman DEBUNKS coronavirus
360Plato: its not like you got it by pissing on your hand
4zimut: tomorrow we are going to see a bigger pile of groceries
xmalware60: you don't have a table to eat?
mashafique: don't forget to hydrate George elaChug
optimizely: @georgehotz how do you choose what project to work on
sliceserve: he DOES have one glass to the left and a different glass to the right
murgmasallam: Dont do it man
theonlymonkas: shkreli has the cure for corona in prison
tkdboy555: @georgehotz here's some super-relevant biophysics https://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/ci100214a#
WooraWoora: Are you not putting other people at risk doing that?
jmp0ut: i eat holding my plates
tornpaperyoyos: Hacker DESTROYS coronavirus with FACTS and LOGIC
peter35_: well a girl would def get me out of the house
t00big2fl4il: what do you think about trial and error
jmp0ut: good to be conscious of what you eat at home
Landowner555: @tornpaperyoyos LUL
jmp0ut: never lose vigilance
jmp0ut: always erect
THX1342: you don't hang out with older people, right? lanaluCat
stale2000: monkaS societial breakdown
Landowner555: can u tell us what this graph shows
THX1342: `geohot kills VCs
THX1342: LUL
Joeliftstuff: monkaW
jmp0ut: fuck the economy
TheZarkxs: who is afraid of the boomer remover? corona is a very light virus
jmp0ut: asterank dot com
RadricCSGO: they dgaf LUL
stale2000: The only thing to fear is fear itself
costcospizza: thats life buddy
scarbromangler: https://neherlab.org/covid19/
scarbromangler: fear is the mindkiller
Stegosaurian: there won't be societal breakdown but an economic collapse is inevitable I think
Emanuell45: imagine starting retirement then get taken out by the rona
scarbromangler: @stale2000 hi
sliceserve: easy now
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz Why don't you use tor browser ?
tornpaperyoyos: Hacker DESTROYS coronavirus with FACTS and LOGIC
jmp0ut: http://www.asterank.com/
SolarBerry: imagine wage slaving your whole life and then dying of corona
innerbean: so there's no option for you to modify behavior for a short period of time to contribute to a greater good in doing the things that is understood to be effective in getting through it?
jmp0ut: how do i pull the 1000 trillion dollar asteroid with klystrons yesterday
iDoMathss: @wheely_mcbones Not saying anything about measuring contribution to society, I’m all for a university based solely around learning (we actually need more of this)
Ayyyy420Lmao: imagine wage slaving
Ozonemaster: Well in Spain we ran out of space for the dead bodies. but apart from that we cool LUL
DiosDIO: Is the Coronavirus man-made?
foti_kasparov: So what do we do?
Penguino138: Do you think there will be a resurgence in China now that they're opening travel back up?
ahahahaitslit: brazil's prime minister is literally a corona virus denier lmao
360Plato: this will cause a debt crisis guaranteed
bulksquat_thrust: A lot of old people dying would actually fix the social security debt issue as morbid as it is
alicyka: I feel like economic collapse is in the chamber so who knows what the fuck is going to pull the trigger
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz So would you rather have more infected/dead people than economic collapse?
mik12f4: dont be another statistic https://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/investigations/why-more-young-males-in-san-diego-county-test-positive-for-coronavirus/2292888/
Ayyyy420Lmao: sneed's feed and seed, formerly chuck's
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz don't you think politicians know them already but they just don't give a fuck
wholesome_pepe: on the bright side. we have way more infrastructure to keep us alive on the cheap than 50 years ago.
hordead: @georgehotz China was able to do it for 2 months
gazny: So you agree that we should go outside by April 12th? I feel with every country but china will lose so much by closing the economy so much. Almost like china gains a lot from all of this
Stegosaurian: there are some economists estimating that unemployment will reach 30%
innerbean: Again.... so there's no option for you to modify behavior for a short period of time to contribute to a greater good in doing the things that is understood to be effective in getting through it?
nohnamw: here in Brazil it is being very difficult
Stegosaurian: companies will go bankrupt and will need bailouts
TheZarkxs: half a million of infected, and only 21k deaths, mostly very elder people. corona is a joke, open my favorite italian restaurant NOW!
jmp0ut: if the internet is considered essential
jmp0ut: it becomes a utility
THX1342: if only people were rational
jmp0ut: this changes net neutrality does it not
Ayyyy420Lmao: 30% is casual here
SolarBerry: completely different world back then
Ozonemaster: check for unemployment in Spain LUL LUL
jmp0ut: merica jank roaded silicon
TheZarkxs: 6,9%
AntiVax_SoccerMom: ask two economists a question and youll get 3 answers
thesevoicesareloud: unemployment numbers come out tomorrow
wheely_mcbones: "some economists"
peter35_: when they ease lockdowns they should make sure masks are available imo
DiosDIO: The coronavirus is more deadly if the hospitals are saturated tho
SofiaLouise: there are a lot of different ways to meassure the unemplyement rate..
WooraWoora: @georgehotz those numbers aren't comparable when people are actively being told not to work, not losing their jobs because of a depression
leftyytwo: scam
localcanofdutchgold: lul
alicyka: lol scam fields
Kawhiet: spreadsheet tracking unemployment right now https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1WLJ1j7igM88C2XysCuN4lMH7W2NUdZq4dnO0DbyR7H4/edit#gid=0
tkdboy555: CAN WE TALK ABOUT how congress is trying to pass an anti-encryption bill right under our fucking noses amid this entire coronavirus epidemic? Shit's fucked, and they will be able to access everyone's data
williamjennings1: two biggest scams lol
Penguino138: cause theyre both scams lol
jmp0ut: RIFK
pec_adillo: basically both government run
sliceserve: this is like watching a movie
Ayyyy420Lmao: the biggest scam is chainlink
Landowner555: theres no % wtf
TheZarkxs: water, electricity, etc.
SolarBerry: govt jobs DansGame
4zimut: scams everywhere
C0deCane: yeah sure back in 2018
covac123: nothing
phrixus_bro: get paid
Eternallightning: red tape
pwnbase: dick all
pz3300: Zero hours workers
Ayyyy420Lmao: push papers
DiosDIO: nothing
wholesome_pepe: the military is the biggest employer
dingus74: lool
ICAntF331MyFAce: get a paycheck no matter what :)
bulksquat_thrust: Lots of security clearance holders too
aj37z: plan meetings
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz In India the government has imposed curfew already for 21 days. And day to day workers does not have anything to go by. Police are already beating the shit out of everybody they are finding out on roads.
aj37z: then plan meetings for planning meetings
theonlymonkas: LUL nothing
C0deCane: a lot of them quit their jobs after trump closed down the gov for 30 days
tkdboy555: @georgehotz usaspending.gov
UniversalGeneve: 14% ooF
mattdougherty22: military is quite bad though in spending
l1ght5p33d: Plato Republic with King GEOHOT!!!!!
Penguino138: That's a lot of slaves
jmp0ut: ZAMBIE!
gazny: This quarantine is getting me ready to live on mars!
Emanuell45: yh road workers
happypuppppy: LUL
ackxhpaez: china just buys bonds to manage their currency
Landowner555: lol
TheZarkxs: less boomers thank to corona=less spending
XiuYee1: LUL
C0deCane: thats not current tho
pz3300: Skim
l1ght5p33d: I vote Geohot for King
vonhoganon: DMV slaves
l1ght5p33d: all in favor
leftyytwo: these statistics are made up by the government!!! scam!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! look at the URL
Joeliftstuff: banana republic good stor
Stegosaurian: maybe it includes the military?
nvda9: @dprophecyguy LMAO
jmp0ut: hack the planet, they're trashing!!!
guinness84: what do you even mean banan republic
Ayyyy420Lmao: foodstamps
Emanuell45: police counts as goverment right?
bulksquat_thrust: think DMV worker
Eternallightning: disability / nursing home ?
360Plato: ugh oh hes going down the rabbit hole.
tkdboy555: LOL
vonhoganon: DMV, military, law enforcement
wheely_mcbones: is actually a good number, compare it to greece
rafalive: george my ball smell nice during this time of covid
ackxhpaez: Also, that's state and local government
deep5: It tells you percent distribution
pwnbase: those figures probably don't include goc contractors either
pz3300: How you gunna pay China the 15 trillion
theonlymonkas: WutFace WutFace WutFace
Ayyyy420Lmao: im surprised he didnt know it
xmalware60: Compare it to france aha
tkdboy555: bruh your mind is getting blown right now
alicyka: Entire nation is just people helping people helping people helping people helping people helping people helping people helping people helping people
Eternallightning: proffesional
Kawhiet: Information
l1ght5p33d: LEET AFFF
Stegosaurian: the private sector and small businesses are going to be hit the hardest
360Plato: information
TheZarkxs: people who get social asistance
innerbean: isn't the debt
vonhoganon: information
Joeliftstuff: information
hhhasan: Mining
happypuppppy: software engineers = nonagriculture self-employed
ackxhpaez: the categories are based on SOC codes https://www.bls.gov/oes/2018/may/oes_stru.htm
iDoMathss: @georgehotz do you think we should have an economic system at all? I.e we go back to non-specie systems of trading
innerbean: something someone would have to try to collect on?
hordead: information
Kawhiet: 80/20 rule
innerbean: who will come get it?
TeaLeafi: i like this lecture.
TheZarkxs: thats literally wealth creation
Ayyyy420Lmao: they produce value otherwise they wouldnt get paid on the free market...
jmp0ut: actually i'd put them in Agriculture, because if software developers like Sean Harris aka Wiz didnt farm the ground and crops are shitfucked
rafalive: rough
rafalive: but true
jmp0ut: what are you valued for
Ozonemaster: "restaurants" *laughs in McDonald's*
tkdboy555: REKT
ackxhpaez: and the industries are based on NAICS codes https://www.census.gov/eos/www/naics/
wheely_mcbones: US is not really producing value, it buys value from other countries and sell it in a high value, the are like old cars salesman
TheZarkxs: i do not think you understand economics my friend
guinness84: naval ravikant derivatives
360Plato: let me guess engineers are log value
SofiaLouise: How do you define value? If someone wants to eat in a restaurant, they create value, right?
pec_adillo: i think you mean production not value maybe?
DiosDIO: Farmers are important
theonlymonkas: exponential?
ackxhpaez: BLS doesn't collect data on agriculture
eric_hansen: D
jmp0ut: Josh Harris aka |Wiz
jmp0ut: my bad
aj37z: monopoly
jmp0ut: been so long
ackxhpaez: agriculture data is collected by the Department of agricultural statistics
tkdboy555: Value is relative to the job that maximally contributes to technology that defeats death. No cap.
leftyytwo: nobody cares about the tool only the result
foti_kasparov: So what's your point ?
gazny: This has happened before, literally the renaissance where people developed new tools and we progressed.
jmp0ut: when guys like Josh Harris went from billions to nothing in dot com bust they probably felt the same
SpaceGhost8: huh?
tkdboy555: We're trying to defeat death here
jmp0ut: but to turn into like potato farmers
360Plato: LUL were next to actors
vonhoganon: LOL
jmp0ut: lmao
localcanofdutchgold: they run em in the movies
williamjennings1: What are data centers?
kaiokenx90: puts or calls?
theonlymonkas: LUL
Kawhiet: Truckers?
tkdboy555: #TranshumanismGang
cookienz: LOL so acting is just as important as visa's paywave service ok
bulksquat_thrust: hopping off for the night, gotta work early, take it easy chat Geohot
Eternallightning: those are some of the most opposite sectors you could choose
vonhoganon: mechanics?
TheZarkxs: any king of money exchange is wealth creation, and the robbers of the politicians get their part
360Plato: military
mik12f4: what about P and B services
AntiVax_SoccerMom: KKona DEEP STATE
Penguino138: Govt ppl gonna get bailed the fuck out
aj37z: print money brrrr
vonhoganon: military, law enforcement
wheely_mcbones: well you are using it now
ackxhpaez: Schools
Emanuell45: police officers
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz Check the definition?
SpaceGhost8: brrrrrrrrrr
eric_hansen: @georgehotz lots of bureaucratic red tape to create no-value jobs
l1ght5p33d: prevent anarchy
DiosDIO: Actors and Sportsman people make more money than the military and the state
williamjennings1: push paperz
Incurs0: dod
360Plato: and law enforcement
TheZarkxs: administration probably
roystang: is this live
alicyka: Military is ~%3
dr_set: schools
AntiVax_SoccerMom: DWP
zwisch: military, police, firemen, etc.
Waldoqq: military police teachers
XiuYee1: MonkaW
wheely_mcbones: roads, information, security, laws...
vonhoganon: but then again taht doesnt make sense bc military is 1% or less of the total population im pretty sure
robotboy987: transportation
dr_set: schools are a big percentage
Waldoqq: city officials
hhhasan: Apparatchiks
jmp0ut: a growth expectancy of 4 million by 2028
tkdboy555: they do nothing
SpaceGhost8: the gubberment KKona
SolarBerry: can someone tell me who runs the world wide web
tkdboy555: shitty data science
jmp0ut: what's the birth rate of the U.S.
wholesome_pepe: military or private contractors for the department of defence?
williamjennings1: just sneezed :o
gazny: Simulations about corona lol, and deep space satellite spying on each other
wheely_mcbones: sanitary system, flying logistics, measurement patterns...
jmp0ut: and immigration rate?
UniversalGeneve: the militiary serves as america's greatest past time: dick flexing on other countries
tkdboy555: they do shitty data science
Ayyyy420Lmao: @SolarBerry Al Gore
Lourned: city people do nothing and they get paid nothing
C0deCane: Border patrol Kappa
flickapotamus: military and school's
360Plato: military has operations on every continent
Eternallightning: start the repo
nvda9: schools a
SpaceGhost8: makes money move
l1ght5p33d: repay societal debts
innerbean: is that just federal or all, local, state and such?
eric_hansen: @SolarBerry google Tim Berners Lee
nvda9: schools are
JonBoy11: military, politicians, local city jobs, post office, etc, etc, etc
Stegosaurian: Where would you categorize artists and athletes? do you think they create value?
Landowner555: twitch streamers are the value destruction people 4Head
foti_kasparov: What if we use the human resources of military to create value?
tkdboy555: straight up, government jobs do shitty data science based on the 1st page of their google searches
peter35_: journalists
AzzoDio: rent seeking businesses
cookienz: sec are value destruction
Parkpark1997: o
360Plato: next to actors
UniversalGeneve: @Stegosaurian artists make value. athletes? Hmm....
Landowner555: athletes are next to baristas
Eternallightning: entertainment value ?
bufferovrflw: https://www.bls.gov/careeroutlook/2014/article/federal-work-part-1.htm
cars1n: @solarberry nobody. It is just a connection of servers so the server owners kinda and the infrastructure owners
Ayyyy420Lmao: athletes do ofc if you include soccer
DiosDIO: Athletes arent necessary
TheZarkxs: ?
robotboy987: irs, fbi, sec etc
bufferovrflw: ^ federal gov sector
innerbean: how complicated is it to managed hundreds of millions of people?
THX1342: athletes are just entertainers
Landowner555: music is pretty legit tho..
innerbean: it's a big job
AzzoDio: high frequency tradin
m00chan: making life better isnt value?
360Plato: we should just broadcast war and call it "american sports"
bufferovrflw: https://www.bls.gov/careeroutlook/2014/article/federal-work-part-1.htm <<< federal gov sector
Landowner555: artists make tools, athletes r tools cbrahAyy
scarbromangler: what about the pornographers
theonlymonkas: FBI open up
wheely_mcbones: yeah!
eric_hansen: technically HFT is a zero-sum game @georgehotz
cars1n: @scarbromangler artists
lordk3k: violent flash animations
williamjennings1: who gives the most value ?
PiroFloydian: can you rehash n and n squared people? @georgehotz
Emanuell45: homeless people take value?
Ayyyy420Lmao: what about NEETs relying on gobernment gibs to buy chicken tendies??
PiroFloydian: i missed that
jmp0ut: the stats in 2019 say about 4 million jobs accounted for from immigration and births but illegal migrants number in the 20's of millions
Landowner555: grad students take out value Keepo
Bloodswordz88: Sex Workers
360Plato: Rentseeking is the term your looking for
foti_kasparov: Should there be more toolmakers then the ones that use them?
Ayyyy420Lmao: what about NEETs relying on gobernment gibs to buy chicken tendies???
innerbean: that's populous value...subjective appreciation, who are you to judge it's 'value'?
ThirstyDrank: Is take-value > neutral positive
Stegosaurian: Do you think the government should bail out large corporations to avoid a recession or eventual depression?
Lourned: not in russia LUL
Pedroso: what about the distortion of the media
dr_set: how about contamination and waste? They produce contamination and waste
btpisroot: what if that coffee is the tool that helps someone be exponential?
nvda9: B)
scarbromangler: it's linear vs non-linear
DiosDIO: Doctors are REALLY needed these days
vonhoganon: doesnt HFT create very high liquidity in the market though?
SpaceGhost8: and equipment
Bloodswordz88: Do Sex Workers count?
Ayyyy420Lmao: what about NEETs relying on gobernment gibs to buy chicken tendies??
alicyka: Active Military are 0.9% of the population, so I don't know where the fuck the other 12% comes from.
l1ght5p33d: The stock market shouldn't even exist probably
ThirstyDrank: Productivity of farmers is probably exponential already. Where agriculture would be linear
ackxhpaez: Farm statistics are done by the USDA https://www.ers.usda.gov/topics/farm-economy/farm-labor/
SolarBerry: HFT does provide liquidity
jmp0ut: so if about 30 million unaccounted for undocumented migrants live in America the employment sector's stats are janked
Landowner555: @DiosDIO news flash, doctors wont be coming up with the cure for the coronavirus
Ayyyy420Lmao: nothing, doctors are a living wikipedia
SofiaLouise: Find a diagnosis?
foti_kasparov: Do prostitutes create value?
360Plato: glorified encyclopedia
phrixus_bro: I heard that hooking people up to ventalators was very involved
knilecrack: it's not hard
K177: get a monkey to do a xray scan LUL
iDoMathss: @georgehotz So the act of innovation is the generation of value in your eyes?
knilecrack: because you have a doctor.
Eternallightning: Researchers add the value doctors distribute it
vonhoganon: @K177 doctors dont do xray
DiosDIO: @Landowner555 Taking care of eldery people is important tho
xalariian: what about scientists
RadricCSGO: they just prescribe whatever the drug companies tell them to prescribe
l1ght5p33d: Crowdfunding with HFT in the middle
Ayyyy420Lmao: what about NEETs relying on gobernment gibs to buy chicken tendies??
Landowner555: @DiosDIO NURSES and PSWs do that
dr_set: You said the other day that was an argument to make that a person born today has negative value, if you agree with that, then doctors are not very useful
scarbromangler: It's the nurses who do most of the hard-work, I think
knilecrack: Yes but they know how human body work
K177: @vonhoganon ah yeah true
jmp0ut: 190435.9 would have to be the stats
THX1342: doctor's make decisions and decide where assets are put into
AresRai: gen x
Bloodswordz88: what about cam girls
foti_kasparov: Do elderly people create value at all?
jmp0ut: for 2028 stats of total jobs
wholesome_pepe: doctors = symptom mangagers
wheely_mcbones: acatually deciding what medication will treat someone without killing this person because of another disease
SolarBerry: retirement homes were abandoned in spain and they died
williamjennings1: nurses work 60 hours a week
innerbean: If the money gets laid up in huge amounts in accounts doing nothing it lowers the amount available to circulate. so makes many more, the rest, 'poorer'
scarbromangler: what about e-girls
vonhoganon: what about hentai creators
PiroFloydian: what about sex workers @georgehotz ?
bufferovrflw: https://www.bls.gov/careeroutlook/2014/article/federal-work-part-1.htm @georgehotz Federal Goverment jobs breakdown
solitarynative: What should I spend my trumpbux on?
scarbromangler: what about the okay boomer girl
Ayyyy420Lmao: what about NEETs relying on gobernment gibs to buy chicken tendies and shitpost all day?? do we create value?
DiosDIO: @Landowner555 Nurses can't do all the work alone
coloneljerkoff: Whats the value of pontificating twitch streamers?
Kawhiet: Value is subjective
hordead: doctors are being replaced by google
Pedroso: what about the media distortion
PiroFloydian: workers create value
wheely_mcbones: you probably would I think
Landowner555: @DiosDIO you have no idea what ur talking about man
jmp0ut: whats the cost of 20 million jobs
phrixus_bro: what do you think about the value of the finance industry
jmp0ut: thats what america is budgeting to lose
foti_kasparov: I thought Apple was a scam
l1ght5p33d: Jobs was pretty scammy Woz was the product
innerbean: create or capture?
solitarynative: What should I spend my trumpbux on?
360Plato: Stock Traders are their to efficiently allocate ressources
happypuppppy: where do people who spend all day on twitch chat like us fit in?
darkclemo: starship stacking is going on right now @georgehotz
peter35_: that whole starship thing is so cool
innerbean: value capture
tkdboy555: So MAYBE we should be creating a society that focuses on helping people help themselves raise their base value, so that there is a higher percentage of the population that gets to "Elon Musk" tier
darkclemo: pressure raptor test next 3 weeks
edu4594: geo is grad in...?
ooMariaoo: oh
phrixus_bro: nooo
edu4594: bio?
edu4594: cs?
SpaceGhost8: LUL
vonhoganon: hedge funds/prop trading nothing of value?
mashafique: Jebaited
Ayyyy420Lmao: what about NEETs relying on gobernment gibs to buy chicken tendies and shitpost all day?? do we create value?
Santiago_LHC: @edu4594 hacking
Emanuell45: thats a bad human being
williamjennings1: stop with the neets
Stegosaurian: Why do you think largest companies threaten mass layoffs unless they get a bailout?
edu4594: @Santiago_LHC hacking at UCLA
Eternallightning: visionary
yaus_baus: tendies stimulus package
foti_kasparov: @edu4594 Check his LinkedIn for details
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz do you think having a vision with a dick attitude is okay ?
360Plato: whatever bro
wheely_mcbones: I think society should be happier and not necessarily more efficient, I'm not sure if both go together
jmp0ut: so 4 million jobs will afford the cost to lose 20 million jobs and process everyone and require atleast 2 jobs at minimum to capture every person
Emanuell45: lmao
boengels: Morning George!
peter35_: Ayyyy420Lmao n-no FeelsBadMan
l1ght5p33d: but why cant you put music on it?
PiroFloydian: For watching off stream. Why elons boring company is bs: https://youtu.be/4dn6ZVpJLxs?t=18 @georgehotz
l1ght5p33d: BUT CANT PUT DATA ON IT
jmp0ut: so you need 60 million people at minimum to process 20 million undocumented migrants
DiosDIO: @Landowner555 Try not having any doctors in a hospital for a week in any hopsital in the world then
edu4594: @foti_kasparov i cannot, i don't have a linkedn
l1ght5p33d: NO DATA ON IPHONE
dorkmo: suicide nets
l1ght5p33d: no data
funwayz: apple fanboy Kappa
alicyka: George, Table 2 shows which department federal employees work https://www.bls.gov/careeroutlook/2014/article/mobile/federal-work-part-1.htm if you're interested; Table 2
dorkmo: lol
Lourned: Commodore 64 was far more superior computer
Parkpark1997: but u are android of self driving
AzzoDio: Apple still makes quality hardware though their software is terrible
Ayyyy420Lmao: @yaus_baus just buy popeye's stocks and when u buy chicken tendies you get your money back
K177: thats assuming that a different company wouldn't come up with a touch screen concept for phones and push it out
Hawklite: is he really implying apple is the innovation behind phone technology?
scarbromangler: Kind of surprised you're not an android guy
Eternallightning: @georgehotz why are so many people not as passionate about a good prooduct as jobs ?
risesinner: The boring drill fits exactly in his rockets
jmp0ut: jank roaded
tkdboy555: SAMSUNG?
jmp0ut: simple math
tkdboy555: uhhhh
foti_kasparov: @edu4594 Create a trash account
Kawhiet: Teachers count too
edu4594: @foti_kasparov ok...
vonhoganon: jesus christ the VA
Pedroso: Omg, you read so fricking fast
Ayyyy420Lmao: veteran affairs?
wholesome_pepe: all those pensions we have to pay monkaS
Penguino138: Jerk off verterans
dorkmo: VA hospital
williamjennings1: push paperz
Eternallightning: VA hospitla ?
360Plato: manage ptsd bois
vonhoganon: veterans healthcare
wheely_mcbones: there is a book called bullshit jobs who talks about the mental breakdown of people who do useless jobs
phrixus_bro: healthcare for veterans
alicyka: Veteran Affairs is the VA, infamously terrible and useless
innerbean: oh, so the ends justify the means even if it means screwing others? ugh
Parkpark1997: take care of them
latenightbj: military loans
pec_adillo: care takes and state run hospitals
scarbromangler: department of VA fights the war against the Colin Kaepernicks of the world
risesinner: helps them navigate the VA and Veteran resources
l1ght5p33d: i want to run apk on iphone
THX1342: are veterans considered employees of that dpt?
AzzoDio: no president gets elected by promising to cut the military budget
DiosDIO: This is part of the Military
Stegosaurian: Do you think the large military budget is justified?
Kawhiet: There's a reason it's called a government job
entangledbeing: Government could include university professors and researchers
l1ght5p33d: we want apk on iphone
Emanuell45: thats some stalin shitt
vonhoganon: they include doctors and other medical staff as well to take care of veterans
Parkpark1997: ask trump
l1ght5p33d: APK ON IPHONE ONLY or apple dies
wholesome_pepe: cuz they fought in ww2 and vietnam
coloneljerkoff: VA has a huge system of hospitals
tkdboy555: @georgehotz USASPENDING.GOV
risesinner: each county has a veteran rep
JonBoy11: everyone that works at a VA hospital technically. all the way down to the guy cleaning dishes
risesinner: that is why they are so many
foti_kasparov: @edu4594 I mean u won't regret it :)
risesinner: they make almost no money
tkdboy555: @georgehotz usaspending.gov
K177: so theoretically if hitler had a positive impact in the future then he was a good person? LUL
Lourned: USA = military industrial complex LUL
risesinner: each county has one
bufferovrflw: Nerd-sniping: The Stream
l1ght5p33d: why can't i run apk on iphone
innerbean: hmmmm, managing how many vets? That's not efficient
mikey9988: Chair force LUL
hordead: remember there are 52 states
360Plato: So Israel should build Hitler statues?
entangledbeing: State university professors and researchers may fall into gov
williamjennings1: how would you eliminate them ? :o :o
risesinner: each county has 1 and they make about $20k/yr
edu4594: @foti_kasparov i hope lul
l1ght5p33d: y no apk on iphone tho
PiroFloydian: Mao executed landlords cant be that bad @georgehotz
Ayyyy420Lmao: wrong he dided in 82 in paraguay
pec_adillo: tru just give the vets their money, let them figure out their own care
ahahahaitslit: lMao
bufferovrflw: Well, due to Hitler and the Nazi Germany, we've got rockets
AzzoDio: maybe he has a secret diary where he invented cold fusion pretty much the only scenario
2600: that's one of the arguments for UBI, is getting rid of the the administrative structure deciding who gets what.
tornpaperyoyos: Well most of the employees in veteran affairs are veterans themselves
dr_set: or in latin america a couple of years ago ...
kaiokenx90: do prostitutes add value?
Pedroso: What you think about vertical lockdown in Brazil?
foti_kasparov: Heil the Führer
AresRai: killing 25million people w all their potential is a lot of unquantifiable bad
360Plato: oof
K177: LOL
Stegosaurian: What do you think of the large military budget? Is it justified?
Penguino138: @georgehotz what do you think about China reopening it's borders, possibly letting the virus back in?
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz What about instagram influencers ?
Ayyyy420Lmao: nazi scientists were kidnaped by nasa so we could go to the moon
cybergenik: We got research into medicine, Noice
vonhoganon: isnt much of modern china mostly due to xiaoping?
hordead: hitler still killed more people than the coronavirus
tkdboy555: government officials are themselves lobbyists for useless government jobs and inefficiency in the federal government system
PiroFloydian: oh they are 100%
latenightbj: rapidward.com
innerbean: I think the same positive value can be created without screwing others over, it just gets distributed fairly...
Landowner555: the nazis did a lot of experiments on humans
optimizely: Looking for an idea to work on next
solitarynative: stalin
Emanuell45: lmao
Landowner555: something we'll never be able to do again probably
Lizardan: Hitler
Parkpark1997: hitler vs coronavirus
vonhoganon: the military offers $100,000 signing bonuses like its candy
mikey9988: Hitler is Covid-420x69 ?
williamjennings1: OMg
Parkpark1997: EDUCATION
SpaceGhost8: hitler ez
DiosDIO: Now, hitler
K177: LUL
Nussinov: we should have nuked corona virus when we had the chance
williamjennings1: yikez
scarbromangler: coronavirus isn't doing anything wrong. it's just being itself
PiroFloydian: military industrial complex is maybe the worst @georgehotz
saygan_: if Hitler was good then do I have the right to enslave my neighbors if I can prove it will have a positive outcome in a few decades
wholesome_pepe: darpa literally funded the basic research for the corona virus tho LUL
solitarynative: Stalin worse than both
wheely_mcbones: sovietic union did more to end the nazis than the US but they are not receiving this much money for their veterans, is not about merit
pikomane2: is it 18 million veterans divided by how many patients per psychiatrist
tornpaperyoyos: They tell you that you only have to serve 4 years but its a minimum of 8. 4 active duty 4 reserve
2600: hitler vs coronavirus who would win
Bloodswordz88: HahaSnowhal
SofiaLouise: WW2 : 75 million
cars1n: Society would be much more advanced if we kept having world wars because preventing death is the absolute best motivator @georgehotz
btpisroot: Eh, let's go with WW2
pz3300: Yeah
abdcw: i mean hitler was a bad guy but at least he didn't force me to stay inside and not get pussy
foti_kasparov: HITLER WITH CORONAVIRUS IS THE WORST THING EVER
K177: ccp data monkaS
PiroFloydian: try US @georgehotz
Bloodswordz88: HahaLean
Kawhiet: Mao killed more people than hitler
logi6000: what did I miss
hordead: just go by the amount of jews he killed
AntiVax_SoccerMom: monkaS Hitler with super aids
Nussinov: adolfovirus
DiosDIO: Did hitler kill anyone himself?
Landowner555: stalin and mao are the real villans
THX1342: expendable, right?
williamjennings1: 43million what
Ayyyy420Lmao: @hordead how many is that?
tkdboy555: bioweapons is a cold-war thing
SpaceGhost8: uh
pz3300: Himself?
THX1342: -.-
logi6000: @pz3300 well yes
pikomane2: hitlers still alive
l1ght5p33d: i wanted to run a single apk on my iphone. it had ONE JOB
Stegosaurian: world population in the 1940s was around 2.6 billion
Ayyyy420Lmao: @pikomane2 in our hearts
raystriker98: India is gonna get fucked, our PM is a joke
logi6000: what would you name a search engine
foti_kasparov: @ayyyy420lmao No, in Argentina
PiroFloydian: @DiosDIO he killed himself
Kawhiet: Mao killed more people than hitler
SpaceGhost8: EZ
hordead: @Ayyyy420Lmao 1.3m
tornpaperyoyos: OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq
PiroFloydian: yeah Modi sucks lmao
Ayyyy420Lmao: @foti_kasparov no he went to colombia, then argentina, then paraguay, died in 82
DiosDIO: @PiroFloydian Fair enough
Hawklite: what's the economical impact hitler vs corona though?
KaleSC: @georgehotz do you think it's good that all the old people are dying ?
360Plato: whats the ACE2 prevalence for Indians?
Stegosaurian: Africa will be hit hard
AzzoDio: isn't India hot climate?
K177: wait, does your coronavirus projection factor in overwhelmed hospitals?
l1ght5p33d: sweet justice
kaiokenx90: Are you saying there wouldn't be a difference in response in the US from Trump vs Obama?
alameda13: do u think human killed hims3lf more or viruses @georgehotz
wheely_mcbones: like 1 million were japanese nuked that did not needed to die
4zimut: careful we have twitch staff
K177: ahh aight
Ayyyy420Lmao: @hordead im surprised you could give the actual figure and not the meme number
DiosDIO: The virus isn't killing itself
wheely_mcbones: is not all on Hitler
AresRai: are tropica countries less at risk ?
martinkirilov: And we still talk about Hitler. If coronavirus turns out to be worse, imagine the aftermath of that
Bloodswordz88: People die on the Toilet everyday
hordead: @Ayyyy420Lmao what's the meme number?
AzzoDio: 2x just corona deaths? what about death from other sources that also need hospitals?
Tyrant_01: GEORGE DID YOU STOP HACKING ?
K177: cmonBruh
AzazelTheGoat: how many people has mcdonalds killed?
WEEEEEEEELL_ITS_KNOCC_OUT: monkaS
solitarynative: cmonBruh
tkdboy555: The US government should contract AI companies to calculate which jobs are most able to be automated and then to actually automate them. We would cut federal spending by BILLIONS, if not HUNDREDS OF BILLIONS.
AzazelTheGoat: is mcdonalds worse than hitler?
360Plato: shut it down
SpaceGhost8: projections thus far have all been wrong, to be fair, and I hope it remains that way
logi6000: George I like that idea from yesterday about organizing the worlds information
mikey9988: monkaW
raystriker98: no dude, he made us bang utensils and applause for no reason at all.. I'm not kidding Google India utensil banging coronavirus
DecayingSkullz: Twitch is going to somehow make an issue of this.
RNG_S0uL: speaking of nazis here comes twitch staff
Ayyyy420Lmao: @hordead 6 milions
Penguino138: Will more die from the economic impact of the virus than the actual virus?
K177: KKona wtf
innerbean: death measuring contest? gah
UneducatedZoomer: monkaS
optimizely: How do you choose what to work on next?
TeaLeafi: nah your good?
DecayingSkullz: Hitler convo
wheely_mcbones: Obesity vs Hitler
williamjennings1: mhm kind of want mcdonalds right now
Parkpark1997: free speech
btpisroot: I think we said too many trigger words
jomkingal: Hi George greetings from NJ
DecayingSkullz: Yeah exactly
TeaLeafi: free speech is awesome!
K177: yeah free speech is not a thing on twitch LUL
DiosDIO: Twitch isn't about Free speech
TeaLeafi: Twiutch can go succccc it lols
hordead: @georgehotz Conclusion.. Hitler was a deadly virus
knilecrack: you are insulting corona
DiosDIO: is about E girls
SpaceGhost8: Shkreli save us
K177: Kappa
tkdboy555: The US government should contract AI companies to calculate which jobs are most able to be automated and then to actually automate them. We would cut federal spending by BILLIONS, if not HUNDREDS OF BILLIONS.
TeaLeafi: Twitch is a scam
latenightbj: will obesity rates increase becaue of social distancing ?
mutrx: is this end of stream q&a
Ayyyy420Lmao: we're adults? Kappa
kruzustv: yo my ese got a cabrona virus :(
vonhoganon: twitch = free speech? LUL
phrixus_bro: DLIVE BABYE
C0deCane: This is purely scientific
K177: PogU
AzzoDio: every time you talk about world War II you start getting people talking about Neo-Nazi stuff eventually, they somehow find every twitch channel
theonlymonkas: SCAM
TeaLeafi: YEAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
localcanofdutchgold: lul
knilecrack: private twitch yeah
360Plato: dlive stream
innerbean: haha yea, the SAD diet vs all the tyrants
TeaLeafi: !!!!
zelkh9: what if we get obese sars-cov-2
btpisroot: comma.twitch
TeaLeafi: YEAHGHHHHHHHHHHHHH
Parkpark1997: go on mixr
raystriker98: Mixr
Lourned: like mixer LUL
williamjennings1: just go to mixer
Natschz: GO TO MIXER IF YOU GET BANNED xD
theonlymonkas: LUL
fullcind: twitch free speech KEKW
ICAntF331MyFAce: POGU
PiroFloydian: comma.stream
TeaLeafi: comma.twitch
dorkmo: hi im 12
AzazelTheGoat: i didn't see a "this is an adult stream with mature subject matter". im triggered
alameda13: chat is 12 years old
K177: mixer PepeLaugh
TeaLeafi: comma.twitch !!!!!!!!!!!
tkdboy555: automate the government
THX1342: LUL
hhhasan: comma.tv
THX1342: comma.thot
TeaLeafi: comma.twitch
Parkpark1997: comma.tv
360Plato: famous last words lul
theonlymonkas: NICE
aar0npham: Lol
edeustua: have you ever used gaussian processes for anything?
hordead: There;s no free speech on this platform
Emanuell45: there are 3 moderators here lmao
kaiokenx90: can u reverse engineer my farts
THX1342: thanks, mods
Stegosaurian: George what do you think the future of human evolution is?
kruzustv: OOOF
SpaceGhost8: comma,dank
TeaLeafi: AHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
aar0npham: Comma.twitch
TeaLeafi: got em!
AzazelTheGoat: lol gotem
optimizely: Interesting project to work on ?
UniversalGeneve: call it spasm LUL
TeaLeafi: gotem
mutrx: @georgehotz did you look at SAMPLE6
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz Probably "Hitler" is a keyword that alerts Twitch Staff?
TeaLeafi: gotem!!!!
newlastaccount: How many animals have you killed?
mounnrocc: !uptime
UneducatedZoomer: @georgehotz could you hack me rn if you wanted to
DiosDIO: How many people has cancer killed?
logi6000: I like your idea of organizing the worlds info
tkdboy555: like automating government jobs?
jomkingal: Do you stay up late most of the time?
Lourned: @georgehotz hey i used your jailbreak on my iphone 5 back in the days, thanks :D
solitarynative: more like sample dicks amirite
hordead: @georgehotz How many hours of sleep do you usually get?
theonlymonkas: do you still want to be a serial killer ?
C0deCane: a lot
wheely_mcbones: well you don't want neonazis making reunions on twitch, is no good for publicity
optimizely: Any Interesting project idea?
innerbean: it's not being used offensively to sow hate
l1ght5p33d: "Have you ever used gaussian processes"------- - Is this a troll?
Emanuell45: There is 1 staff here lmao
solitarynative: monkaS
phrixus_bro: hi staff
williamjennings1: where
Ayyyy420Lmao: @stale2000 hello janny
TeaLeafi: staff lols
TeaLeafi: staff is lame
RNG_S0uL: do you think us new yorkers are fkd?
foti_kasparov: Should be more I guess
PiroFloydian: that was in 1 year
georgecruece: hi gasol
TeaLeafi: cancer is a scam
360Plato: its ok guys the twitch staff is Warhammer player so he probably's a fascist anyway LUL
TeaLeafi: CANCER IS A SCAM!
logi6000: staff is a scam
DiosDIO: Everyone can have it
SpaceGhost8: I'm waiting for WA to update their count because all I see is this bullshit message "The state's notifiable conditions database is currently experiencing a slowdown because of a 10-fold increase in the number of lab reports received. Our IT team is working to correct the issue."
AzazelTheGoat: AzazelTheGoat subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! there are so many different types of cancer
yaus_baus: cancer is a shill
alicyka: You usually get cancer at the end, yes
mounnrocc: cancer is induced by inflammation i heard
vonhoganon: obesity -> heart disease
alicyka: It's just the end might be at a young age lol
mounnrocc: but im dumb so
AzazelTheGoat: I heard turmeric helps with inflamation
Penguino138: The cure for cancer is changing peoples' habits and behaviours
innerbean: cannabinoids and mutated cells research is fascinating too
THX1342: Did selfies kill more than coronavirus in 2019?
Landowner555: look up prevalence of cancers in children/young adults
DiosDIO: There is no cure to cancer also
boengels: Hey George, what sources would you use to find out real corona death numbers vs gov reported in other countries? thoughts?
Ayyyy420Lmao: autism rates also on the rise
mounnrocc: food related fosho
KaleSC: the Bubonic Plague triggered the Italian Renaissance because all the wealthy (older) people died and younger people inherited the wealth to spend how they wanted on arts for example... do you think something similar could happen after covid?
btpisroot: Twitch staff are fans of the Hotz
martinkirilov: Yeah, but cancer has been out there for a long time. Imagine covid19 being out for the same time, though probably we’d find a vaccine
Penguino138: @georgehotz The cure for cancer is changing peoples' habits and behaviours
PiroFloydian: They do now pepeLaugh
theonlymonkas: the hotz
UniversalGeneve: dna has a half life of ~120 years. you get cancer since as you age, a lot of your DNA start randomly breaking. you have enzymes that repair that, but they're "stupid" enzymes
alextodoroki: im gay and lubed and ready to go boys
KaleSC: the spanish flu killed 50 million
logi6000: obesity epidemic like it's God damn polio. Americans are spoiled. Lazyboy got it right.
williamjennings1: ):
PiroFloydian: depends
optimizely: Death is a scam
hordead: @Penguino138 lol
PiroFloydian: on what the raw numbers are
AzazelTheGoat: thats a crazy number
AresRai: check Japan numbers 🤔
PiroFloydian: if suicide just goes way up and nothing else changes thats bad @georgehotz but the other way is good yeah
ThirstyDrank: wow that looks like a correlation in the middle
hordead: coronavirus is just speeding up death by cadiovascular disease
ThirstyDrank: where they had the intersect
cars1n: Mental health is = physical health
theonlymonkas: LUL
innerbean: the increasingly toxic environment and diet filled with free radicals means alotta cancer.
boengels: @hordead that is true
AzazelTheGoat: is that death of a broken dick? unsafe sex?
DiosDIO: COVID-19 is also killing more smokers
THX1342: is selfie inflicted deaths on the rise or is it plateauing?
K177: KKona
SpaceGhost8: vaping CiGrip
Lourned: vaping PogChamp
360Plato: Dying from too much food
Penguino138: Smoke them ciggies
btpisroot: sigh
AzazelTheGoat: hey guys remember that vaping death epedemic? that was like covid-18, or covid lite
aj37z: smoking weeed
Emanuell45: VAPE SEGMENT COMING SOON
C0deCane: smoking is big is Asian areas i heard
SpaceGhost8: vaping saved the tobacco industry
Kawhiet: lmao russia
pec_adillo: takes a generation to phase out smoking deaths
Ayyyy420Lmao: smoke every day dudes
DecayingSkullz: Newton formulated his theory of gravity in quarantine in the time of the black plague. Pretty interesting.
logi6000: we need to listen to the obesity part of underwear goes inside the pants
AzazelTheGoat: i was surprised to hear vape shops were still open during this pandemic.
bufferovrflw: What's up with Greenlad?
bufferovrflw: *Greenland
innerbean: oh, wasting disease in deer? if that jumps over it will be ugly
DiosDIO: @C0deCane China's pollution is fucking disgusting
THX1342: that graph is brilliant
williamjennings1: woah
K177: LOL
mutrx: TRUE
SpaceGhost8: terrorism monkaS
knilecrack: terrorisam
williamjennings1: heat disease
knilecrack: ahahahaha
williamjennings1: heart*
SpaceGhost8: LUL
360Plato: 1/3 people killed from terrorism would be living in Yemen
Penguino138: 33% terrorism = fear mongering
mutrx: we live in a society
tkdboy555: LINK PLEASE
Lourned: where is gaming?
asanti20: good ole heart disease
boengels: scary really
peter35_: now it's muh russia
mutrx: did you watch Joker @georgehotz
optimizely: Show us a scam
deep5: every minute 60 seconds pass
boengels: how much we are being lived
innerbean: i like the style of this stream...hah
zwisch: interesting to see stroke is about right
T3chHS: Give us link please
Penguino138: How many deaths a yaer from Ligma?
C0deCane: LUL i fuckin hate the media
AzazelTheGoat: but mcdonalds employes a lot of people. is the cure worse than the problem?
Emanuell45: 1 IN 3 people die of cancer?
PiroFloydian: corporate owned media is shit
phrixus_bro: crazy
alameda13: link?
williamjennings1: so 1/3 of chat is going to die from heart diesease
boengels: george can you share that link
boengels: plz
wheely_mcbones: McDonalds
DiosDIO: Media says Terrorism kills more than cancer LUL
tkdboy555: link pleasee
gamerguy009: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Lourned: I guess video games are under terrorism LUL
tkdboy555: elink please
boengels: Link please?
tkdboy555: link please
sigmund_graphics: media is garbage
UniversalGeneve: @tkdboy555 https://ourworldindata.org/causes-of-death
boengels: georgeeeeeeee
T3chHS: Paste the link here please!!
boengels: linke please?
williamjennings1: too many energy drinks
boengels: hahaha
littleZIPPY_92: be pnemonia
UniversalGeneve: THE LINK: https://ourworldindata.org/causes-of-death
asanti20: and heart disease is usually linked with obesity
AzazelTheGoat: is higher respitory disease from smoking dank bud?
boengels: BEEP BEEEEEPPPPP
wheely_mcbones: the flu
wheely_mcbones: Corona is lower respiratory disease
logi6000: we need to listen to underwear goes inside the pants
wisamalrawi: Yes
AzazelTheGoat: yep
PiroFloydian: yeah ive heard of it
logi6000: yeo
Tyrant_01: GEORGE SHOULD I STOP LEARNING CYBERSEC AND GO WORK WITH YOU IN COMMA?
SpaceGhost8: my dad is dying of COPD, yeah
gamerguy009: Dont touch your face
wisamalrawi: Quite famous actually
innerbean: yea...
boengels: Thanks @UniversalGeneve
innerbean: commercials
wisamalrawi: Smoking causes it
RNG_S0uL: yeah my dad has it
AzazelTheGoat: its something i heard about and I live in canada. Not sure if thats why
DecayingSkullz: What are your thoughts on using a Neuralink implant to cure neurodegenertive diseases like ALS or dementia
Ayyyy420Lmao: wtf is this
Landowner555: LOL?
SHAVEYY_: geo is bedtime
Kawhiet: its like half of the death causes can be attributed to McDonalds
SHAVEYY_: go bed
wisamalrawi: They carry oxygen tank with them
omniilista: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
aj37z: this video is cursed
SpaceGhost8: LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: i'm addicted, i'm addicted to marihuana
Lourned: 420
AntiVax_SoccerMom: LUL
SpaceGhost8: LMAO
localcanofdutchgold: BANNED
DiosDIO: LUL
gamerguy009: I want neuralink
innerbean: cannabinoids are dank
mutrx: F
Emanuell45: lag?
ankitc: you got throttled son
Ayyyy420Lmao: third world country internet
ankitc: charger
MrTriharder: F
hordead: tos
bloopsterr: lagg
koreanfoodyum: snort weed erryday
williamjennings1: f
xmalware60: lag
zwisch: frames dropped out the wazoo
ankitc: its the charger
gamerguy009: Lagg
peter35_: yeah lag
AzazelTheGoat: prescription drugs killed my mom. I have a deep hate for the problem of over prescribing.
MrTriharder: Corona affecting the internet monkaS
hordead: tossss
braininavatt: lol I thought it was me LUL
Emanuell45: twitch ai probably caught that naked guy
whycopper: why is my pp hard
wisamalrawi: Lagg here too
4zimut: !tabs
ankitc: charger throttled it
localcanofdutchgold: actually banned
Penguino138: major lag
neto3113: upload constraints?
Ayyyy420Lmao: injecting a whole marihuanas every day
foti_kasparov: cbrahTune cbrahTune cbrahTune cbrahTune
anup_kodlekere: youtube has reduced bandwidth
MrTriharder: Kreygasm
anup_kodlekere: pretty sure twitch will too
SpaceGhost8: better
Hawklite: it's good now
williamjennings1: gonna get a snacky
Landowner555: TWO chargers
mutrx: twitch staff is censoring monkaS
gamerguy009: Bad Lagg
AzazelTheGoat: twitch is throttling the stream becasue there was a bum
AresRai: losing a lot of frames
Lourned: saved
wisamalrawi: bandwidth probably
Penguino138: video killed the bandwidth
mounnrocc: laggy boye
btpisroot: not enough ram
hordead: your internet caught the coronavirus
ankitc: yes its fine now
koreanfoodyum: making use of that thunderbolt 3
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz Wait, Macbook/OSX supports multiple chargers? damn
Landepbs: you need to download more RAM Kappa
Ayyyy420Lmao: must be cold with all those iwndows open
MrTriharder: Ok now
peter35_: stack overflow monkaS
cars1n: Wow ram doesnt grow on trees
innerbean: if the thc-a isn't dried or raised above 180f it doesn't turn to thc and it's not psychoactive
iDoMathss: Chromium over safari? Asking since I'm not sure
aj37z: need windows11
DecayingSkullz: @bufferovrflw yeah you have four thunderbolt ports
gamerguy009: Geohotz create a better twitch site
AzazelTheGoat: these lyrics aren't 100%
bufferovrflw: @DecayingSkullz I know, I didn't know that you could use multiple of them, I though only one port would be used for Power Delivery, even if you connected an additional charger
MrTriharder: @georgehotz we need comma.tv now
AzazelTheGoat: accurate*
m0ld_0n3rz: remember when this was on the radio in like 2004
pz3300: I thought that said lady boy. Phew
m0ld_0n3rz: it was a pretty big hit
THX1342: LUL
C0deCane: LUL hahahhaa
pwnbase: t h i c c
mashafique: LUL
asanti20: OBESITY
aj37z: very hard indeed
Lourned: cheesecake Kreygasm
SpaceGhost8: definitely not on the radio
un3okapi: leading cause of death: capitalism
williamjennings1: WOKE
C0deCane: 55 gal drum of coke LUL
ankitc: i am obese
koreanfoodyum: No one cares about the obesity epidemic, but everyone freaks out when there's a pandemic SeemsGood
asanti20: thiccness oppression
wheely_mcbones: Corona is lower respiratory disease
ahahahaitslit: stay woke
m0ld_0n3rz: yeah this guy had like two hits that made it to the radio
Stegosaurian: TOUGH QUESTION: for the sake of evolution should medicine not be perfected and should natural selection be allowed to propagate and perfect humanity?
pz3300: See George start eating proper food dude
foti_kasparov: Supersize me
Incurs0: I want that drum of coke
btpisroot: Stay coke
neto3113: burgers and cheesecake though ...
ankitc: strapons
pz3300: No lol
alicyka: sounds like aesop rock or busdriver
ackxhpaez: Every 60 seconds in Africa, a minute passes
aj37z: socialism is the future
DecayingSkullz: lmao
mounnrocc: localist capitalism ftw
mashafique: No LUL
Santiago_LHC: @Stegosaurian Nah, evolution has its own agenda, and it's only reproduction
pikomane2: if capitalism is so good why is the birth rate in africa 8x higher
Landowner555: ^
Lourned: capitalism is bad when government is ran by capitalists
peter35_: the problem is cheap hyperpalatable foods
innerbean: capitalism has killed more people than religion...well, 'greed' has
Emanuell45: lmao
Ayyyy420Lmao: if capitallism so good why bad things happen?!?''1111'1'1
PiroFloydian: capitalism can be blamed for the people that stave bc theres more than enough food wasted for them. same with preventable medical deaths @georgehotz
tornpaperyoyos: @innerbean LUL
markydothh: Oh shit! Sup George!
AzazelTheGoat: does comma.ai have an underwear inside the pants policy?
robotboy987: doesn't capitalism mean less government workers
MrTriharder: Comparing anything to religion to win arguments DansGame
THX1342: the answer as usual is: it's complicated
Eternallightning: @pikomane2 that’s not a good thing
amedhussaini: capitalism provides incentives
Ayyyy420Lmao: if capitalism is so good why was i born so retarded to fall for socialist memes?
wheely_mcbones: thanks to medical sanitary revolution, not to capitalism
innerbean: is it an argument?
SpaceGhost8: *applies to comma ai*
innerbean: i discuss
AzazelTheGoat: soap
pikomane2: obamacare
aj37z: ^
PiroFloydian: tchnology
solitarynative: capitalism bad, me moral and good person
alextodoroki: lol does comma ai do internships
mikey9988: weed monkaS
tearisten68: He is taking the bait!
THX1342: penicilin
aj37z: thanks obama
THX1342: LUL
Emanuell45: capitalism = better technology = better health care = longer life
wheely_mcbones: compare life expectancy growth between US and China
SpaceGhost8: science
SpaceGhost8: bitch
vloood: i'm not a capitalism hater, but like mexico has the same lifespan and a tenth of the gdp lol
pikomane2: aliens
innerbean: technology has lengthened lives
Lourned: capitalism is doomed because you need to profit all the time and when there are no other place to profit it eats itself bro
Ayyyy420Lmao: if capitalism is so good why cant i get a gf?
Stegosaurian: MEDICINE & URBANIZATION increased life expectancy
koreanfoodyum: all capitalism is guilty of is using the 99% for the 1%
vloood: health has almost nothing to do with capitalism lol
PiroFloydian: smart people innovating irrespective of the profit motive @georgehotz
robotboy987: China did that
innerbean: technology built fortunes
neto3113: the will to be better and do better ?
braininavatt: bruh
vonhoganon: capitalism is life
monaliso: what are you drinking george
pec_adillo: capitalism cant kill as its an absence of violent restriction and coerced monopoly
pz3300: People don’t live any longer than they did 100 years agp
localcanofdutchgold: @vloood they buy the technology that you researched
asanti20: capitalism is an only fans
C0deCane: I think its amazing the problem is when corrupt people take advantage of it
alextodoroki: HOTZ does comma ai do internships
UniversalGeneve: hypercapitalism, like the USA, is a double edged sword.
robotboy987: china build technology
PiroFloydian: market socialism is a thing @georgehotz
Santiago_LHC: capitalism = free market
tearisten68: communism is better when done right, problem is it never can be done right
solitarynative: USA is not hyper capitalist wtf
mounnrocc: communism is impossible, really
Lourned: true
Stegosaurian: capitalism isn't sustainable in the long run
THX1342: the issue is centralization
Landowner555: the american dream is dead
mutrx: Law of Equivalent Exchange - fullmetal alchemist @georgehotz
un3okapi: @georgehotz leading cause of life is capitalism, but life always leads to death.
innerbean: capitalism is an ideology that values profit over any other consideration
wheely_mcbones: US is not most of the world
mounnrocc: who the fuck is gonna give up that amount of power for a stateless society
Parkpark1997: apple
pikomane2: yes go off king name the fed
ThirstyDrank: Transference of value, but based on industrialization. That comes at a price of environmental costs in long-term
innerbean: the market is not capritalism
AresRai: @tearisten68 maybe it will when robots are presidents instead
sigmund_graphics: :o
koreanfoodyum: what if you took the top 10 richest peoples money and gave it to the rest?
solitarynative: US is closer to a corporatocracy
wheely_mcbones: US is the exception of the world, the rule is India and China
markydothh: George! I promise i will subscribe once I make some money....the baby gets priority!
PiroFloydian: market socialism is a thing @georgehotz
amedhussaini: NIMBY
knilecrack: so they get value
pz3300: Denmark mortality rate 1918 = 10.1 Denmark mortality rate 2018 =9.8
Landepbs: the problem is monopolies
alextodoroki: m8 does comma ai do internships
williamjennings1: Lets be positive
mounnrocc: marxs critique is spot on. the solution not so much
360Plato: they would waste it
Ayyyy420Lmao: @PiroFloydian oxymorons are a thing yes
AzazelTheGoat: the problem is capitalism made things easy and a side effect was it made people lazy.
monaliso: is that wine george?
Santiago_LHC: That's the tendency of capitalism though. A broken system.
alwayxtoxic: you're so right
Stegosaurian: when you consider the ever increasing world population, capitalism isn't efficient when it comes to resource management
aj37z: we need better math teachers
wisamalrawi: What does San Francisco allow that stupid zoning to exist ?
vonhoganon: so true
PiroFloydian: @Ayyyy420Lmao no you just dont understand what socailism is lmao
ThirstyDrank: It's trickle-up economics
Ayyyy420Lmao: @PiroFloydian no u
THX1342: the 90% would buy shit made by the 10% and make the 10% rich again LUL
mounnrocc: absolutely
DecayingSkullz: BIIITCONNNEEEEEEEECCCCCTTTT
mounnrocc: LOCALISM BABY
C4TFive: A server wipe would be dope though
braininavatt: do you think billionaires should exist?
JdPaulBlart: give me my freedom dividend before i riot @georgehotz
THX1342: YES. decentralize
PiroFloydian: anarchosyndicalism is decentralization @georgehotz
vonhoganon: libertarian geohotz
MrTriharder: Bitcoin admiralJoy
logi6000: let's go something I believe in extremely
Lourned: solution is pay government employees better and hire smart people
AzazelTheGoat: is localism nationalism lite?
wheely_mcbones: decentralization is the reason US has more problems with Corona than China did
ThirstyDrank: Explain centralization and its issues plz
tkdboy555: @georgehotz how about universal basic income tied to inflation/quantitative easing, essentially preserving the buying power of every American, it can be implemented with blockchain, in fact it would be best implemented through blockchain
pz3300: Lazy people are lazy
wheely_mcbones: but is also a good thing
alicyka: anarchy means you get your socialist world, I get my capitalist world
360Plato: nah you need to centralize to compete with malevolent players
pikomane2: could u explain how blockchain would make rent seeking impossible?
pz3300: Yes
koreanfoodyum: very tru
innerbean: capitalism uses false scarcity and denying access for increase profits but if it becomes the top and often only priority it's corrupts a society
PiroFloydian: anarchosyndicalism is decentralization for gov @georgehotz
aj37z: Decentralize budget allocation
ankitc: truuu
wheely_mcbones: @PiroFloydian yeah
tkdboy555: UBI IMPLEMENTED VIA BLOCKCHAIN
solitarynative: @innerbean brainlet take
pz3300: Reddit sucks dick
ahahahaitslit: take a hit
PiroFloydian: take out profit motive of healthcare w/ M4a @georgehotz
fartdog2009: hey, i think that this might help.
williamjennings1: we just need to meditate brah
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz Thoughts on "Social Democracy" ?
dorkmo: i so badly want to go to waffle house
The1theycallmonk: George is speaking the truth tonight!
wheely_mcbones: why is so expensive? political lobby pretty much
whyZaya: Poor people care.
amedhussaini: the question is.. what is the quickest path to a post scarcity economy?
tkdboy555: NO
alfyfav: Omg this live keeps up
Lourned: $350 for STD test bro, 350 fucking dollars
The1theycallmonk: Healthcare is too expensive. Spreading the cost isn't the solution
un3okapi: why not decentralize the schooling system?
wheely_mcbones: but free market results in a lot of Shrkrellis
robotboy987: Google is bad because all this big websites have good seo
bluejimmy168: 600 dollars for a healthy adult to get insurance iin my state is dumb.
aj37z: @dorkmo capitalism
innerbean: it's not about a binary between capitalism and socialism, either extreme is unbalanced.
tkdboy555: I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT YANG'S VERSION OF UBI BUD
360Plato: @wheely_mcbones thats a bad thinbg?
AzazelTheGoat: houses shouldn't be as expensive as they are.
mattdougherty22: atoms is harder than bits, that's where we need to focus even more.
tkdboy555: I'M TALKING ABOUT UBI TIED TO QUNATITATIVE EASING AND INFLATION
PiroFloydian: innovation happens irrespective of the profit motive @georgehotz
THX1342: georgehotz I am all for decentralization but I always get hanged on 'big projects'... like moon landings... who tackles them?
C0deCane: @georgehotz LUL show these people poverty in america compared to poverty in other "great" places in the world with socialism ahahha
AzazelTheGoat: I work full time and am struggling to get a house. it literally makes no sense
wheely_mcbones: @360Plato yeah
dorkmo: robots
pikomane2: thats that colonizer mentality
logi6000: truth
Emanuell45: its not about bringing the top down its about bringing the bottom up
ThirstyDrank: Yes, but that's at the cost of the environment again
wheely_mcbones: things are cheap because we made education universal, not because of capitalism or free market
mutrx: bernie2020,24,28,32!!!!!
jomkingal: Hi George! Sorry off topic but greetings from NJ!
boengels: but increasing the economy also seems to destroy the natural world...
pec_adillo: IP is bull
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz What about its impact on scciety and the way it affects people ?
koreanfoodyum: LOL LIMEWIRE
AzazelTheGoat: is apple a metaphor for... apple?
mattdougherty22: what do you think of Income Share Agreements versus student loans to help keep schools accountable?
innerbean: i hate sounding like this but it's about the distribution of the total wealth
C4TFive: George Shapiro LUL
gamerguy009: Dont pay hockey players so much
PiroFloydian: anarchosyndicalism is what youre looking for @georgehotz
gazny: We need an opensource society
dprophecyguy: You can create wealth but nobody is giving a fuck how it's fucking up with the environment
koreanfoodyum: do what you want cause a pirate is free, cause you are a pirate!
wheely_mcbones: this is true, information should be free
latenightbj: whos the guy with the gun ?
dorkmo: but but open source 3d printed guns
theonlymonkas: i like how this guy thinks
THX1342: georgehotz I am all for decentralization but I always get hanged on 'big projects'... like moon landings... who tackles them? Twitch Prime
SofiaLouise: dont you thinks patents are important?
dprophecyguy: This graph doesn't talk about environment impact
360Plato: ok IP law is necessary to incentivize research
wheely_mcbones: this graph happened because education became universal
opus_000: cash flow
Parkpark1997: :d
knilecrack: how can you like capitalism and then talk about IP like that ?
alfyfav: To end poverty you don't have to end richness
dsqst: The graph is distribution
AzazelTheGoat: hockey players provide a service, and it's something i couldn't do so the value is there for them to get paid a lotr
innerbean: that's exactly my point, thanks for making it so clearly.....hehe
mutrx: giraffe extinction solved extreme poverty confirmed
l1ght5p33d: This is my garden and i like it except the chain link fences those suck
tkdboy555: SO WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THE FEDERAL RESERVE?
24786d: Just change the definition of poverty EZ
Penguino138: Preach @georgehotz
edeustua: how would you deal with rent seeking via blockchain?
Lourned: define extreme poverty Kappa
innerbean: we can keep printing money but it keeps going into fewer and fewer hands
dsqst: There are many who have nothing and it’s not artificial to them
vonhoganon: just remove it 4Head
AzazelTheGoat: HUNTER GATHERING TIMES BOYS
theonlymonkas: Nice book! any other recommendation?
C0deCane: Im telling you compare the poverty in America to the poverty in other countries they are way way worse off
Emanuell45: lmao
dingus74: lol
sigmund_graphics: lol
williamjennings1: u lived in the woods?
markydothh: The problem is that the system is RIGGED b/c politics is CORRUPT. Lobbyist, big corporates, these fking policitans are CORRUPT!
EXSNarrow: LMAO
localcanofdutchgold: 3 lul
braininavatt: three?
braininavatt: more like two
Lourned: LUL
wheely_mcbones: @C0deCane compared to sweeden, japan or scotlan? are you kidding?
EquiFox: best content on twitch rn
dorkmo: extreme poverty = nyc in the time of coronavirus
logi6000: wait a minute this mother fucker just said he tried to live in the woods
ankitc: as a software developer i earn less then 400 dollars a month
tkdboy555: DOES THIS TAKE INTO ACCOUNT INFLATION. I'M GUESSING NOT
C0deCane: compare it to a super power @wheely_mcbones
mutrx: 2.0 per day gang 🦀 🦀 🦀 🦀 🦀 🦀 🦀
360Plato: so tree fiddy is a lot
innerbean: distribute the power equally not based on capital as the highest value, it's about people, we the people, not the capital
DecayingSkullz: Geohot should write a book
dprophecyguy: @ankitc get a good job man
jomkingal: We are programmed from birth. To be dependent on these things that we were taught that we need.
Emanuell45: @ankitc wtf, where do you live?
AresRai: @ankitc what country curious
Ayyyy420Lmao: obviously yes
Lourned: @georgehotz so $2 is not extreme poverty? LUL
wheely_mcbones: @C0deCane you don't have any 1st world big country
ankitc: Nepal
tkdboy555: lmfao, but what the REAL value of inflation
mutrx: it says adjusted for inflation @georgehotz
tkdboy555: these numbers are busted
jimmyadaro: Sup
foti_kasparov: @ankitc Makes sense
boengels: what is extreme poverty
Emanuell45: @AresRai must be 2nd or third world
knilecrack: for 2$ daily you can have one pljeskavic per day
MrTriharder: @ankitc Just move to India
innerbean: and sex...can;t forget about that. hehe
alicyka: Government is just an HR department / middle management for humanity, fuck it
rorhug: Call someone you trust to discuss
AresRai: @Emanuell45 2.5 LUL
AzazelTheGoat: but is there quality of life any good?
markydothh: Thats b/c of CHINA
wheely_mcbones: @C0deCane you can't compare it to 3rd world countries because of story, imperialism and stuff
AzazelTheGoat: their*
whyZaya: pljeskavics should be illegal.
dorkmo: and look at a population growth chart too
knilecrack: it's because of 2nd WW
HellxNebula: ppl who starved died before reprodtuce and the most wealthy survived and it goes on thats way
gamerguy009: Cant survive on minimum wage
markydothh: CHINA's ascent has probably accounted for half of the 40%
dorkmo: adding people
logi6000: but now the real question is how do we get out of the simulation
mattdougherty22: what smart people do you interact with most? Those at comma?
appreciation1: @tkdboy555 just think what a poor poerson has today vs what a miner had in 1850 in a "first world country" it does take infaltion into account
Emanuell45: @AresRai LUL LUL
innerbean: yes, very good.....because of technology
knilecrack: it's good that USA was not destroyed in WW2 otherwise EU would come back now on it's feet
innerbean: the market created that
Ayyyy420Lmao: @mattdougherty22 us the twitch chat chads
williamjennings1: dang
amedhussaini: the chinese market reforms started at around that time
amedhussaini: early 80s
Stegosaurian: the world's economy is based on a broken financial system
C0deCane: @wheely_mcbones japan is not a super power i was speaking more about china russia they poverty in those countries is far worse off then the poverty in america even the rural areas in america are way way better off
koreanfoodyum: isn't china full of starving people? that's why they have the wet markets that had the bat which transmitted corona? isn't that extreme poverty? :o
Emanuell45: you can say what you want about the chinnese, but they do good things for their countries population
mattdougherty22: hahah sadly not @Ayyyy420Lmao look at your name. We are watching him
solitarynative: ANELE Clap
markydothh: India?
360Plato: they dont have the culture
markydothh: NO
PiroFloydian: @koreanfoodyum wet markets are a rich people thing
aMANT3: !time
jimmyadaro: @Stegosaurian What??
Jehhred: no wonder the chinese are so sringy
rorhug: Call someone. Bring a guest onto the show and discuss this.
wheely_mcbones: @C0deCane you are ignoring world history behind that
AzazelTheGoat: I dont trust stats provided by the CCP. im biased. or is a third party getting this info
THX1342: look at braizl
koreanfoodyum: weird rich people then
noobaj: all lockdown
williamjennings1: !time
tkdboy555: @appreciation1 except they actually knew how to grow their own shit in their backyard, but instead, now we just have hyper-green grass for our dogs
SofiaLouise: it has slowed down with modi
markydothh: India wont have the same ascent that CHINA had
MrTriharder: @georgehotz I am from India. Economy is crumbling a bit :)
PiroFloydian: @koreanfoodyum yes
Kawhiet: China -> India -> Africa
gamerguy009: North Korea is starving
mutrx: @georgehotz can you speak chinese
Ayyyy420Lmao: @mattdougherty22 i just smoke weed to lower my iq from 180 to 140
dprophecyguy: India only few cities are in good position
aj37z: 4head
t_lokus: extreme poverty is really very poor metric of global economy, it's just a very basic measurement that has so many problems.. it's like the chapter 1 in economics and dropped so fast, there are a lot of arguments on why is so weak metric
ThirstyDrank: China has super cheap food
innerbean: profit can be a motive for it, if it's the only and top motive it corrupts the system.
koreanfoodyum: nk is def starving
tornpaperyoyos: Why did you spend a year in china?
dprophecyguy: Nobody is starving in india also
aj37z: 4Head
tsAllySparkles: you spent a year of your life in cities
opus_000: they can't produce enough food
ThirstyDrank: but comparably, healthier but less caloric than ours
tsAllySparkles: try going around rural china
C0deCane: @wheely_mcbones thats the point why capitalism is better if it wasn't it wouldn't be that way in those countries simple as that
foti_kasparov: Having 1b population is hard
MrTriharder: Only Mumbai Bangalore Hyderabad chennai is good in India @georgehotz
DecayingSkullz: @architectzs if you ask about that you'll get timed out
mattdougherty22: @Ayyyy420Lmao same, how old are you? What do you do for a living?
wheely_mcbones: @C0deCane this is not because of capitalism, is because of universalizing education in the last century
24786d: You're likely attributing correlation to causation. I like to think we're in a period of peace and stability, which really helped
Ayyyy420Lmao: @mattdougherty22 im a 35 years old neet living on government housing and welfare
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz In India the standard of living is pretty bad. People do not care about how they live like they are used to being oppresses it seems
ThirstyDrank: what about their dystopian app social rating
DecayingSkullz: @architectzs everyone asks about that
joker2k999: damn. talks getting deep.
l1ght5p33d: no
SpaceGhost8: right, it's state controlled but its really not all that different fundamentally
wheely_mcbones: @C0deCane you have more capitalism in US than you have in Germany or Sweden
dorkmo: visit a reducation camp :P
C0deCane: @wheely_mcbones what the hell does that have to do with the how life is in poverty areas in america and in china
wheely_mcbones: @C0deCane still they have better living conditions
koreanfoodyum: that's what I'd hope, in private, even a communist reign wouldn't keep you from shit talking winne the pooh :D
innerbean: eh, there's some issues for sure but different than the ones in the west
MrTriharder: Wuhan monkaS
mattdougherty22: @Ayyyy420Lmao how did you come across geo?
jimmyadaro: What about Africa?
mattdougherty22: lol im 20
markydothh: How's your mandarin? Talk some dirty Mando to me.
appreciation1: @tkdboy555 you are shifting the goalpoasts now. Also you are free to grow your own stuff alnd is very cheap in the rural areas especially in poorer countries you need around 2 baseball fields of land for 1 person to live off of
logi6000: George have you read Fahrenheit 451
AzazelTheGoat: thats interesting
williamjennings1: 9times
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz And also in india lot of people relate politics with religion and they also associate their politician with god like figures
ThirstyDrank: They have starvation during droughts
innerbean: east and west both have their issues
C0deCane: @wheely_mcbones LUL dude
AzazelTheGoat: i guess the same is here in canada. The reservations can look pretty depressing when driving through
robotboy987: India has more "linear" segment of economy eg. farmers
architectzs: can i not be curious?
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz Currently in india the PM is like god to more than half of the country
mattdougherty22: what smart people do you interact with most? Those at comma?
theonlymonkas: have you been on latin america?
Lourned: if starvation was every a problem in the world population would decrease not increase, no?
DecayingSkullz: @architectzs no you can't
PiroFloydian: what book were you talking about earlier?
architectzs: explain?
THX1342: India is going on a baaad road...
Ayyyy420Lmao: @mattdougherty22 i know about him since the iphone thing, youtube recomends shit about him sometimes
brownyyyylocks: India is beautiful!
mattdougherty22: Peter Thiel all about not declining @georgehotz
theonlymonkas: permutation city
innerbean: what if the mic on their phone catches it and webo records it? boom....busted hehehe
gamerguy009: Canada is good
wheely_mcbones: @C0deCane US is better than China, but is not because of capitalism
360Plato: @brownyyyylocks you should travel more
williamjennings1: stock market is scary
Kawhiet: Why do you think the emoji is like that?
mutrx: @architectzs scroll down to see the rules, keyboard = timeout
alicyka: There's nothing sadder than a beautifully built house covered in mold, hidden behind 4 feet of grass
MrTriharder: @georgehotz if u come To Mumbai, I’ll show u around. No indian will be able to scan u with foreign prices :)
gamerguy009: Geohotz move to Canada
C0deCane: the rural america i live in is better now than it was 4 years ago
Lourned: cant exploit China any more, they are getting rich now FeelsBadMan
AzazelTheGoat: i think victim mentality is a major poison on a culture
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz You won't find more welcoming people anywhere in the world than in India.
tkdboy555: @georgehotz @appreciation1 IN THE 1800S, 90% of the american population lived on farms. At least back then we actually grew our own shit. This whole poverty thing is relative because we are ascribing wealth to a monetary metric, instead of actually material possession. The entire philosophy of this metric is busted http://jaysonlusk.com/blog/2016/6/26/the-evolution-of-american-agriculture
architectzs: do people really ask that much lmao
PiroFloydian: when the market goes up it doesnt help most people. when it goes down they all suffer @georgehotz
DecayingSkullz: @architectzs yes
mutrx: @architectzs yep
opus_000: stock market is basically gambling
DecayingSkullz: @architectzs scroll down and read the only rule of this channel
solitarynative: what states are you talking about?
martinkirilov: everyone is so used to the stock market going up, most people buy in expecting to make money overnight. you should expect to lose, hope to win
jimmyadaro: @opus_000 Hell na
architectzs: thats interestinmg
rorhug: Call someone George - bring a guest onto the show to discuss.
brownyyyylocks: @dprophecyguy Which parts of India have you been to?
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz You should live in India for some time not just visit India. Talk with people and maybe can start a university here. There are way more talented people here than USA but with no guidance
wheely_mcbones: The world can't consume as much as America do, the problem with capitalism is in the wealth distribution around the world not around america
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you speak any foreing languages?
tsAllySparkles: what interstate
jimmyadaro: @wheely_mcbones Shut the fuck up with your communist shit lmao
ThirstyDrank: Do you think deregulating would help stimulate the economy, like with weed
360Plato: you should visit the caucuses
Lourned: what country is the US and friends going to exploit next for cheap labor?
mattdougherty22: any podcast fans able to give me feedback on this episode format? http://mattdougherty.online/Podscribe-mock/test/test2
wheely_mcbones: @jimmyadaro I'm not wrong tough
dprophecyguy: @brownyyyylocks I am from India
tornpaperyoyos: @wheely_mcbones you are though
jimmyadaro: @wheely_mcbones Hell yeah you're
joker2k999: any crazy Bangkok stories? LUL
brownyyyylocks: LOL.
koreanfoodyum: AMERICA, FUCK YEAH!
tkdboy555: LITERALLY 90% OF AMERICANS LIVED ON FARMS IN THE 1800s, NOW ITS 2%, PLEASE DON'T RELATE POVERTY TO MONETARY ACCUMULATION.
ahahahaitslit: USA!!!!!!!!
solitarynative: Is adderal the best way to stimulate the economy?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @wheely_mcbones cant be wrong if i say im not wrong, smart move!
AzazelTheGoat: haven't you seen crazy rich asians?
rndmsqnce: where in california is truly rural?
C0deCane: LUL you can become a billionaire in china overnight if you come out with a hit product
innerbean: they catching up
jimmyadaro: Capitalism has took out the 90% of population from poverty, what the fuck man
Belowzer0w: We need a graph for happiness. Does happiness and wealth correlate? I mean if you have more than food and water, how does this reflect in happiness?
vonhoganon: @rndmsqnce riverside
PiroFloydian: @rndmsqnce eastern i think
jimmyadaro: @Belowzer0w Will create some kind of Kuznets curve
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz Do you care about nationality?
MrTriharder: @georgehotz America Iceland Russia and kazakstan consume the highest fossil fuels in the world per capita
HellxNebula: sweet data
360Plato: @solitarynative speed used to be over the counter
amedhussaini: california is very rural outside of sf/la/san diego
ThirstyDrank: I think a big problem now is that people are pushed on depending on others to distribute value, rather than producing
innerbean: probably more consumers worldwide than in NA
AzazelTheGoat: my parents grew up on a farm, i grew up in a comfy house with central heating. its crazy
THX1342: any graph showing % of americans that are home owners vs rent?
appreciation1: @tkdboy555 I get that. My problem with that argument is that farming is a grueling and backbreaking task and i'd rather go and live in a moderately big city and do my office job. and most people tend to agree with me because most people live in cities instead of homesteading which is definitly possible in todays world in most moderatly rich countries. also specialization makes the same lands yield more food so the best farmers make more food for all of us. famring is a skill.
boengels: no
opus_000: heroin
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz Happiness Index
moonwalker15: No, it does not
AzazelTheGoat: happiness to me is security
tornpaperyoyos: @MrTriharder how tf is iceland on that list
foti_kasparov: OMG indians just blasted in the chat
wheely_mcbones: good point.
solitarynative: @360Plato damn lol
dprophecyguy: Search for happiness index
mutrx: look at all the celebrities who are crying bc of quarantine in their mansions @georgehotz
vonhoganon: money = happiness
C0deCane: There is definitely an algorithm for happiness im sure
Ayyyy420Lmao: ofc it subjective so u just ask ppl 'are u happy m8?'
Lourned: west virgina PogChamp
innerbean: my pants
MrTriharder: Just make Finland as the winner for happiness :) admiralJoy
theonlymonkas: no
rndmsqnce: state of jefferson?
innerbean: was that wrong? sorry
dprophecyguy: There is official happiness index
tkdboy555: @appreciation1 the entire point is the poverty metric he used is bullshit. people in extreme poverty back then were well fed as fuck, no cap
joker2k999: acceptance, laughter, arguing w/ a friend and winning, and having a few bucks in the bank
innerbean: it's in the declaration of independence
martinkirilov: "Happiness is your biggest enemy. It weakens you. Puts doubts in your mind. Suddenly you have something to lose!" - Rush BibleThump
DecayingSkullz: How do you think we should measure intelligence?
innerbean: pursuit of it
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/World_Happiness_Report Check this out
Hawklite: happiness simply means one's expectations or desires are being met
ahahahaitslit: will you ever write a book
opus_000: happiness is perspective
Ayyyy420Lmao: @Hawklite what if u have no expectations or desires?
The_Troll_Toll: i lived in SF (retreated to a bunker a month ago) and know ppl who lived with you at the crypto castle
jimmyadaro: @Hawklite That changes all the time
innerbean: the constitution is to promote general welfare? how to measure that?
tkdboy555: @appreciation1 life was food
appreciation1: @tkdboy555 oh I agree that it's bs. Bad measure of poverty. better measure would be imo. What did the emperor of china have vs the average poor person today
360Plato: I think fufillment is more important. I much rather be Russian then German
Lourned: happiness is relative
Hawklite: @jimmyadaro so then when it changes and your expectations/desires aren't met, then you aren't happpy
gaocaandra: did you check out weinstein
dprophecyguy: Checkout happiness index. Top 5 Countries are scandinavian
AzazelTheGoat: they were too tired to think about trivial shit like that
The_Troll_Toll: ted kacynzski bro
innerbean: i like happiness....haha
C0deCane: Get back on coronavirus LUL
HellxNebula: hapiness is all about perception
Ayyyy420Lmao: @360Plato i'd rather not exist than be german or rusian
sigmund_graphics: Possibly happier to have something ot do
solitarynative: physical pain give you purpose and meaning bro
Belowzer0w: Working with your body is satisfying
innerbean: joy is better
tkdboy555: @appreciation1 yes, wealth inequality should be extremely relevant to the metric but it isn't
boengels: George have you ever seen this??! https://mynoise.net/NoiseMachines/cafeRestaurantNoiseGenerator.php?fbclid=IwAR1f5EQ9Zov7PHukgYq6DnPvw-8zbDUz8Dan0eJ1RfuADDYgm4ZRaGsftmg
Emanuell45: no dude
boengels: perfect for study time :D
innerbean: fulfillment is the bomb
Ayyyy420Lmao: nope
The_Troll_Toll: think of all the pussy you'd get
Ayyyy420Lmao: fuck social score and shit like taht
AresRai: no dude emperor in china had 3000 wives @georgehotz
martinkirilov: You can't measure happiness, everyone has their own concept of it
The_Troll_Toll: the armies you could command
THX1342: think about all the sick parties tho
innerbean: at peace is divine
360Plato: @Ayyyy420Lmao St Petersburg is comfy
un3okapi: getting pegged is painful
boengels: cafe noise generator
appreciation1: @tkdboy555 when was the last time some1 died because of a bad harvest in america? happend all the time when 90% of the population was farming
C4TFive: kings could use people as toilet paper though
innerbean: hehehe,,, how much to buy it?
mutrx: im annoyed i won't be able to witness the crazy shit that's going to happen in the future @georgehotz
Emanuell45: the social status of a king would be way better than slaving away at a apple sweat shop
localcanofdutchgold: forsenCD
AzazelTheGoat: thoughts on ending the welfare state? @georgehotz
pz3300: They shore were healthier
tsAllySparkles: if you were a king in 1600 you'd go to war with the land of sony
solitarynative: forsenCD nice
AresRai: concubines
joker2k999: Damn. but those castle's tho bro...
innerbean: not physical pain....psychological suffering...self suffering, that's the difference
HellxNebula: why the hell you want 3k wives one is enough
HellxNebula: xd
C4TFive: 3000 waifu's maybe
jimmyadaro: LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: gengis khan fucked like 20k thots
appreciation1: @georgehotz emporor of china had 20 different foods to chose from I have more with takeout
murkythunder: for hotz 3k is chump change
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz Not at once I hope
dorkmo: in one afternoon on tinder
aj37z: chad
innerbean: yup
C0deCane: LUL thats Viagras roots
joker2k999: LUL
AzazelTheGoat: lol
dprophecyguy: @georgehotz How many sex partners you are aiming for ?
mashafique: The Hotz Harem LUL
360Plato: Welfare is a practical necessity at this point
mutrx: @dorkmo maybe for women :(
doctorgenus: how many sex partners do you have?
Emanuell45: if you end the welfare state, crime is going to go through the roof
logi6000: @hellxnebula one just didn't cut it for that Chinese emperor
brownyyyylocks: 3k do you know what women are like??
AzazelTheGoat: @Emanuell45 thats true
PiroFloydian: hell yeah
Snobbysteven: only 3k? pft, that's just a Tuesday night....
ooMariaoo: loll
Ayyyy420Lmao: sex yikes
braininavatt: it's gonna be sick! (literally)
pz3300: What, you don’t have 3k bitches?
SpaceGhost8: fuck coronavirus lets do that
localcanofdutchgold: this guy
tkdboy555: hahahahah
brownyyyylocks: ewwwwww
C0deCane: how many kids do you think he had?
HellxNebula: @logi6000 i guess he could throw her somewhere when to blabla began
THX1342: that's good stream content: hacking STDs
innerbean: I've found things in a dumpster that kings of the past couldn't cream of
robotboy987: fucking alimony for 3k wives
doctorgenus: can we do that for the next stream?
dorkmo: 10 a day for a year
brownyyyylocks: gross
ooMariaoo: relax lol @TeaLeafi
foti_kasparov: @TeaLeafi Are you really that interested dude
solitarynative: I'm halfway there :)
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: COOMING every day
fyezool: lend me some of your power george
l1ght5p33d: all about selectivity
360Plato: I mean over 20 years once ever 1.5 days
brownyyyylocks: 3
koreanfoodyum: set your goals high, go for 3.5 billion! ^-^
davidvilla700: by order of the peaky fuckin blinders
murkythunder: u a virgin bro ?
pz3300: You luuuv politics george
bufferovrflw: I don't think most of the 3k weren't voluntary sex partners
braininavatt: comma.bio
jimmyadaro: You eliminate welfare, you create The Purge… Boom, no poverty, no crime, no shit LUL
joker2k999: ..give or take huh..
THX1342: cure aids, instant king
theonlymonkas: LUL
doctorgenus: would u have sex with a sexy robot?!!!!!!
shieeeeeeeeet: what is the path from reverse engineering covid-19 to curing it?
Jehhred: Less than 3,000. big surprise there
appreciation1: @tkdboy555 we agree when it comes to the problems I think.
SpaceGhost8: LUL
AzazelTheGoat: can't cure aids, more money in the treatment than the cure
jimmyadaro: It's taken
innerbean: obonervirus
alicyka: Oh here's a question: What project would you want to work on if there was no government threatening you? Still what you're doing now?
braininavatt: no if I buy it first Kappa
MrTriharder: @tealeafi Cause u suffer from autism
C0deCane: ez
latenightbj: comma.xxx
logi6000: do you believe in ai girlfriends
koreanfoodyum: comma.tv
dorkmo: epic domain grabbbb
phrixus_bro: too late
opus_000: lol
solitarynative: TriHard yoink
THX1342: LUL
jimmyadaro: You eliminate welfare, you create The Purge… Boom, no poverty, no crime, no shit LUL
localcanofdutchgold: Kapp
bluejimmy168: Yoinked
pz3300: I’m on about 1000 now
theonlymonkas: but how many of them were humans?
SpaceGhost8: mine now :)
Ayyyy420Lmao: shit i was searching for my CC already
mattdougherty22: just bought it bub
braininavatt: comma.xyz
bluejimmy168: mine now :)
foti_kasparov: comma.gov
tkdboy555: how about artificial sentience?
360Plato: eugenic bear fighting
Lourned: he works for the government Kappa
brownyyyylocks: oh its q&a time
AzazelTheGoat: blink twice if you're not safe george
koreanfoodyum: comma.edu
pz3300: About 200 civilians and 800 hookers
doctorgenus: if sony didn't sue you, would you be doing what you're doing today?
Santiago_LHC: comma.vaio
squiggly_nibba: how's your other company
brownyyyylocks: i love q&a time!!
tornpaperyoyos: I already bought it
logi6000: do you believe in ai girlfriends
koreanfoodyum: comma.darpa
mattdougherty22: ill sell it for an autograph
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz Thoughts on disinformation campaings on Social Media? Any idea what we could do to solve it?
l1ght5p33d: good stream
THX1342: how many times have you stopped to think "how can I exploit the system?"
edeustua: thoughts on Chris Arnade
dorkmo: have you seen the movie HER?
1monkjuice: would you accept an offer from the army?
edeustua: ?
Hawklite: what set of beliefs are you going to push in your university?
ahahahaitslit: have you used ocaml
pz3300: You buy it off me
Ayyyy420Lmao: can jet fuel melt steel beams?
braininavatt: do you have any sony devices?
solitarynative: do you like cbt?
Abnico: how is your weighted blanket?
koreanfoodyum: comma.ngo would mean u ain't a suit :O
phrixus_bro: yaas
PiroFloydian: true
AzazelTheGoat: spooky.
THX1342: why do people use social media to inform themselves anyway....
pz3300: That’s what you think
tornpaperyoyos: Are you gonna DESTROY the coronavirus with FACTS and LOGIC????
mutrx: are you going to try sous vide @georgehotz
SpaceGhost8: cbd CiGrip
dorkmo: continual variable transmission
pz3300: Lol
Lourned: edgy news are fun LUL
rsten: cock and ball toture moon2MD
latenightbj: twitch included as smc
solitarynative: yes cbt
localcanofdutchgold: cbt the other one
PiroFloydian: cbt is also cock and ball torture i think @georgehotz ?
pwnbase: cock and ball torture
JdPaulBlart: cbt as in cock and ball torture
DecayingSkullz: That's not what he meant by CBT....
innerbean: both rock
SpaceGhost8: ALL IN ACB stockMoon
jimmyadaro: ARE YOU WASHING YOUR GODDAMN HANDS GEORGE?
doctorgenus: what pills do you take everyday beside zinc?
pz3300: Is it worth taking cs50 course on edx online?
Piqcyl: ELI5 past streams? Are you modelling it genetically? Or are you simulating its formation orrrrrr
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz Well, yeah, but the disinformation campaings are the side-effects of those optimalizations
MrTriharder: @georgehotz government is passing a bill to remove encryption DansGame
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you have a pepe the frog image collection??
SpaceGhost8: LUL
ICAntF331MyFAce: LUL
shieeeeeeeeet: what is the path from reverse engineering covid-19 to curing it?
braininavatt: LUL
AzazelTheGoat: show feet
rndmsqnce: hows you coronavirus love life
Santiago_LHC: Come on you guys!
braininavatt: do better chat
solitarynative: sorry guys
bluejimmy168: lol
guy_ross: i tried the hype train
logi6000: no better quality
brownyyyylocks: When all this is over I cant wait to go to Bondi Beach!!!
localcanofdutchgold: read any good math book?
jimmyadaro: Eat garlic George, and raw onions mf
dorkmo: chooooooooooo
Belowzer0w: I love you bye
joker2k999: lol
bluejimmy168: Show feet
HellxNebula: what language you recommend for a beginner
haircutjimmy: what are Microsoft doing with ai?
pz3300: Both
Santiago_LHC: Engage intellect!
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: is there a discord for the twitch channel?
THX1342: georgehotz if you had one space ticket to anywhere, what body would you go to?
mashafique: Any plans to do any physics oriented streams? @georgehotz
onichJu: @georgehotz have u found out something interesting while i been gone for the last 3 days?
tkdboy555: @georgehotz one day I'm gonna start a company to develop artificially sentient super-intelligence, wanna contribute?
theonlymonkas: what book are you reading right now?
koreanfoodyum: ~/fun/corona oh...
Ayyyy420Lmao: can you recomend me a good porno scene gerorge?
l1ght5p33d: I sent my solution about the commai Speed Challenge can you look at it it sucks
jimmyadaro: The opposite to "Microsoft" is "Macrohard"
DecayingSkullz: HYPE TRAIN
boengels: Time to go to work anyway. Thanks for your thoughts George
opus_000: is groovy worth learning for ml
ParaLizard: Any opinionated advice for a CS undergrad?
Emanuell45: @georgehotz how do you keep motivated when solving hour long probelms
innerbean: how would you attack it?
doctorgenus: if I do all the leetcode problems, will you give me a job at comma?
ICAntF331MyFAce: get hype VoHiYo
AzazelTheGoat: can you find the cure for flat feet? i desperately need arches george.
wheely_mcbones: learned a lot today
PiroFloydian: Scam train?
EquiFox: do you get a lot of custom car port request for comma ?
Lourned: i love corona virus, no more traffic, no more lines, love it
yousodead: are you poor begging for bits
noclip32: Cheer1 Cheer1
dorkmo: Party1 Party1 Party1
solitarynative: PogChamp
64pillars: do you have an artistic ability?
DecayingSkullz: Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa
Emanuell45: @georgehotz how do you keep motivated when solving hour long probelms. ,
UniversalGeneve: @georgehotz watch this offline, good visualizations of DNA replication processes: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Hk9jct2ozY
dingus74: jackoo1Weird_SG
l1ght5p33d: whats your favorite movie
abdcw: what is the minimum amount of money one needs to be paid to suck dick where it isn't gay?
tkdboy555: @georgehotz one day I'm gonna start a company to develop artificially sentient super-intelligence, wanna contribute?
jimmyadaro: Have you ever been scamed (online or not)??
localcanofdutchgold: which ones do you not answer?
logi6000: me is broke boi
Abnico: thoughts on scale ai?
Emanuell45: @georgehotz how do you keep motivated when solving hour long probelms...
ICAntF331MyFAce: VoHiYo1 VoHiYo1 VoHiYo1
onichJu: LUL
koreanfoodyum: PrideCheers PrideLionYay PrideLionYay PrideLionYay PrideLionYay PrideCheers
innerbean: how would you attack covid?
brownyyyylocks: twitchies revolt!!!!!!!
l1ght5p33d: favorite food
THX1342: LUL
jimmyadaro: Have you ever been scamed (online or not)?
foti_kasparov: GOOOO SCAAAM TRAAAAAINNNNN CHOO CHOO cbrahTune cbrahTune
theonlymonkas: LUL
onichJu: you really are the ultimate capitalist @georgehotz
doctorgenus: why is your grocery bags still out?
THX1342: S C A M
dingus74: ResidentSleeper
Ayyyy420Lmao: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
FerFap: Gearge you should check WORLDOMETERS for the coronavirus they have lots of good grphs for each country .
shieeeeeeeeet: *crickets*
DecayingSkullz: CHOOOOOO CHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
Abnico: scale ai
ahahahaitslit: how do you get a hype train
ooMariaoo: oh
mashafique: Professional scam trainner LUL
privacyisnowhere: how many times do you beat the meat per day?
l1ght5p33d: best country
jimmyadaro: :LUL:
Penguino138: LETS GOOOOO
Landowner555: @jimmyadaro yes i have, right now
mutrx: CHOOOO CHOOOOOO
logi6000: well
jimmyadaro: LUL
HellxNebula: @georgehotz what language you recommend for a beginner and how to evolve
joker2k999: too much pressure LUL
ankitc: CHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
Abnico: scale ai yo
jimmyadaro: Have you ever been scamed (online or not)?
martinkirilov: Damn, selling out again, I see @georgehotz
yaus_baus: its a scam
ankitc: CHOOOOO
theonlymonkas: choooo chooooooo
alicyka: George is threatening to withhold his intellectual property in exchange for money
kyxstreams: hypeee
doctorgenus: is there milk in those bags?!!!
PiroFloydian: I'm poor someone else do it!
ICAntF331MyFAce: Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1
yaus_baus: dont do it
ahahahaitslit: how the fuck do you get a hype train
mikey9988: YEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEET
ooMariaoo: guys D:
jimmyadaro: Have you ever been scamed (online or not)??
ankitc: CHOOOO
tsAllySparkles: ok boomer
THX1342: s E L L o u T
mutrx: POGUUUU
dorkmo: choooooooooooo chooooooooooooooo
Piqcyl: CHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
DecayingSkullz: TRAIN
SpaceGhost8: bye george
localcanofdutchgold: no one wants to be scammed
onichJu: damn
koreanfoodyum: MrDestructoid MrDestructoid MrDestructoi
tkdboy555: sorry im poor af
opus_000: what's your social security #?
happypuppppy: nooo
AzazelTheGoat: how do you make a hype train?
jimmyadaro: Have you ever been scamed (online or not)?
theonlymonkas: LUL LUL
yaus_baus: scam
Ayyyy420Lmao: SCAMMED
logi6000: choooo
tornpaperyoyos: How does one hype train
doctorgenus: what do you mean by hype train?
C0deCane: stupid train LUL
jimmyadaro: goddamn it
64pillars: PepeHands
HellxNebula: @georgehotz what language you recommend for a beginner and how to evolve!
ankitc: CHOOOOOOOOOO
theonlymonkas: :(
Abnico: OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog
l1ght5p33d: best stream
brownyyyylocks: boooooo u whore
jimmyadaro: Have you ever been scamed (online or not)??
phrixus_bro: thanks for streaming
mikey9988: Jebaited
latenightbj: <3
happypuppppy: BibleThump
braininavatt: SwiftRage you suck chat
UniversalGeneve: UniversalGeneve is gifting 2 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 10 in the channel!
UniversalGeneve: UniversalGeneve gifted a Tier 1 sub to theonlymonkas!
UniversalGeneve: UniversalGeneve gifted a Tier 1 sub to williamjennings1!
jimmyadaro: Have you ever been scamed (online or not)?
l1ght5p33d: BEST STREAM 1000X FOREVER
MrTriharder: DansGame DansGame DansGame
braininavatt: too late Jebaited
doctorgenus: did you watch lex yesterday?
UniversalGeneve: damn, that usually starts it
Penguino138: @georgehotz Thanks again for the streams, keep on going and keeping us calm
ahahahaitslit: allahu akbar
onichJu: LUL
EquiFox: do you get a lot of car port request for comma ?
theonlymonkas: ¡@UniversalGeneve thanks!
jimmyadaro: Have you ever been scamed (online or not)??
ICAntF331MyFAce: PogChamp
HellxNebula: @georgehotz what language you recommend for a beginner and how to evolve?
SpaceGhost8: :)
iIyaRPV: PogChamp
Ayyyy420Lmao: i'm not tho
ICAntF331MyFAce: PogChamp YOU
DecayingSkullz: HYYYYYPE
logi6000: thanks. bye
pz3300: Hype
Lourned: PogChamp
ooMariaoo: oh
joker2k999: no, bro... don't read the comments. lol
dingus74: lool
MrTriharder: PogChamp
dorkmo: hype train historyyyy
Emanuell45: true
mashafique: PogChamp
privacyisnowhere: what do you think about Genetic Algorithms?
Landowner555: i relate with the comment above it
n0_0xygen: PogChamp
opus_000: 🤔
AzazelTheGoat: everyone go like that comment
mutrx: Poggers
jimmyadaro: 2020 mf
ICAntF331MyFAce: PogChamp
tornpaperyoyos: 2019?
mutrx: PogChamp
jimmyadaro: Have you ever been scamed (online or not)?
ICAntF331MyFAce: LUL
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz Thanks for tonight stream. I really REALLY enjoyed it.
koreanfoodyum: HELLO FUTURE PEOPLE READING THIS VOD!
bigduddas: Pog
localcanofdutchgold: Pog
SpaceGhost8: sitting in my house ordering amazon prime now
ooMariaoo: Pog
funwayz: HI SON I WAS HERE
THX1342: LUL
braininavatt: Im so proud BibleThump
UniversalGeneve: history == COMMA.BIO LUL LUL
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Have you ever been scamed (online or not)??
brownyyyylocks: @dorkmo yeahhhh buddyyyy
alicyka: aight sick I'm gonna jerk off to anime for 3 weeks
doctorgenus: everyone will google geohotz github corona once he cures it!
ahahahaitslit: alllllaaahhhhhhh
mutrx: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
C0deCane: LUL ahahahaha
Penguino138: @georgehotz Keep streaming and keeping us all calm we appreciate it
Lourned: lets riot PogChamp
localcanofdutchgold: OMEGALUL
ooMariaoo: loll
MrTriharder: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
mounnrocc: i dont but thats ok
MrTriharder: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
foti_kasparov: WE DON'T
ICAntF331MyFAce: PogChamp
tornpaperyoyos: My mommy says I matter
mashafique: LUL
SofiaLouise: damn
TeaLeafi: i matter more then u 5head heheheheh
latenightbj: netflix time l8
Ayyyy420Lmao: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
MrTriharder: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
joker2k999: i want two boxes! sold
logi6000: organize the worlds information
leandzz: PogChamp
ahahahaitslit: ALLLLAHHHHHHHH
asanti20: Change the world by getting the corona virus
brofessorbob: San Diego hit the inflection point today
ICAntF331MyFAce: PogChamp 👋
Piqcyl: XD
doctorgenus: peace out bro
braininavatt: I am special cuz I've lived this far BibleThump
AzazelTheGoat: i did my part
Belowzer0w: hive mind matters
koreanfoodyum: bye
PiroFloydian: gnight
THX1342: I N S P I R A T I O N Kreygasm
Stegosaurian: N O O N E M A T T E R S
yaus_baus: what a memer
noobaj: PogChamp
mashafique: BibleThump
foti_kasparov: bb
logi6000: bue
Incurs0: PogChamp
TeaLeafi: wowoowowooww
TeaLeafi: rip
Lourned: TIME TO RIOT
wheely_mcbones: nice motivational ending
ooMariaoo: oh
dr_set: BibleThump
bufferovrflw: <3
localcanofdutchgold: no loop PepeHands
AzazelTheGoat: see ya chat
innerbean: all trolls matter
asanti20: Woooo
THX1342: hahahha thanks geo, gn
tornpaperyoyos: MY MOMMY SAYS I MATTER YOU ASSHOLE
braininavatt: time for HYPE TRAIN
pwnbase: HeyGuys
TeaLeafi: noooooooooo
foti_kasparov: CLIP THE END SOMEONE
UniversalGeneve: goodnight.
marcosbrolkin: nice
phrixus_bro: tyler1H1 tyler1H2
ooMariaoo: oh hype train
logi6000: time to go check out pornhub premium